<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>哈佛商业评论</title><description>哈佛商业评论全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link/> https://hbr.org/ <item><title><![CDATA[How to Take Better Breaks at Work, According to Research]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/05/how-to-take-better-breaks-at-work-according-to-research]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄形象>; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/05/May23_31_SelmanHosgor.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Selman Hoşgör 的艺术作品； malerapaso/Getty Images（沙漏）； Iryna Veklich/Getty Images（时钟）； Westend61/Getty Images（笔记本电脑上的女人）； WeAre/Getty Images（做瑜伽的女人）； Johannes Mann/Getty Images（工人）； Anton Vierietin（抱头的男人）&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;总结。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp ;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;全天定期休息可以提高幸福感和工作表现，但很少有人定期休息 &amp;#8212;或采用最有效的类型。对 80 多项关于休息的研究进行了系统回顾，概述了一些最佳做法，可以让我们从工作中抽出大部分时间，包括地点、时间和方式。它还为管理者和组织提供了一些技巧，鼓励他们的员工进行更有益和更频繁的休息。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href= &quot;/2023/05/how-to-take-better-breaks-at-work-according-to-research?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/05 /how-to-take-better-breaks-at-work-according-to-research?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;对于我们中的许多人来说，提高工作效率意味着花费更多工作时间。我们花在工作任务上的时间越多，完成的工作就越多，这似乎很直观。毫不奇怪，流行文学中充斥着关于如何最大限度地利用工作时间的建议。例如，“CEO 的日常”通常包括凌晨 4 点起床、周末工作，甚至是“&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnet.com/culture/marissa-mayer- says-the-se-secret-of-success-is-working-130-hours-a-week/&quot;>;关于你去洗手间频率的策略&lt;/a>;。&quot;为了应对不断增加的工作量，许多员工选择埋头苦干、不吃午饭并在下班后留下来。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;但始终在线（并做得好！）的成本很高。超过一半的员工 (59%) 表示感到精疲力竭 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.aflac.com/docs/awr/pdf/2022-trends-and-topics/2022-aflac-awr-employee-well -being-and-mental-health.pdf&quot;>;根据 Aflac 最近的一项调查&lt;/a>;。敬业度发生了相反的变化，&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gallup.com/workplace/468233/employee-engagement-needs-rebound-2023.aspx&quot;>;美国工人的敬业度正在下降&lt;/a>;。令人担忧的是，&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.emerald.com/insight/content/doi/10.1108/LODJ-11-2015-0249/full/html&quot;>;高度倦怠&lt;/a>;和&lt;a href= “https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/10.1177/0972150916631082”>;低参与率&lt;/a>;与绩效受阻有关。我们可以做些什么来解决我们不断下降的幸福感，同时保持表现？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;暂停工作而不是继续工作可能对这两个方面都有帮助。我们的团队对两种相互竞争的说法很感兴趣——一种更侧重于将工作更多地作为绩效指标，另一种则关注定期休息以保护健康——以及关于这些主题的个别研究的混合（有时甚至相互矛盾）的结果，我们的团队进行了&lt;a href=&quot;https://psycnet.apa.org/record/2022-90592-001&quot;>;对现有工作场所休息研究的系统回顾&lt;/a>;。在分析 80 多项研究后，我们（与我们的同事 Zahra Premji、Timothy Wingate、Connie Deng、Lisa Bélanger 和 Nick Turner）证实，全天暂停工作可以改善幸福感，还有助于完成更多工作。与长时间工作的流行说法相反，我们的研究表明，在工作时间内休息不仅不会降低绩效，而且有助于提高绩效。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;为什么休息有益于健康 -存在和表现？&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;就像需要充电的电池一样，我们所有人的身体和心理资源都是有限的。当我们的电池电量不足时，&lt;a href=&quot;https://psycnet.apa.org/doiLanding?doi=10.1037%2Fa0036904&quot;>;我们会感到&lt;/a>;耗尽、精疲力竭和压力山大。&lt;/p>; &lt;p >;在油箱中只剩下很少的能量时继续工作会给健康和工作表现带来压力。在极端情况下，不间断的工作会导致恶性循环：尽管员工处于疲惫状态，但仍试图完成任务，但无法做好，甚至会犯错误，导致更多的工作和更少的资源来处理这些相同的任务。这意味着我们工作得越多，生产力就越低，我们就会变得更加疲惫。例如，想想同一句话读了第五遍，仍然没有吸收它。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;好消息是，休息可以帮助员工充电，并缩短疲惫和减少的负面螺旋生产率。然而，并非所有休息的效果都是一样的。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;什么类型的休息对改善幸福感和表现更有效？&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;休息有许多不同的形式和形式：锻炼、浏览社交媒体、散步、与他人社交、小睡、吃午饭等。然而，我们的系统回顾表明并非所有休息类型都同样有效。换句话说，&lt;em>;如何&lt;/em>;暂停工作很重要。以下是一些需要考虑的常见休息要素：&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;休息时间和时间&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;更长的休息时间不一定等同于更好的休息时间。仅几分钟但定期（微休息）从工作中脱离出来就足以防止疲惫和提高绩效。例如，员工可以短暂休息吃零食、伸展身体或只是凝视窗外。此外，休息的时间也很重要——早上休息时间越短越好，而下午晚些时候休息时间越长越好。这是因为工作日的疲劳加剧，我们需要在下午有更多的休息时间来充电。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;休息的地点&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;休息的地点对我们的生活有很大的影响恢复。在办公桌前伸懒腰和出去走走看起来都是非常相似的休息活动，但它们的充电潜力可能有很大不同。我们的审查表明，在户外休息并享受绿色空间比仅仅呆在办公桌前更能为员工充电。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;休息活动&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;在工作期间进行体育锻炼休息可以有效地改善幸福感和表现。对于对脑力要求很高的工作，锻炼是一种特别有价值的恢复工具。然而，这种休息类型的积极影响是短暂的，员工需要定期锻炼才能产生好处。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;尽管有这些好处，但锻炼并不是最受员工欢迎的休息方式雇员。我们的审查表明，浏览社交媒体是最常见的休息方式——几乎每个人 (97%) 都表示参与过这项活动。然而，&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0747563215302703&quot;>;研究人员发现&lt;/a>;在工作休息期间滚动浏览社交媒体会导致情绪疲惫。因此，&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0747563215302703&quot;>;人们最终会&lt;/a>; 创造力和工作参与度下降，而不是资源得到补充。因此，这种类型的休息可能无法有效提高性能。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Furry break companion&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mdpi.com/1660-4601 /16/19/3670&quot;>;我们评论中的一项研究&lt;/a>;表明，与狗的互动可以降低皮质醇激素的水平，皮质醇激素是压力的客观指标。由于对性能的影响仍不清楚，因此需要在该领域进行更多研究。然而，我们确实强烈怀疑，与毛茸茸的伙伴一起休息对许多员工来说是有效的。 &lt;a href=&quot;https://psycnet.apa.org/doiLanding?doi=10.1037%2F1076-8998.6.1.81&quot;>;研究表明&lt;/a>;与宠物的互动可以显着提升个人的心理健康，这反过来又是&lt;a href=&quot;https://psycnet.apa.org/record/1999-15533-008&quot;>;与绩效密切相关&lt;/a>;。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;管理者和组织可以做些什么来鼓励休息？ &lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;仅仅有休息时间并不能保证收益。工人可能不会以最有效的方式使用他们的休息时间或根本不休息。作为组织中的决策者和榜样，管理者在鼓励有效的工作休息方面处于重要地位。这可以通过多种方式实现：&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;培养对休息时间的积极态度&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;虽然员工通常对休息时间持积极态度并报告说休息时间有益于绩效，但这种情绪并不总是由管理人员。这可以阻止人们充电。因此，让管理人员了解工间休息与绩效相关的好处至关重要。例如，人力资源经理可以将此信息纳入公司的健康培训计划。组织还可以考虑实施“健康时刻”（类似于安全时刻），在此期间他们可以分享他们的有效休息策略和集思广益的有趣休息活动。甚至在工作场所悬挂有关休息的好处和最佳做法的海报也能起到很大的作用。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;自己休息&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;经理可以通过采取以下方式传达休息的重要性定期最有效的类型，员工可以模仿。例如，一位经常在附近公园遛狗的经理可以告诉她的员工，她将暂时离开工作岗位。这样的策略不仅树立了一个积极的榜样，而且还为不打扰休息设定了明确的界限。以身作则将有助于防止与休息相关的可能的耻辱和内疚。越来越多的组织领导者&lt;a href=&quot;https://onlinemba.wsu.edu/blog/5-ways-the-worlds-top-ceos-maintain-their-work-life-balance/&quot;>;是有前途的认识到这一点&lt;/a>;，甚至分享他们的&lt;a href=&quot;/2020/12/im-a-ceo-and-a-working-dad-heres-what-i-wish-i-did-differently&quot;>;遗憾关于没有足够的休息时间&lt;/a>;。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;安排专门的休息时间&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;我们的审查表明，许多员工无法定期休息，或者被劝阻，因为的耻辱;因此，我们建议管理人员和组织安排专门的休息时间。这样的休息时间需要小心执行。严格的休息时间表，例如强制员工仅在特定时间和预定时间停止工作，会降低员工的自主权，甚至会对员工产生有害影响。我们建议提供一定长度的休息时间，例如每天一小时，并由员工自行决定何时以及多久休息一次。提供灵活的工作时间表、创新的工作场所休息计划，例如“休息票”（例如，每天发放允许员工选择休息一小时的票），或提供现场社交或体育活动，这些都是最佳休息时间的一些例子&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;为休息创造空间&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;正如我们在上面强调的那样，休息的位置可以在最大化其利益方面发挥重要作用。例如，拥有一个小公园或室内绿地可以传达组织对促进工作休息的承诺，并提高休息对员工绩效的好处。为了进一步发挥户外休息的好处，您还可以将其变成一个不拴绳的遛狗公园，喜欢与动物互动的员工可以在这里玩耍。这也可以用作招聘工具，因为&lt;a href=&quot;https://theconversation.com/pandemic-pet-boom-has-increased-the-demand-for-pet-friendly-workplaces-200217&quot;>;宠物友好的工作场所正在兴起&lt;/a>;，许多公司已经采用了&lt;a href=&quot;https://psycnet.apa.org/record/2022-68687-003&quot;>;宠物友好政策&lt;/a>;。 &lt;/p>; &lt;p>;员工在家工作的组织也可以通过安排在线公园会议来利用他们可用的空间，远程员工可以在方便的户外空间边走边坐边参加会议。或者，他们可以为员工分配“休息预算”以创建自己的休息空间。例如，员工可以购买室内植物或瑜伽垫。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;员工绩效一直是组织关注的问题，如今越来越多的组织正在努力解决员工福祉问题。工作休息是改善两者的有前途的工具。组织需要认识到休息的重要性，并有意识地努力促进有效的休息。&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 31 May 2023 20:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[A Roadmap to Success for the U.S. Semiconductor Industry - SPONSOR CONTENT FROM ARIZONA COMMERCE AUTHORITY]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/sponsored/2023/05/a-roadmap-to-success-for-the-u-s-semiconductor-industry]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;html>; &lt;head>;&lt;/head>; &lt;body>; &lt;figure>; &lt;img 咏叹调-describedby=&quot;caption-attachment-357154&quot; src=&quot;/resources/images/article_assets/2023/05/ACA_HERO-SunsetHiker-Rocks-RIGHT-1200x720-1.jpg&quot; >; &lt;/figure>; &lt;p>;Yogi Berra 曾经说过，“如果您不知道要去哪里，那么您最终会去别的地方。”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;在像半导体这样重要的行业中，“去别的地方”是行不通的。半导体或微芯片是现代电子产品的大脑——它们是美国经济和国家安全未来的核心。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;美国要在半导体制造和创新方面引领世界，我们需要知道在哪里&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;2022 年签署成为美国法律的 CHIPS 和科学法案是至关重要的第一步。这项具有历史意义的举措拨款 520 亿美元用于半导体研究和制造计划，同时建立了针对半导体的临时税收抵免。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;要取得成功，CHIPS 法案需要一个路线图，一个计划来指导我们今天和未来几十年的行动&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;对于该计划，请查看国家半导体经济路线图 (NSER)。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;国家战略，行业主导&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt; div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div id=&quot;DFP_IC_pos3&quot;>; &lt;script type=&quot;text/javascript&quot;>;if (isAdobeSync()) googletag.cmd.push(function() { googletag.display(&quot;DFP_IC_pos3&quot;); }) ;&lt;/script>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;NSER（发音为“answer”）是一项以行业为主导的 10 年计划，旨在提高美国在半导体制造领域的竞争力并加强供应链弹性，制图工业界、政府和学术界的领导者为美国发明的技术加强制造生态系统的途径。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;NSER 提供严格的数据和分析，在四个领域建立明确的目标：基础设施、供应链、劳动力和创业精神。包括亚利桑那州在内的各州正在率先采用创新解决方案来推进这四个目标。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;2022 年 11 月，亚利桑那州 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.azcommerce.com/news-events/news/2022/11/ governor-ducey-announces-100-million-to-enhance-arizona-semiconductor-ecosystem/&quot;>;宣布&lt;/a>; 1亿美元的资金用于加强其半导体基础设施、劳动力和研究能力，重点是加速发展、商业化和制造下一代美国半导体技术。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;此外，&lt;a href=&quot;https://news.maricopa.edu/blogs/semiconductor-manufacturing-industry -booming-jumpstart-your-career-10-days&quot;>;Semiconductor Technician Quick Start&lt;/a>; 正在引导更多女性和少数族裔进入该行业。这是马里科帕社区学院、亚利桑那州商业管理局和英特尔的合作伙伴，这个为期两周、40 小时的新手训练营教授基本技能，并包括在毕业时与英特尔面谈的机会。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;倒车半导体下滑&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;近几十年来，随着产能向海外转移，美国半导体制造业稳步下滑，中国和亚洲其他国家大力投资芯片制造和研发（研发）。按照目前的路径，到 2033 年，美国在微芯片制造中的份额可能会从今天的 11% 下降到 8%——低于 30 年前的 40%。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;实现 CHIPS 法案的全部价值并发展整个制造生态系统将需要政策制定者、行业参与者、学术界和其他利益相关者在竞争前的共同利益领域共同努力。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;如果这些利益相关者实现 NSER 目标，美国可以获得多达 30% 的资本投资根据波士顿咨询集团的数据，未来 10 年全球半导体行业。这可能会使美国在全球容量中的份额增加多达 17%，扭转长达数十年的下滑趋势。&lt;/p>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div id=&quot;DFP_IC_pos4&quot;>; &lt;script type=&quot;text/javascript&quot; >;if (isAdobeSync()) googletag.cmd.push(function() { googletag.display(&quot;DFP_IC_pos4&quot;); });&lt;/script>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;一个转变这种规模将对美国经济的弹性产生重大好处，推动创造数以千计的高薪工作，提升我们的技术领先地位，并加强美国的国家安全。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;那么我们从哪里开始呢？ NSER 从基础设施开始。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;加强国内基础设施&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;半导体是美国经济中资本最密集的行业之一。除了受过良好教育的劳动力和研发设施之外，芯片制造还需要物理场地、设备和交通基础设施。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;NSER 的长期愿景包括使国内监管和激励环境与竞争市场保持一致，以增加美国的吸引力，投资于共享研发基础设施以鼓励合作，并加强基础设施以提高可持续性。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;提高供应链弹性&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;半导体供应链的极端的复杂性使美国面临商品和服务流动中断的巨大风险。这些风险最严重地体现在材料、晶圆制造以及封装、组装和测试 (PAT) 方面。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;东亚地区约占所有 PAT 产能的 80%，其中 40% 在中国​​大陆.美国支持不到 5% 的全球 PAT 容量。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;为了提高美国的弹性，NSER 规定增加陆上、近岸和友岸活动。这一努力应包括建立可靠的材料、消耗品、中间产品和设备来源，同时提高国内半导体制造能力。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;但由于完全在岸外包成本高昂且不切实际，该路线图还提倡保持美国获得全球市场和提高供应链可见性。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;解决人员问题&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;半导体行业面临的最大挑战之一是培养员工队伍。在美国，该行业雇用了大约 277,000 名工人。为了满足 NSER 设想的未来劳动力需求，该劳动力库需要在未来十年内增加数十万人。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;流失率；美国学生对科学、技术、工程和数学的兴趣下降； &lt;/p>; &lt;p>;NSER 提出了一系列强有力的行动来加强人才管道，方法是确保公平和包容的培训机会，增加技术工人的保留率，解决可逆的人才流失因素，并确保劳动力仍然能够适应不断变化的行业需求。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;赋予企业家权力&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;企业家通过改进工艺和生产方法为半导体行业做出贡献，通常会带来增量收益&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;然而，企业家面临的挑战是巨大的，例如吸引资金和获得制造商测试产品所需的设施、设备和材料。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;NSER 建议扩大对企业家的私人、政府和学术投资；改善设施和知识的获取； &lt;/p>; &lt;p>;CHIPS 法案重振了 21 世纪的美国半导体行业。为了利用这一势头，该行业现在必须着眼大局并迅速采取行动以改善整个制造业格局。 NSER 是行业成功的路线图。&lt;/p>; &lt;hr>; &lt;p>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.azcommerce.com/national-semiconductor-economic-roadmap/&quot;>;&lt;strong>;&lt;em>;阅读点击此处了解更多关于国家半导体经济路线图的信息。&lt;/em>;&lt;/strong>;&lt;/a>;&lt;/p>; &lt;/body>; &lt;/html>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 31 May 2023 04:25:04 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Are You Failing to Prepare the Next Generation of C-Suite Leaders? - SPONSOR CONTENT FROM DAGGERWING]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/sponsored/2023/05/are-you-failing-to-prepare-the-next-generation-of-c-suite-leaders]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;html>; &lt;head>;&lt;/head>; &lt;body>; &lt;figure>; &lt;img 咏叹调-describedby=&quot;caption-attachment-356905&quot; src=&quot;/resources/images/article_assets/2023/05/HBR-Hero.png&quot; >; &lt;/figure>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;&lt;em>;作者：Chris Thornton &lt;/em >;&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“让我们一起度过难关吧。”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;对于许多领导者来说，这是过去三年的口头禅。 “让我们及时度过这一刻，专注于满足我们眼前需求的短期解决方案，当一切恢复正常时，我们将处理我们一直搁置的所有问题。”&lt;/ p>; &lt;p>;现在是时候处理这​​些问题了：新的商业模式；供应链;环境、社会和治理 (ESG)；新的工作方式；新技术;新的人才需求；新的生产力差距。高管们意识到，后起之秀的领导者缺乏领导公司走向未来的技能、知识和能力。&lt;/p>;开发团队就如何富有同理心、领导虚拟团队和进行勇敢的对话进行领导力培训。虽然这些通常是好的和令人愉快的，但微观培训不能解决宏观问题——我在这里告诉你它不会有什么不同。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;现在需要的是全面改革了解组织如何培养和准备他们的领导者，以推动他们的公司走向未来，并将自己推向最高管理层。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;您可能在想，“提升技能？多年来我们一直这样做！”你是对的。它一直被用作实现性能的长期投资。&lt;/p>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div id=&quot;DFP_IC_pos3&quot;>; &lt;script type=&quot;text/javascript&quot;>;if (isAdobeSync()) googletag。 cmd.push(function() { googletag.display(&quot;DFP_IC_pos3&quot;); });&lt;/script>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;虽然它曾经是一个“很高兴拥有”，它现在已成为业务关键优先事项。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;当然，每个组织都有从令人难以置信的战略到非常个人化的需求——有些需要他们的人事领导者转变整个职能，解决他们的供应链挑战，并且留住客户，而其他人则需要他们的人才领导者来加速他们的数字化转型，展示灵活性和同理心。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;无论情况如何，组织都可以通过以下三种方式开始并确定正确的调整步骤具有最高管理层目标的人事领导者的技能：&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;&lt;em>;打破你的研究孤岛并勇敢起来。 &lt;/em>;&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;大多数公司都淹没在员工和候选人数据中。问题不在于数量；它的连接性。员工和求职者数据只能说明部分情况，通常 HR 拥有并保护这些数据。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;为什么这很重要？因为很少有倾听工具可以帮助一线经理确定他们的团队未来需要哪些技能来满足客户的需求。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;那么，该怎么办？停止孤立地查看员工反馈，开始将其与消费者、客户和部门数据（包括顾问范围和支出）联系起来。创建一个跨职能团队，负责讲述您的员工（尤其是您的领导者）需要什么的整个故事。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;让团队找出他们在客户体验方面失败的地方。询问他们为什么员工要离开以及这对合作伙伴有什么影响。询问他们您是否正在聘请顾问来解决我们自己的团队应该能够解决的问题。&lt;/p>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div id=&quot;DFP_IC_pos4&quot;>; &lt;script type=&quot;text/javascript&quot;>;如果(isAdobeSync()) googletag.cmd.push(function() { googletag.display(&quot;DFP_IC_pos4&quot;); });&lt;/script>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;创建您自己的列表痛苦、困难的问题，并要求团队看看数据能告诉你什么。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;除了最高管理层之外，你的组织中没有人可以拥有这种观点。因此，不要指望其他任何人对此进行授权。首席执行官、首席人力资源官/首席产品官、首席财务官、首席运营官……你拥有这个。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;&lt;em>;停止关注症状，开始关注根本原因。&lt;/em>;&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我们都听过这样一句话：“人们离开的不是糟糕的工作，而是糟糕的经理。”离开公司的人还认为冥想应用程序将补偿不知道如何领导的领导者。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我不是在敲打调解应用程序。 （我手机上有两个）。但提出正确的问题并深入了解整个企业需要改变什么以实现增长目标的根源是关键。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;为员工提供免费订阅冥想应用程序可以对员工产生积极影响日常工作，但这并不能解决导致他们感到压力和精疲力尽的根本原因。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;相反，为了降低血压和提高工作满意度，领导者可以提出以下问题： “我们的人民领袖是否接受过领导培训？” “他们知道如何传达战略并将其转化为他们的团队吗？” “人事领导者是否知道如何展示端到端的思维并采取行动？” “人事领导是否知道他们需要做什么才能实现最高管理层的目标？”然后在开始发现根本原因的过程时问“为什么”。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;&lt;em>;激活企业以实现最高管理层的目标。&lt;/em>;&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p >; &lt;p>;现在您已经收集了反馈和数据，是时候激活领导者以及整个企业所需的技能和能力，以实现最高管理层的目标。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;到为此，领导者必须确定技能差距在哪里，确定领导者缺乏哪些技能，并决定改进哪些技能以领导组织走向未来。现在是时候开展培训和建立学习文化，让领导者跟上时代的步伐，并为他们配备所需的技能。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;但这并没有就此结束。除了持续和全面的学习，您的组织还必须设定目标和成功目标。 70/20/10 模型在这里会做很多，这意味着 70% 的培训是通过在职经验完成的，20% 通过与他人的关系和互动完成，10% 通过正式培训和教育。除此之外，测量过程将显示培训是否有所作为。这不仅仅是关于受训者的感受——而是关于将培训与业务成果联系起来。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这一切都不容易。这需要一点勇气、一些最高管理层的责任感和极大的好奇心。您的经理将您的团队团结在一起，他们理应处于成功、学习和成长为下一代领导者的位置。&lt;/p>; &lt;hr>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;&lt;em>;Chris Thornton 是集团高级负责人在 Daggerwing。&lt;/em>;&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;&lt;em>;了解 Daggerwing 如何帮助您的组织 &lt;a href=&quot;http://daggerwinggroup.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;创造一种学习文化&lt;/a>;。&lt;/em>;&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;hr>; &lt;p>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>; &lt;/body>; &lt;/html>; &lt;! -- 引用 -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 31 May 2023 00:25:04 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[To Improve Your Work Performance, Get Some Exercise]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/05/to-improve-your-work-performance-get-some-exercise]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄形象>; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/05/May23_27_650521689.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Klaus Vedfelt/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt; span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;虽然身体活动对整体幸福感的好处已得到广泛认可，但缺乏关于它如何影响工作成果的研究，包括工作表现和健康。来自英国和中国的大约 200 名员工参加了为期 10 天的研究，作者在研究中收集了自我报告和客观的身体活动数据（通过可穿戴智能手环设备），以及自我和主管报告的工作成果。他们发现了一些关于影响员工和组织的日常身体活动的值得注意的发现，以及一些研究支持的方法来获得增加身体活动的许多好处。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/05/to-improve-your-work-performance-get-some-exercise?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br >; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/05/to-improve-your-work-performance-get-some-exercise?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;全球，&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.who.int/news-room/fact-sheets/detail/physical-activity&quot;>;14 亿成年人运动量不足&lt;/a>;，其中三分之一的女性和四分之一的男性不运动从事足够的身体活动。事实上，自 2001 年以来，身体活动水平没有任何改善，高收入国家缺乏身体活动的情况是低收入国家的两倍。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;为了对抗缺乏身体活动的负面影响， 2018 年，&lt;a href=&quot;https://apps.who.int/iris/bitstream/handle/10665/272722/9789241514187-eng.pdf&quot;>;世界卫生组织&lt;/a>; (WHO) 发起了一项全球行动旨在到 2030 年将缺乏身体活动的人数减少 15% 的计划。通过促进身体活动和鼓励个人定期锻炼，世卫组织力求最大限度地发挥身体活动的益处：预防和管理非传染性疾病，如心血管疾病（包括冠心病和中风），各种类型的癌症，改善整体身心健康，提高认知能力，并确保健康的成长和发展。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;尽管身体活动对整体健康的益处已得到广泛认可，缺乏关于它如何影响工作成果的研究，包括工作绩效和健康。这一点尤为重要，因为各种新兴的工作模式带来了更大的灵活性和便利性。然而，我们发现自己坐得越来越多，动得越来越少，因为我们中的许多人不再需要通勤上班或从一个会议走到另一个会议。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;身体活动如何影响工作绩效&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;鉴于我们醒着的大部分时间都花在工作上，为了支持世界卫生组织增加身体活动的倡议，我们的 &lt;a href=&quot;https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/full/10.1111/peps.12585&quot; >;recent research&lt;/a>; points to some important work-related implications of physical activity.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Approximately 200 employees from the UK and China participated in a 10-day study in which we captured self-reported and objective physical activity data (via a wearable smart band device), as well as self- and supervisor-reported work outcomes. We uncovered some noteworthy findings about daily physical activity that impact employees and organizations:&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Motivation for physical activity predicts physical activity.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;It may seem obvious that being &lt;em>;motivated&lt;/em>; to partake in an activity would lead to &lt;em>;doing&lt;/em>; said activity, but anyone who has ever made and then abandoned a New Year&#39;s resolution knows this isn&#39;t necessarily the case. People&#39;s &lt;a href=&quot;https://psycnet.apa.org/record/1997-43682-004&quot;>;autonomous motivation&lt;/a>;, a stable individual difference reflecting the degree to which one feels self-determined to engage in a behavior, is a critical &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.annualreviews.org/doi/abs/10.1146/annurev-orgpsych-032117-104640&quot;>;personal resource&lt;/a>; that can prompt individuals to engage in physical activity. Importantly, the more autonomous the form of motivation — in other words, the more people consider physical activity to be a fun and enjoyable activity rather than something to dread — the more likely they are to engage in daily physical activity.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Physical activity accrues next-day, work-relevant resources.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;We found that daily physical activity generated a package of next-day resources, called “resource caravans,” that contributed to work-related outcomes.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The first resource immediately afforded by physical activity is &lt;a href=&quot;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/12531177/&quot;>;quality sleep&lt;/a>;, or a person&#39;s degree of satisfaction with their daily sleep experience. Physical activity promotes protein synthesis and facilitates quality sleep as a homeostatic feedback process benefitting the body and brain. The second resource gain is &lt;a href=&quot;https://psycnet.apa.org/record/2008-13168-008&quot;>;vigor&lt;/a>;, an affective resource associated with energy and vitality. The third resource gain is &lt;a href=&quot;https://psycnet.apa.org/record/2005-08269-016&quot;>;task focus&lt;/a>;, a cognitive resource that supports enhanced information processing, attention, and concentration.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Physical activity improves next-day job performance and health.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Existing research on the impact of physical activity in the work context has focused on physical activity during &lt;a href=&quot;https://psycnet.apa.org/record/2022-01996-001&quot;>;specific periods&lt;/a>; (eg, exercising over the lunch break), neglecting consideration of physical activity throughout the whole day. This has further contributed to inconsistent findings, as employees may perceive a depletion of resources (such as vigor and concentration) immediately after physical activity, which may actually interfere with their work.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;All this is to say that it may &lt;a href=&quot;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/17032494/&quot;>;take some time&lt;/a>; to experience the work-related benefits of physical activity. Sure enough, our research finds time-lagged benefits of physical activity on &lt;em>;next-day&lt;/em>; task performance, creativity, and health symptoms. Across two studies, we consistently found that employees&#39; daily physical activity throughout the day generates resource caravans consisting of physical (sleep), affective (vigor), and cognitive (task focus) resources, which further contribute to next-day job performance and health outcomes in different ways. Physical and affective resources serve to reduce daily bodily pains; cognitive resources contribute more to daily task performance; and affective resources and cognitive resources are stronger predictors of self-rated creative performance.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Job self-efficacy shapes the capacity to gain resources from physical activity&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://journals.aom.org/doi/abs/10.5465/3069429&quot;>;Job self-efficacy&lt;/a>;, which reflects an employee&#39;s perception of their capacity to perform their job, amplifies the resource-generating benefits of daily physical activity on sleep quality and task focus. People with higher levels of self-efficacy tend to hold stronger positive beliefs in their motivation and ability to acquire work-related resources from daily physical activity.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;How to get more physical&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;If you&#39;ve found yourself moving less while working remotely, here are three research-backed ways to reap the many benefits of increasing your physical activity:&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Focus on building a habit of daily physical activity.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Anything worth doing is worth doing slowly. Don&#39;t be discouraged if you don&#39;t see immediate work-related benefits from physical activity. Our research specifically examined time-lagged, next-day benefits of physical activity, demonstrating significant resource gains that contributed to performance and health payouts. Day by day, concentrate on forming new healthy habits, and results will unfold in time.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Remember that some is better than none.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;We often talk ourselves out of physical activity because we&#39;re just too tired, hungry, stressed, or busy (ourselves included!). Our findings echo the perspective of the WHO, in that “some physical activity is better than doing none.” To realize health benefits and minimize the harmful health effects of being sedentary, the WHO recommends that adults ages 18 to 64 years should engage in at least 2.5 hours of moderate-intensity or at least 1.25 hours of high-intensity physical activity each week.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Our research identifies moderate-intensity physical activity as most impactful for generating physical, affective, and cognitive resource gains that further benefit next-day task performance, creativity, and health outcomes. Given that low-intensity physical activity may require longer engagement to reap resource gains, and high-intensity physical activity may lend itself more easily to injury, moderate-intensity exercise is a more feasible goal for many. Moreover, we found that even short periods of physical activity, even 20 minutes each day, were sufficient to generate resources that contributed to employees&#39; next-day task performance and health.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Motivated or not, just get moving!&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Our research reveals that even employees who dislike exercising can reap benefits from daily physical activity. We also found that autonomously motivated individuals are more likely to participate in physical activity, implicating the “fun factor” as a key driver of physical activity engagement — so find an activity that makes exercise less onerous and more enjoyable. If a bootcamp session isn&#39;t your thing, try a challenging hike or a boxing class. The next time you want to swap exercise for a comfy couch, aim for just 20 minutes.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3 style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;. . .&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;If you&#39;re looking to up your game at work, make an effort to include more physical activity into your days. Your body will thank you, and your mind will reward you with more energy, better task focus, and improved creativity.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 30 May 2023 22:25:04 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Research: How Successful Health Care Organizations Keep Worker Morale Up]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/05/research-how-successful-health-care-organizations-keep-worker-morale-up]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/05/May23_27_1273381559.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Jena Ardell/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;There are signs that some US health care organizations are scoring some successes in addressing the worker morale and retention crisis. But data from Press Ganey surveys shows that there is a widening gap between the most- and least-successful organizations. This article draws lessons from the former. It discusses three key elements needed to engage workers, make them more resilient, and make them feel more aligned with their leaders.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/05/research-how-successful-health-care-organizations-keep-worker-morale-up?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/05/research-how-successful-health-care-organizations-keep-worker-morale-up?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;The workforce burnout and retention crisis has been dominating health care for the last three years, but data (finally) shows some encouraging trends. Analyses of survey responses from the last three years show that the decline in workforce “engagement” has flattened out and “resilience” is actually improving. The data also shows a spreading of the pack — with bigger variation between organizations where workforce morale and retention is improving versus others where the slide continues. This article will capture some of the best practices that have the potential to turn a vicious cycle into a virtuous one.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Survey Findings&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;The following analyses are based on about 1.6 million survey responses from employees of US health care organizations (including over 121,500 physicians) during 2020, 2021, and 2022 conducted by our company, Press Ganey. While burnout has been &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.hhs.gov/about/news/2022/05/23/new-surgeon-general-advisory-sounds-alarm-on-health-worker-burnout-and-resignation.html&quot;>;worsening for all types of health care professionals&lt;/a>;, three additional metrics provide a more complete picture of what is happening in health care:&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Engagement&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;During the last year, there has been a flattening of the downward trend for engagement, which measures employees&#39; emotional bond with the organization and their willingness to go above and beyond their job descriptions to meet the needs of patients and colleagues. Using a five-point scale, engagement declined .10 the year after the pandemic started (calendar year 2021) — the largest decline in engagement for caregivers that Press Ganey has observed, but the decline has slowed, with only a .02 decline in 2022.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Alignment&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;There was a similar flattening of the rate of decline of alignment&lt;em>;, &lt;/em>;which is assessed through measures that reflect providers&#39; perceptions of their relationship with organizational leadership. For example, if they do not feel respected or that their voices are heard in decisions that impact their practice, they are not likely to feel aligned with the organization even if they are proud of it. This helps explain why so many women physicians have quit.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Resilience&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;There was actually some improvement in 2022 in resilience:&amp;nbsp;the ability to find meaning in work (&lt;em>;activation&lt;/em>;) and recharge when away from work (&lt;em>;decompression&lt;/em>;). (See &lt;a href=&quot;/2018/10/helping-health-care-workers-avoid-burnout&quot;>;this article&lt;/a>; for specific survey items used to gauge both.) The good news is that activation remained stable throughout the pandemic for virtually everyone in health care. These are good people motivated by doing good. But the even better news is that decompression improved in 2022 after two years of steep decline. This data indicates that caregivers are learning how to cope with the stresses of this era, their organizations are doing a better job of supporting them, or both.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;These three encouraging trends don&#39;t apply to everyone. Our data shows a widening gap between the top 10% of organizations in workforce engagement and the bottom 10%.&amp;nbsp;In short, employee engagement at many organizations is improving, while at others it is getting worse. The data suggests that some organizations are trapped in a vicious cycle in which stress is leading to burnout leading to worse performance leading to more stress. But other organizations (or sub-units of those organizations) are in a virtuous cycle in which pride among caregivers leads to better engagement which leads to better performance which leads to more pride.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The picture that emerges from this data is that health care has dedicated and hardworking people who have been through a lot but, in the right circumstances, still have more to give. What are those right circumstances? Data from organizations in the top decile of workforce engagement offers insights.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Top performers scored markedly higher than others in five specific domains: support from and confidence in senior leadership, recognition of the contribution of employees, respect and involvement in decision-making, manageable job stress, and adequate staffing.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;How do we get from a vicious cycle to a virtuous one? By implementing these measures:&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Authentically listen.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;The first thing organizations and their leaders should (and can) do immediately is to listen and understand the challenges facing their individual employees and their leaders. What it means to &lt;em>;authentically &lt;/em>;listen changed during the pandemic. It no longer means just getting out for “leadership walk rounds,” surveys every one or two years, or occasional town halls for the shift that happens to be on duty at midday. It involves not only amassing more information but also simultaneously &lt;em>;showing&lt;/em>; employees that you are doing so.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Today, &lt;em>;authentically &lt;/em>;listening requires a major shift in the frequency, breadth, and depth of listening, which can be accomplished thanks to technology. For example, new tools can empower managers to perform pulse surveys focused on specific issues or specific groups of employees and reveal opportunities to address their specific needs. Virtual focus groups and digital communities can “bring together” employees facing similar challenges and enable both connection and opportunity to collaborate and solve shared challenges.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Crowdsourcing technology allows managers and leaders to involve their front lines in identifying solutions to problems and prioritizing which solutions to start with. By leveraging artificial intelligence (AI) and natural language processing, employee comments can be organized and channeled to reveal both challenges and successes, both of which create opportunities to fix the problems and scale the existing successful solutions. Many leaders still shudder at the idea of surveying employees when they know the feedback will be painful, but authentically listening is a sign of respect.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>; Make engagement and well-being a priority.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;While every organization will have different and unique results from its listening efforts, top-performing organizations all have one thing in common: Senior leaders (often including their boards) have prioritized the importance of employee engagement and well-being. They recognize that an engaged and healthy workforce is critical for them to provide excellent patient care and reduce patient suffering.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;These top performers hold themselves accountable for improving every year and are making the investments to support this improvement. While they rely on their HR leaders heavily, they engage leadership across the organization, including nursing, physician, and quality and safety leaders to collectively address these issues.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>; Focus on three improvement areas.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Next, virtually all top-performing organizations focus on doing these things:&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;Encourage self-care.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Tactics to support individuals should emphasize the importance of self-care — something done poorly in health care. Organizations should share positive feedback from colleagues, leaders, and patients (and the vast majority of patient feedback &lt;em>;is &lt;/em>;positive) to demonstrate organizational gratitude and respect.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Organizations should both invest in peer-support programs so that colleagues can identify suffering in their ranks and design solutions that will help them. And they should continue their evolution from the traditional in-person workplace to one that embraces hybrid or remote work where possible — an evolution that introduces complexity for managers but can enhance resilience for their employees.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;Support leaders and teams.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;After listening, the best organizations take their data and go deeper. They identify teams that are facing more obstacles and leaders who are struggling. They support the managers of these units in developing improvement plans to address specific issues revealed through surveys, focus groups, and other listening approaches.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Developing leaders and building teams is also a critical tactic for maintaining virtuous cycles. This requires investments in coaching and more structured training. Focusing on the skills that leaders require to engender trust and confidence should be taught so that new leaders have the skills to support and build their teams. Ultimately the goal for leaders is to create a psychologically safe environment where those around them feel comfortable speaking up and out and actively contribute to improvement.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;Fix broken systems and processes.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Finally, top-performing organizations demonstrate their commitment to fixing dysfunction in the systems and processes currently in place. They fix broken processes, leverage technology, and build teams so that they can all work smarter. And they know that to solve these problems, they must include the voices of their front lines. They have developed reliable processes for ensuring that those closest to the work are supported in solving the problems. Many organizations have adopted the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nejm.org/doi/full/10.1056/NEJMp1809698&quot;>;approach of GROSS&lt;/a>; (“getting rid of stupid stuff”) and have put processes in place to listen to their front lines and then implement solutions. Others are using new crowdsourcing technology that enables employees to submit innovative solutions to challenges revealed through annual surveying; these organizations then use these submissions to blaze a path forward.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This continuous reevaluation of systems and processes must be built into the organizational frameworks of health care providers. This type of approach is one that many organizations have already taken to build a safety culture and improve quality outcomes for patients. It must now be applied to organizational efforts to improve engagement and resilience in order to retain the remarkable people who continue to work in health care.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Organizational leadership that embraces a coordinated strategy of authentically listening to its employees and patients, developing their leaders, and continuously improving workflows will drive the flywheel of pride and engagement necessary to sustain the virtuous cycle.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 30 May 2023 21:25:05 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[How a &ldquo;Pay-to-Quit&rdquo; Strategy Can Reveal Your Most Motivated Employees]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/05/how-a-pay-to-quit-strategy-can-reveal-your-most-motivated-employees]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/05/May23_27_465417507.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;adventtr/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Companies often have a hard time determining how motivated or committed their employees are, because employees know it goes against their own interests to declare themselves &lt;em>;un&lt;/em>;motivated or &lt;em>;un&lt;/em>;committed. The solution to this problem is for companies to put incentives in place that encourage employees to reveal how they actually feel. In this article, the author, a behavioral economist, describes an incentive plan that has been deployed successfully to this end &amp;#8212; the so-called Pay-to-Quit program, in which companies offer employees a significant sum of money to leave their jobs.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/05/how-a-pay-to-quit-strategy-can-reveal-your-most-motivated-employees?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/05/how-a-pay-to-quit-strategy-can-reveal-your-most-motivated-employees?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Companies often need to reduce the size of their workforce. But how do managers decide which employees to let go and which to keep?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;One often-overlooked parameter in the decision-making process is motivation. The math is simple: All else being equal, the more motivated employees are, the higher their value — which means managers should prioritize keeping highly motivated employees on board. The problem is, employees know that companies value motivation, so they have a strong incentive to&lt;em>; appear&lt;/em>; motivated, even if they&#39;re not. To work against that tendency, managers need to create incentives that will encourage employees to reveal their true levels of motivation.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;The Pay-to-Quit Program&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;One such strategy is to offer employees money to resign voluntarily — the so-called Pay-to-Quit strategy. Zappos, the online shoe and clothing retailer, was the first to employ the strategy, making what has become known as “the offer”: a bonus for new hires to quit following a four-week training period if they didn&#39;t feel that their job was a good fit for them. Zappos started the bonus at $100. When almost no trainee took the offer during training, they raised it all the way up to $4,000, and still almost no one took it — a sign that the company&#39;s workforce was highly motivated.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Amazon, which bought Zappos in 2009, adopted a variation of this strategy. Here&#39;s how Jeff Bezos &lt;a href=&quot;https://slate.com/business/2014/04/amazon-jeff-bezos-shareholder-letter-the-company-pays-workers-up-to-5000-to-quit.html&quot;>;explained it&lt;/a>; in his letter to shareholders in 2014, the first year Amazon put the program into effect:&lt;/p>; &lt;blockquote>; &lt;p>;Pay to Quit is pretty simple. Once a year, we offer to pay our associates to quit. The first year the offer is made, it&#39;s for $2,000. Then it goes up $1,000 a year until it reaches $5,000. The headline on the offer is “Please Don&#39;t Take This Offer.” We hope they don&#39;t take the offer; we want them to stay. Why do we make this offer? The goal is to encourage folks to take a moment and think about what they really want. In the long-run, an employee staying somewhere they don&#39;t want to be isn&#39;t healthy for the employee or the company.&lt;/p>; &lt;/blockquote>; &lt;p>;Amazon made its program available to warehouse workers for years, but at the beginning of 2022, because of a tightening in the labor market, the company &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.businessinsider.com/amazon-suspends-program-pays-warehouse-workers-to-quit-2022-1&quot;>;suspended the program&lt;/a>; for warehouse workers and now only offers it to graduates of its Career Choice upskilling program.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In the work I do as a behavioral economist who advises organizations, I&#39;ve found that the Pay-to-Quit strategy can be remarkably effective. In many organizations, dissatisfied employees have no reason to disclose their true sentiments, but you can incentivize them to do so by offering them money to resign, making it costly for them to be dishonest. One outcome of this strategy is that those who stay are more motivated, of course. But an additional benefit is that those who stay feel the need to justify that decision to themselves — which they typically do by working harder toward longer-term objectives. If they turn the Pay to Quit money down, in effect they invest it in their future with the company. This boosts their productivity and commitment.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Everybody wins with this strategy. It allows managers to identify which employees are genuinely motivated and which are not; it allows unmotivated employees to make an amicable departure with money in hand; and it allows motivated employees to genuinely demonstrate their commitment. And if nobody takes the offer, as recently happened at Trainual, a company that provides automated training and onboarding processes, that&#39;s also a positive outcome: The company ends up learning something important about its new hires and providing them with a motivational boost — at no cost.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2 style=&quot;text-align: left;&quot;>;Testing the Program&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;It&#39;s hard to judge the success of such incentive-based programs without running a controlled study. How can you really know if the right people are quitting, or if those who stay get a moral boost from doing so? To find out, you need to run an experiment that includes a control group that is not offered the incentives, which you can compare to a group that is offered them.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;I&#39;ve recently been working with a large consulting company that is conducting such a test. The model is instructive. The company decided to implement a significant technological change in the way it operated — a change that would require senior employees to invest time in learning new technology and drastically alter their working methods. Some of these employees were enthusiastic about the opportunity, and others were not, but management couldn&#39;t distinguish between them.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Company leaders recognized that they needed to figure that out in one particularly important context — when they were considering which employees to name as partners.为什么？ Because when the company chooses who to promote, it is declaring them highly competent and valuable, which immediately makes them interesting to other companies, who often begin efforts to lure them away. The company wants to avoid a situation in which it trains employees and promote them to partner at the expense of others, only to see those partners take their knowledge and training and go elsewhere. In addition, it&#39;s hard to fire partners even if they don&#39;t do a good job or embrace necessary changes in how work gets done. That&#39;s why the company&amp;nbsp;wanted to figure out which employees were the most motivated &lt;em>;before &lt;/em>;it decided which of them to name as partners. If the company could do that, it could then make its investments in training much more strategically and cost-effectively.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The Pay-to-Quit strategy seemed perfectly suited to this situation. So the company launched an experiment. In some of its many offices around the world, it offered employees an exit bonus if they chose to leave prior to the partnership decision, and it then compared those offices to somewhat similar ones (the control group) where no bonus was offered. To be considered a success, the program would have to lead to retention rates in the offices where the program was offered that were better than that of the control group.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;So far, the program has been a success. In the offices that offered the bonus, close to 12% of the employees chose to take it. Revealingly, those employees were not the worst performers on the team, which suggests the program was doing the job it needed to: identifying capable employees who don&#39;t necessarily feel a strong commitment to the company and might leave after being named partners. The retention rates of new partners in the offices where the bonus was offered has also been higher than the rate in the control group. The program was temporarily put on hold because of Covid-19, but the company now plans to relaunch the program on a larger scale.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;How to Launch a Pay-to-Quit Program&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;If you&#39;re considering adopting a Pay-to-Quit program, make sure you follow these five rules:&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;1. Be transparent&lt;/strong>;.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;When you launch the program, make sure to explain exactly how the program works and why you&#39;ve decided to launch it. Employees will respond better to the program if they understand its purpose.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;2. Offer the right amount.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;The amount you offer should be sufficient to motivate some employees to take it but not so high that lots of them do. That amount will be different at every company, so run a pilot to figure out what works best for you.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;3. Be selective.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Not all employees should be eligible for the offer. Determine which groups or positions are most likely to benefit from it (as the consulting company above did, when it targeted potential partners), and limit the offer to those employees.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;4. Set a deadline.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;The program should not be open-ended. Give employees a relatively short period during which to decide whether to accept the offer, and make it clear that the offer will not be available after that date.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;5. Monitor and evaluate.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;The program will only succeed if you regularly measure its effectiveness and make adjustments as needed. This will only be possible if you first clearly define your long-term goals and then monitor and evaluate success relative to them.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Ultimately, the Pay-to-Quit program is an instructive example of how companies can use the power of incentives to find out more about their employees. Remember, talk is cheap. Simply asking employees about their preferences may not reveal what you need to know —&amp;nbsp; but with a smart inventive plan in place, you can learn a lot.&lt;a href=&quot;#_ftnref1&quot; name=&quot;_ftn1&quot;>;&lt;/a>;&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;br>;&lt;hr>;&lt;div>;获取更多RSS：&lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.net&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.net&lt;/a>; &lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.best&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.best&lt;/a>;&lt;br>;&lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Mon, 29 May 2023 21:25:04 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Research: The Flexibility Options Your On-Site Employees Want]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/05/research-the-flexibility-options-your-on-site-employees-want]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/05/May23_27_1292966666.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Westend61/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Gallup surveyed more than 5,700 US workers in industries such as manufacturing, transportation, health care, education, and service to understand which flexibility options their employers were offering and which flexibility options would entice them to switch jobs. The most commonly offered options (relaxed dress code, flexible start and end times, choice over which days they work per week) were not the ones that employees most valued (increased PTO, four-day workweek, remote or WFH options).&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/05/research-the-flexibility-options-your-on-site-employees-want?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/05/research-the-flexibility-options-your-on-site-employees-want?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;According to a June 2022 Gallup survey, almost half of US workers have jobs that they need to do on-site, in industries such as manufacturing, transportation, health care, education, and service. Many workers in these sectors would love the option to work from home but can&#39;t. Yet they want flexibility and autonomy too.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Gallup recently asked 150 CHROs of large global companies what kinds of flexibility they were considering for their fully on-site employees. They offered 11 options:&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;Work remotely some of the time&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Work at multiple locations&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Four 10-hour-day work weeks&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Three 12-hour-day work weeks&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Flexible start and end times&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Choice over which days they work per week&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Choice over which hours they work per day&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Flextime, or some choice over the hours they work&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Shorter shift lengths&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Increased paid time off (PTO) or vacation time&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Relaxed dress code&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;We then asked more than 5,700 fully onsite US workers if their organization was offering these options. Their most common responses were relaxed dress code (55%), followed by flexible start and end times (33%), and choice over hours they work (flextime) (31%).&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;We also asked employees which of these options they would change jobs to get. The two clear winners were &lt;em>;not&lt;/em>; the ones organizations offered most: increased paid time off or vacation time (57%) and four-day work weeks (44%).&lt;/p>; &lt;div>; &lt;figure>; &lt;img aria-describedby=&quot;caption-attachment-357185&quot; src=&quot;/resources/images/article_assets/2023/05/W230516_HARTER_FLEXIBILITY_360.png&quot; >; &lt;/figure>; &lt;p>;&lt;span>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.hbr.org/data-visuals&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;See more HBR charts in Data &amp;amp; Visuals &lt;i>;&lt;/i>;&lt;/a>;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;While vacations and the four-day workweek were the most popular flexibility options for employees, neither is a panacea. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gallup.com/workplace/285674/improve-employee-engagement-workplace.aspx&quot;>;Employee engagement&lt;/a>; also matters.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Vacations play an important role for organizations. Gallup &lt;a href=&quot;https://news.gallup.com/poll/180335/taking-regular-vacations-may-help-boost-americans.aspx&quot;>;has found&lt;/a>; that people with more vacation time — controlling for other factors, including income — report higher well-being. But &lt;a href=&quot;https://news.gallup.com/opinion/gallup/187868/workplace-health-benefits-aren-enough.aspx&quot;>;Gallup research&lt;/a>; also shows that people with engaging work and one week of vacation report 25% higher well-being than actively disengaged workers who have six or more weeks of vacation.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The &lt;a href=&quot;/2022/05/what-leaders-need-to-know-before-trying-a-4-day-work-week&quot;>;four-day workweek&lt;/a>; has gotten a lot of attention in the past few years. Gallup research has found that among those with fully on-site work responsibilities, those with a four-day workweek reported lower active disengagement and higher overall well-being.&amp;nbsp; This suggests that a four-day workweek may provide advantages to those who do not have options to work remotely. While it doesn&#39;t improve the likelihood that an employee will be engaged in their work or workplace, the four-day workweek does reduce the chance that work will be perceived as miserable, which increases the opportunity for thriving.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Blending Flexibility into On-Site Work&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;How can leaders ultimately decide which flexibility alternatives work best for their organizations&#39; on-site employees? One way is to involve those employees in thinking about which realistic flexibility options might improve their overall lives and their team&#39;s performance.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Perks and benefits may successfully attract new employees, but they don&#39;t guarantee high engagement and productivity. These are mostly inspired by great managers who work closely with employees to set clear goals and priorities, give frequent and meaningful ongoing feedback, focus on employee development, and build a culture of high accountability. Flexibility without strong performance management simply does not work.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Regardless of whether jobs are done on-site or remotely, it&#39;s important that work is individually productive, collaborative, of high value to customers, and improves employees&#39; overall lives. These outcomes are the ultimate measure of whether flexibility options work.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Mon, 29 May 2023 20:25:04 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[AI Can Help You Ask Better Questions &mdash; and Solve Bigger Problems]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/05/ai-can-help-you-ask-better-questions-and-solve-bigger-problems]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/05/May23_26_887787366.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Paul Taylor/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Most companies still view AI rather narrowly, as a tool that alleviates the costs and inefficiencies of repetitive human labor and increasing organizations&amp;#8217; capacity to produce, process, and analyze piles and piles of data. But when paired with &amp;#8220;soft&amp;#8221; inquiry-related skills it can help people ask better questions and be more innovative.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;There are two distinct, yet related, paths to do this. 1) Use the technology to change the cadence and patterns of their questions: AI increases question velocity, question variety, and question novelty. 2) Use AI to transform the conditions and settings where people work so that questions that spark change &amp;#8212; what we call &amp;#8220;catalytic&amp;#8221; questions &amp;#8212; can emerge. This pushes leaders out of their comfort zones and into the position of being intellectually wrong, emotionally uncomfortable, and behaviorally quiet and more reflective, all of which, it turns out, promotes innovative thinking and action.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/05/ai-can-help-you-ask-better-questions-and-solve-bigger-problems?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/05/ai-can-help-you-ask-better-questions-and-solve-bigger-problems?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Just a few years ago, businesses wrestled with artificial intelligence mainly in the abstract — a “future of work” problem they&#39;d have to contend with down the line.现在？ &lt;a href=&quot;https://aiindex.stanford.edu/report/&quot;>;More than half&lt;/a>; the companies around the world are actively adopting AI. Although investments are particularly high in industries such as health care, data management and processing, cloud computing, and fintech, all types of organizations and functions have incorporated AI technology into their operations. And generative AI tools such as ChatGPT are forcing leaders to ask where and how AI can help their businesses.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Even so, most companies still view AI rather narrowly, as a tool that alleviates the costs and inefficiencies of repetitive human labor by automating mundane physical tasks (like moving merchandise in warehouses) and increasing organizations&#39; capacity to produce, process, and analyze piles and piles of data. But the technology can do much more than that.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Paired with “soft” inquiry-related skills such as critical thinking, innovation, active learning, complex problem solving, creativity, originality, and initiative, this technology can further our understanding of an increasingly complex world, allowing us to engage in more abstract questioning and shifting our focus from identification to ideation. In our research and workshops with executives, we&#39;re finding that companies have much to gain by treating AI as a knowledge-work collaborator in diverse areas such as product design, process efficiency, and prompt engineering. Partnering with the technology in this way can help people &lt;a href=&quot;/2018/03/better-brainstorming&quot;>;ask smarter questions&lt;/a>;, which in turn makes them better problem solvers and breakthrough innovators. We are also seeing the initial impacts of more context-aware AI systems (like ChatGPT), and as they continue to improve, the skill of asking questions (or creating prompts) will only become more valuable in the discovery process.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Although experts have recognized the need for software engineers to ask smart questions upstream, when developing automated tools (to bake in fewer biases and assumptions), little has been said about the flipside of the relationship between AI and inquiry: the technology&#39;s potential to help people become more inquisitive, creative problem-solvers on the job. We aimed to correct this oversight through design-thinking sessions and extensive follow-up conversations with tech-driven business leaders from a diverse array of countries and industries. We also surveyed roughly 200 leaders, from more than 30 countries who participated in our executive education programs at MIT —to learn how artificial intelligence has affected questioning patterns and innovation behaviors and outcomes in their organizations. (For this research, we&#39;ve defined “artificial intelligence” broadly to include machine learning, deep learning, robotics, and the recent explosion of generative AI.)&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;We have found two distinct, yet related, paths that leaders follow to strengthen their (and their teams&#39;) inquiry muscles as they tap the power of AI in their question-asking work.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;On the first path, they can use the technology to change the cadence and patterns of their questions: AI increases question velocity, question variety, and question novelty. Results from our ongoing research show that AI can significantly increase all three.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;On the second path, AI can help transform the conditions and settings where people work so that questions that spark change — what we call “catalytic” questions — can emerge. This pushes leaders out of their comfort zones and into the position of being intellectually wrong, emotionally uncomfortable, and behaviorally quiet and more reflective, all of which, it turns out, promotes innovative thinking and action.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Let&#39;s look at how each path can lead to breakthrough ideas.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Increasing velocity, variety, and novelty.&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Partnering with AI to ramp up the velocity, variety, and novelty of questions requires companies to train algorithms to answer the basic, easy (yes/no) questions independently and to reveal deeply buried patterns in the data. When this foundation is laid, humans can start exploring the power of more context-dependent and nuanced questions that AI technologies are not yet capable of answering alone.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Question velocity&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Algorithms can provide immediate answers to questions that leaders pose, in turn allowing them to ask more — and more frequent — questions. In our research, we found that 79% of respondents asked more questions, 18% asked the same amount, and 3% asked fewer.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;At the cybersecurity firm Cybereason, researchers rely on AI and machine learning to immediately answer the basic questions about &lt;em>;what&lt;/em>; happened in an apparent breach so the team can more quickly turn its attention to formulating deeper questions about &lt;em>;why&lt;/em>; it happened. In the past, CEO Lior Div said, findings were more black-and-white: “It&#39;s an attack. It&#39;s not an attack. It&#39;s good or it&#39;s bad.” But the speed with which AI filled in those blanks opened up a whole new line of questions around intent — and what hackers are really after in a given situation.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Of course, there are risks to using AI to generate rapid-fire questions. For one, people may keep asking more and more questions without working their way toward an actionable path, making it important to recognize when the process stops being productive. For another, more questions don&#39;t necessarily amount to &lt;em>;better&lt;/em>; questions, which means you&#39;ll still need to exercise human judgment in deciding how to proceed.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Question variety&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;AI helps uncover patterns and correlations in large volumes of data — connections that humans can easily miss without the technology. Knowing they have this tool at their disposal frees up leaders to ask farther-ranging questions and explore new ideas that they may not have otherwise considered. In our research, we found that engagement with AI led respondents to ask different questions than they otherwise would have 94% of the time.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Consider this example: Kli Pappas, the director of predictive analytics at Colgate-Palmolive, told us that his team tapped AI to understand how charcoal became a wildly popular ingredient in consumer products so they could “find the next charcoal.” Their algorithm generated and answered thousands of questions based on their initial search for data, sketching out a decades-long trajectory from charcoal scrubs in South Korea 20 years ago to charcoal appearing in face washes in the US and then in all kinds of products around the world. The AI-generated data led the team to ask hundreds of less-obvious questions to spark creative thinking about future trends that may be lurking in unexpected places. “We look backwards across categories and try to see how do trends move between categories from hair care, to skincare, to oral care,” Pappas said. “Just doing that puts you a decade or more ahead of the curve.”&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Question novelty&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;AI also facilitates deeper insights by helping users arrive at novel, “category jumping” questions — the gold standard of innovative inquiry — that apply understanding from one area to a completely different space. Our research shows that AI led respondents to ask unique questions that changed the direction of their team, organization, or industry 75% of the time.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;When you know a technology can sift through much more data, and connect more dots, than you could ever do alone, it gives you license to ask wilder questions — things you would never ask if you had to answer them on your own, because they are intractable for the human brain or somehow go against entrenched cognitive biases.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;While category-jumping questions will not arise in every encounter with AI systems, being open to the possibilities and allowing for freedom of inquiry can pave the way for more instances. Here&#39;s how Mir Imran, a medical innovator and founder of InCube Labs, described the upside when we spoke: “AI can take really obscure variables and make novel connections. When these hidden connections come together, it causes you to reframe your question and deliver disruptive innovations.” In other words, AI&#39;s novel connections can spark your novel questions, which in turn can lead you to investigate solutions others haven&#39;t dreamed of yet — like the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.pharmavoice.com/news/oral-biologic-robotic-pill-Rani-Therapeutics/633965/&quot;>;robotic pills&lt;/a>; that Imran&#39;s team recently created to replace external injections with internal ones.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Creating conditions for better questions.&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;AI can take leaders out of their usual mode of operation and force them to cede control over &lt;em>;where&lt;/em>; their questions will take them.这是好事。 Increased question velocity, variety, and especially novelty give facilitate recognizing where you&#39;re intellectually wrong, and becoming emotionally uncomfortable and behaviorally quiet — the very conditions that, we&#39;ve &lt;a href=&quot;/2017/03/bursting-the-ceo-bubble&quot;>;found&lt;/a>;, tend to produce game-changing lines of inquiry. Jeff Wilke — former CEO of Amazon Consumer Worldwide, now a cofounder of Re:Build Manufacturing — has embraced these conditions not only in his day-to-day work as a tech executive but also throughout his career, continually revising his mental models while moving from role to role. When we spoke, he had this to say: “If you seek out things that you don&#39;t know, and you have the courage to be wrong, to be ignorant, to have to ask more questions and maybe be embarrassed socially, then I think you build a more complete model, and that model serves you well over the course of your life.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;But there&#39;s a hitch to teaming up with AI: &lt;a href=&quot;https://news.mit.edu/2021/does-artificial-intelligence-play-well-others-1004&quot;>;Research&lt;/a>; suggests that it can be challenging for people to do so congenially because AI&#39;s superhuman capabilities and unpredictable moves may prevent them from fully trusting and engaging with the technology. That tracks with what we&#39;ve observed in organizations and learned from our conversations with leaders.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Distrust of the technology is hardly conducive to creative inquiry. So, look for ways to offset that, and don&#39;t just leave it to AI to produce the conditions for breakthrough thinking and problem-solving. Consider how else you might create them. Where is there room in your problem-solving processes for synthesizing things that don&#39;t seem related? How might you use those opportunities to throw people off balance so they&#39;ll generate questions that reach &lt;em>;beyond&lt;/em>; what they intellectually know to be right, what makes them emotionally comfortable, and what they are accustomed to saying and doing? At the same time, how can you create &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/02/what-is-psychological-safety&quot;>;psychological safety&lt;/a>; for people in your organization to ask far-ranging questions and to use AI more effectively to learn from them, ultimately leading to asking better questions? When psychological safety is present, people can say, without repercussion, “I am wrong,” “I am uncomfortable,” and “I am still thinking”?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Rather than neatly resolve all those tensions, leaders and teams must &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.jstor.org/stable/44074714&quot;>;learn to sit with the uncertainty that comes from asking questions&lt;/a>; that take them into new territory. While the process isn&#39;t easy, the results are exciting, which is perhaps the most important benefit of collaborating with an AI system. Excitement provides momentum and motivation to push through a tough process, fueling further creativity.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Mitigating AI&#39;s Weaknesses with Human Strengths&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Artificial intelligence may be superhuman in some ways, but it also has considerable weaknesses. For starters, the technology is fundamentally backward-looking, trained on yesterday&#39;s data — and the future might not look anything like the past. What&#39;s more, inaccurate or otherwise flawed training data (for instance, data skewed by inherent biases) produces poor outcomes.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Leaders and their teams must manage such limitations if they are going to treat AI as a creative-thinking partner.如何？ By focusing on areas where the human brain and machines complement one another. Whereas AI increases the volume of data we can process and the degree of complexity we can manage, our brains work in a reductive manner; we generate ideas and then explain them to other people. Whereas machines lack imagination and moral judgment, we can tap those critical skills as AI helps us increase the velocity, variety, and novelty of the questions we&#39;re asking to solve problems in our organizations. Such differences are the stuff of fruitful collaboration — and optimizing them can reduce the threat of AI to human labor.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;With humans and AI working to their respective strengths, they can transform unknown unknowns into known unknowns, opening the door to breakthrough thinking: logical and conceptual leaps that neither could make without the other. Harnessing this potential will require leaders to look at artificial intelligence in a new light — one that is less about cost savings, efficiency, and automation and more about inspiration, imagination, and innovation. It will also require building a culture that supports, incentivizes, and rewards asking big questions — and not necessarily knowing the answers.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;br>;&lt;hr>;&lt;div>;获取更多RSS：&lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.net&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.net&lt;/a>; &lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.best&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.best&lt;/a>;&lt;br>;&lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Fri, 26 May 2023 22:25:04 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[How &mdash; and When &mdash; Should Companies Engage in the Political Process?]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/05/how-and-when-should-companies-engage-in-the-political-process]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/05/May23_26_1440485588.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Anton Vierietin/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;How should companies participate in politics? For all the discussion about the&amp;#160;&lt;em>;social&lt;/em>; responsibilities of the corporation, there&amp;#8217;s been less discussion of how and whether companies should influence government. A new set of principles from the Erb Institute of the University of Michigan suggests some guidelines based around responsibility, legitimacy, accountability, and transparency.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/05/how-and-when-should-companies-engage-in-the-political-process?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/05/how-and-when-should-companies-engage-in-the-political-process?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;What are the political responsibilities of corporations? They are not to be confused with &lt;/span>;&lt;i>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;social&lt;/span>;&lt;/i>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>; responsibilities. Milton Friedman addressed the latter in a &lt;/span>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nytimes.com/1970/09/13/archives/a-friedman-doctrine-the-social-responsibility-of-business-is-to.html&quot;>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;none&quot;>;famous essay&lt;/span>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>; written half a century ago: “In a free society … there is one and only one social responsibility of business — to use its resources and engage in activities designed to increase its profits so long as it stays within the rules of the game, which is to say, engages in open and free competition without deception or fraud.”&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335559739&amp;quot;:160,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:259}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;But what about &lt;/span>;&lt;i>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;political &lt;/span>;&lt;/i>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;responsibility? What obligations do firms have when it comes to participating in the political process? The same essay gives some clues to Friedman&#39;s thinking. First, he made it clear that corporate leaders are &lt;/span>;&lt;i>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;not &lt;/span>;&lt;/i>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;to act as “legislator, executive and jurist” by using corporate resources “to restrain inflation, improve the environment, fight poverty and so on.” He noted that we have “elaborate constitutional, parliamentary and judicial provisions” to control those functions.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335559739&amp;quot;:160,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:259}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;Second, Friedman made it clear that businesses, in their pursuit of profits are to “stay within the rules of the game.” Presumably, he had in mind not just rules regarding “deception or fraud,” but more broadly, those that call for respecting property rights, honoring contracts, and avoiding negligent behavior toward employees and customers.&lt;/span>;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335559739&amp;quot;:160,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:259}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;So far, so good. But this leaves one crucial question unanswered: Who makes the rules? Or more specifically, who decides how broad rules like property rights and open competition apply to specific cases, such as environmental protection or railroad safety or whatever is the issue of the day? Although Friedman did not quite come out and say it, he implied a division of labor in which it is up to government to make the rules while corporations go about the business of making profits within the rules as they find them. &lt;/span>;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335559739&amp;quot;:160,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:259}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;That is not how things work, however, today or perhaps ever. Instead, we find corporations up to their elbows in the rulemaking process at every level. They contribute to the campaigns of elected officials, lobby regulatory agencies, and do what they can to influence the selection of judges. The result is a system in which the businesses themselves are often the ones who make the rules in the first place. When businesses write the rules, bad things happen. Companies can manipulate regulations to hinder their competitors. They can grant themselves tax breaks or boost their profits at the expense of public safety and the environment. Economists use terms like “rent seeking” or “state capture” but whatever we call them, these corporate behaviors erode faith in government and the democratic process.&lt;/span>;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335559739&amp;quot;:160,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:259}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;It would be simplistic to call for a return to a strict division of labor in which corporations mind their own business and leave the rules to government. For one thing, there has never been such an arrangement to which we could return. What is more, the right to petition the government for a redress of grievances is written in black and white into the Constitution, and that right extends to citizens in their roles as entrepreneurs and corporate leaders. What we need is something more subtle than a division of labor. We need a set of principles to guide and evaluate the participation of businesses in politics.&lt;/span>;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335559739&amp;quot;:160,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:259}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;Recently, the Erb Institute of the University of Michigan has released just such a set of &lt;/span>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://erb.umich.edu/partner-with-erb/erb-principles/&quot;>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;none&quot;>;Principles for Corporate Political Responsibility&lt;/span>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>; (CPR). They are not the first attempt to do so, but they are arguably more comprehensive than anything to date. Although they are not a silver bullet, the principles have the potential to make a substantive contribution, both by clarifying the meaning of political responsibility and by providing a benchmark for determining who is acting responsibly and who is not.&lt;/span>;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335559739&amp;quot;:160,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:259}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;The Erb CPR principles do not take sides in the debate over &lt;/span>;&lt;i>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;social &lt;/span>;&lt;/i>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;responsibility. They are designed to appeal equally to the staunchest Friedmanite and the most progressive advocate of corporate ESG. What they do is lay out some broad guidelines for the political activities of corporations, regardless of their views on shareholder vs. stakeholder primacy.&lt;/span>;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335559739&amp;quot;:160,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:259}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;The Erb CPR principles have three components.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335559739&amp;quot;:160,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:259}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;The first is a broad definition of political activities. Their definition goes well beyond political spending from corporate treasuries to encompass lobbying, participation in drafting laws and regulations, support of nonprofits, and participation public discourse of all kinds.&lt;/span>;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335559739&amp;quot;:160,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:259}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;Second, the CPR specifies four standards for evaluating political actions. The core standard is &lt;/span>;&lt;i>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;responsibility&lt;/span>;&lt;/i>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;, defined as conformity with healthy market rules of the game. That means companies have a responsibility to compete based on the price and quality of their own products, rather than by tweaking laws and regulations in ways that disadvantage competitors. And their political participation must not subvert that responsibility to healthy competition. They are also expected to respect established science, a duty that is especially salient when it comes to issues such as climate change and limiting exposure to hazardous chemicals.&lt;/span>;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335559739&amp;quot;:160,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:259}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;As part of their overall commitment to political responsibility, corporations that sign on to the Erb principles are expected to commit to three more specific standards.&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;i>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;Legitimacy &lt;/span>;&lt;/i>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;means that political activities reflect the company&#39;s views, not those of the individual managers or officers; that they comply with relevant laws; and that they do not pressure employees, shareholders, or other stakeholders to take positions they would not voluntarily endorse. &lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;Next comes &lt;/span>;&lt;i>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;accountability&lt;/span>;&lt;/i>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;, which means the alignment of political activities, including those undertaken through trade associations and other third parties, with the firm&#39;s own stated commitments, purposes, and values. A company should not say one thing and quietly support another. &lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;The final standard is &lt;/span>;&lt;i>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;transparency, &lt;/span>;&lt;/i>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;which means open and honest communication about corporate political activities, including the provision of good-faith information and expertise to all levels of government as needed to support effective policymaking.&lt;/span>;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335559739&amp;quot;:160,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:259}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;The Erb principles do not, of course, have the force of law. They do, however, include provisions to ensure that they are treated as more than an empty declaration that can be signed and forgotten. For that reason, Erb requires corporations that join in supporting its principles to formally adopt one of the following three policies: the &lt;/span>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.politicalaccountability.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/CPA-Zicklin-Model-Code-of-Conduct-for-Corporate-Political-Spending.pdf&quot;>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;none&quot;>;CPA-Zicklin Model Code of Conduct for Corporate Political Spending&lt;/span>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;, the &lt;/span>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.globalreporting.org/standards/media/1030/gri-415-public-policy-2016.pdf&quot;>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;none&quot;>;Global Responsibility Initiative&#39;s Standard 415 on public policy&lt;/span>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;, or a publicly stated policy prohibiting the use of corporate treasury funds for election-related spending. Each of these requires the company to undertake specific, observable measures in support of CPR.&lt;/span>;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335559739&amp;quot;:160,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:259}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;Taken together, the declaration of principles and the specific governance measures that support them offer a set of objective standards against which to judge corporate political activities. Suppose, for example, that a fossil fuel company contributes to the campaigns of state lawmakers who promise to make it harder for competing clean energy suppliers to build transmission lines, or that a transportation company lobbies for lax safety standards that will protect it against lawsuits for negligence, or that a fast-food chain participates in regulatory rulemaking that will make it easier to block workers from moving to new jobs with competitors. These are not imaginary cases. Can they pass evaluation by the standards of responsibility, legitimacy, accountability, and transparency? If not, the companies in question can at least be called out for violating the rules of the game, not only in public, but also by their own shareholders.&lt;/span>;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335559739&amp;quot;:160,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:259}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;The balance between free-market capitalism and constitutional democracy is always a delicate one. The CPR principles can help harmonize the two and they allow for a much clearer dialog about companies&#39; participation in the democratic process. When corporations behave irresponsibly, illegitimately, unaccountably, and opaquely, then capitalism and constitutional democracy are effectively at war. Without a truce, there will be mutually assured destruction.&lt;/span>;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335559739&amp;quot;:160,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:259}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Fri, 26 May 2023 21:25:03 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[6 Pitching Techniques to Use When Budgets Are Tight]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/05/6-pitching-techniques-to-use-when-budgets-are-tight]]><description>&lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/05/May23_26_1408214577.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;SvetaZi/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400&quot;>;Persuasion is not a speech, it&amp;#8217;sa process &amp;#8212; a process of learning about your audience, earning their trust, and building a case that takes into account their interests. In this article, the author outlines six steps you can take to try to persuade a client or senior executive to spend money when budgets are tight: 1) &lt;/span>;Start with stakeholder analysis. 2) Get crystal clear about the benefits of your offering. 3) Connect with a sense of timeliness or urgency. 4) Look for social proof. 5) Anticipate their objections. 6)&amp;#160;Provide a clear next step.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/05/6-pitching-techniques-to-use-when-budgets-are-tight?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/05/6-pitching-techniques-to-use-when-budgets-are-tight?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;How can you persuade a client or senior executive to spend money when budgets are tight?&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Perhaps you are an audit director persuading a business head to take a costly step to avoid the wrath of regulators; an HR executive lobbying your internal client to invest in training while they are going through layoffs; or an engineer trying to convince your VP to prioritize your project over others.&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;No matter your title or job function, each of us is in a sales role. As Daniel Pink describes in &lt;em>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.danpink.com/books/to-sell-is-human/&quot;>;To Sell Is Human&lt;/a>;,&lt;/em>; at some point we will need to sell our ideas, projects, or recommendations to others.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Each of us can develop the ability to influence, often without having formal authority. It requires a delicate balance of &lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;&lt;a href=&quot;/2022/03/to-win-over-an-audience-focus-on-building-trust&quot;>;relationship-building&lt;/a>;, &lt;a href=&quot;/2014/06/how-to-negotiate-with-someone-more-powerful-than-you&quot;>;negotiating&lt;/a>;, &lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;and &lt;/span>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.globalpublicspeaking.com/the-three-modes-of-persuasion-in-person-or-virtual/&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;persuasive communication&lt;/span>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>; skills. &lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Over the past 20 years of teaching these topics, here is what I&#39;ve found to be most effective.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;1. Start with stakeholder analysis.&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;In the &lt;/span>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://store.hbr.org/product/hbr-guide-to-persuasive-presentations/11150&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;&lt;em>;HBR Guide to Persuasive Presentations&lt;/em>;&lt;/span>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;, Ken Haemer says, “Designing a presentation without an audience in mind is like writing a love letter and addressing it &#39;to whom it may concern.&#39;”&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Start by talking to the people you seek to influence before making your case. Ask questions to understand what&#39;s going on in their organization, what challenges they&#39;re facing in their industry, and what their individual goals are for their role. Asking someone to spend money can be tough, and they might be worried about their own jobs; try to understand what they&#39;re going through before you ask them to take action.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;2. Get crystal clear about the benefits of your offering&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;. &lt;/span>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;While it may be obvious to us why an organization should take a particular action, it&#39;s not always clear to the decision-makers. After your stakeholder analysis, crystallize what you have learned about the audience you need to convince.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;What are the benefits to them or the organization if they make this investment? For instance, if your service will save a client money, be prepared to show how much they can expect to save. If it will reduce turnover, quantify by how much. Demonstrating a cost-reducing impact is critically important when budgets are lean. The arguments have to be persuasive to your client and those they report to, not just to you.&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;b>;3. Connect with a sense of timeliness or urgency. &lt;/b>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;When we teach persuasion, we teach people to answer the question, “W&lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;hy now?”&lt;/span>; &lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;when convincing others to take action. The &lt;/span>;&lt;a href=&quot;/2001/10/harnessing-the-science-of-persuasion&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;scarcity principle of influence&lt;/span>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>; by Robert Cialdini suggests using loss language to demonstrate why it&#39;s important to take immediate action. What costs will your audience incur by failing to take action?&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;For example, if you&#39;re convincing a client to buy your product or service, how is their indecision costing them money? How can you demonstrate to them that they can&#39;t afford &lt;/span>;&lt;i>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;not&lt;/span>;&lt;/i>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>; to take advantage of your service? This &lt;/span>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=e0R9HRunZfs&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;demo video&lt;/span>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>; created by professional speaker Traci Brown makes a compelling case for why companies should hire her.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;b>;4. Look for social proof&lt;/b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;. &lt;/span>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;We are influenced by others who are in similar situations. What other organizations are already taking action, and how can you demonstrate that your product or recommended project is benefiting them?&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;For instance, if you&#39;d like to make the case for training amidst layoffs, and one of your main competitors is investing in training, you could explain that your competitor is going to retain more of their top talent through this offering as opposed to going into complete austerity measures. You could suggest &lt;/span>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://trainingmag.com/from-free-fall-to-a-smoother-flight-why-leadership-training-before-layoffs-matters/&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;training&lt;/span>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>; to bring teams together and foster a sense of trust and connection, even amidst the uncertainty of layoffs.&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;b>;5. Anticipate their objections. &lt;/b>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;One of my favorite persuasive tools is the “I know what you&#39;re thinking” strategy. Use your knowledge of your client or industry to relate to what may be holding them back.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;You could use the “Feel, felt, found” technique to say something like, “I can imagine it must be tough to get approval for a program like this. We&#39;ve seen other organizations struggle with this as well, and we&#39;ve found that by framing the program through the lens of retention and succession planning, they were able to get approval.” When you demonstrate that you can understand what&#39;s on their mind, you will build trust.&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;b>;6. Provide a clear next step.&lt;/b>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;So often, the hardest part of the persuasive process is making the ask. When we teach persuasive presentations, we recommend a clear call to action that outlines next steps. How can you anticipate the client&#39;s next steps and provide a clear path that removes potential barriers?&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Say something like, “When we decide to move forward, our next steps will be the following.” This helps the decision-maker see themselves in the process and makes it easier to say yes.&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Putting It All Together&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;For an example of these six steps in action, I turned to my colleague &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/in/orit-rozenblum/&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Orit Rozenblum&lt;/span>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;, an experienced sales executive.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Orit practices consultative selling, when a sales professional acts more like an adviser than a salesperson: instead of pushing a specific product, they will first seek to understand their potential customers&#39; pain points before recommending a variety of solutions based on their customers&#39; needs.&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;In her previous role, Orit worked for a company that sold an innovative technology solution to sales professionals. She told me about a new client she was targeting within an SAP 100 technology company that was already a customer. Rather than the normal offering her company had provided, Orit wanted to suggest a more complex and expensive solution. The new client was having a hard time getting approval for it — it was a big expense and their sales numbers weren&#39;t looking great.&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Let&#39;s look at how Orit applied the steps we suggest above:&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;b>;Stakeholder analysis: &lt;/b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Orit started the conversation by putting aside budgets and focusing on value, in an effort to understand the client&#39;s underlying pain point. When she explained it to me, Orit said, &lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;“You can&#39;t just call a customer and say, &#39;Tell me about your pain.&#39; It takes a few calls, conversations, to get deeper and deeper in the consultative selling process.”&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;b>;Crystal-clear benefits: &lt;/b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;With that information, Orit prepared for a new conversation that addressed her client&#39;s pain point and how her company&#39;s solution could help solve it. This made it easier for&lt;/span>; &lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;her client to talk to &lt;/span>;their&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>; manager.&lt;/span>;&lt;i>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/i>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;b>;Urgency: &lt;/b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;The client&#39;s biggest customer event of the year was coming up, and the company wanted to make a powerful impression. Orit positioned her solution to show the client&#39;s customers the value&lt;/span>; they&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>; provided in the industry.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;b>;Social proof&lt;/b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;: Orit included information on how her solution was helping other sales organizations: identifying what their problem was, what value her company provided, and the ultimate outcome.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;b>;Clear next steps:&lt;/b>; &lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Orit put together a plan for the entire team, including for her client and his manager who had control of the budget. She also &lt;/span>;anticipated their objections &lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;by including how they could work with different departments on implementation, so that when they were ready, they knew exactly how to proceed.&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;So what was the outcome?&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Orit said&lt;/span>;&lt;i>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;, &lt;/span>;&lt;/i>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;“It didn&#39;t happen overnight —&amp;nbsp;it took three months — but the client succeeded in getting the money. Two months into the project, the client said to me, &#39;Orit, it was hard to get the money as an expense. But because we used your software in the quarter and saw the ROI and the value, we don&#39;t see it as an expense anymore, we see it as an investment. Our sales people are using it and it&#39;s working. We get more warm leads, and it shortens the sales cycle because our customers are already engaged and come prepared with questions.&#39;”&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Orit&#39;s final words during our conversation were, &lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;“If you can solve a real problem for someone, even when budgets are tight, they will find the budget for it.”&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Persuasion is not a speech, it&#39;s a process — a process of learning about your audience, earning their trust, and building a case that takes into account their interests. These skills are important in any situation, and essential in times of limited resources.&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Fri, 26 May 2023 20:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Building an Effective Cybersecurity Training Program]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/05/building-an-effective-cybersecurity-training-program]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/05/May23_25_1340731085.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Anton Vierietin/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Just as sports teams practice and train for upcoming games, your organization should be constantly and consistently practicing and training for cybersecurity events, building the muscles and skills they&amp;#8217;ll need to respond when a cyber-attack inevitably happens. Planning and scheduling training and exercise is crucial because it allows teams to assess their performance and readiness. Team exercises should be done regularly and with the same tools, techniques, and procedures used in daily operations, and simulations should reflect real-world scenarios that teammates are likely to encounter in their daily work. This helps to build confidence in responding to specific threats and ensures that individuals are prepared to act accordingly. After each exercise, it&amp;#8217;s important to provide feedback and discuss what worked well and what could be improved. Helping teammates learn from their mistakes and improve their responses is one of the most valuable takeaways from any training event.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/05/building-an-effective-cybersecurity-training-program?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/05/building-an-effective-cybersecurity-training-program?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;In the movie &lt;em>;Any Given Sunday&lt;/em>;, Al Pacino gives &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=f1yWSePMqsk&quot;>;a memorable speech&lt;/a>; to his losing football team. The speech highlights a critical lesson for teams: Trust in themselves and their teammates is critical for success. Just as elite sports teams depend on trust among players to perform at their best, cybersecurity relies on trust in computers, people, and organizations. We trust computers to perform reliably and consistently, just as we trust our teammates to excel in their organizational roles. As with sports, building trust within a cybersecurity team is essential for success. By emphasizing reliable and repeatable behavior, individuals and teams can develop the confidence needed to perform effectively in any situation they encounter.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Our expertise at the CERT Division of Carnegie Mellon&#39;s Software Engineering Institute is in &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sei.cmu.edu/our-work/cyber-workforce-development/index.cfm&quot;>;Cyber Workforce Development&lt;/a>;. Our work helps organizations acquire the skills they need as a team to combat cyber threats. In many ways, business leaders function as coaches, helping employees develop crucial skills to make the organization successful. Just as sports teams must train and practice to build trust and cohesion, businesses must do so to ensure high productivity in an evolving workplace. We believe that individual training and team exercises can help create a clear business advantage. Through repetitive drills and practice, individual players can become subject matter experts on particular tools or techniques, while teams can collectively respond in the best possible manner to any scenario they&#39;re likely to confront. Your organization should be constantly and consistently practicing and training for cybersecurity events, building the muscles and skills they&#39;ll need to respond when an attack inevitably occurs.&lt;/p>; &lt;article-promo>; &lt;hbr-component type=&quot;promo&quot; is-insight=&quot;insight-center&quot; title=&quot;Managing Cyber Risk&quot; dek=&quot;Exploring the challenges and the solutions.&quot; cta-text=&quot;&quot; href=&quot;/insight-center/managing-cyber-risk&quot;>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/insight-center/managing-cyber-risk&quot; style=&quot;color:black;text-decoration:none&quot;>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; Insight Center Collection &lt;/div>; &lt;h3>;Managing Cyber Risk&lt;/h3>; &lt;div>; Exploring the challenges and the solutions. &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hbr-component>; &lt;/article-promo>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Identify Key Cybersecurity Skills for Your Organization&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Just as coaches defines the style of play for their teams, developing an effective cybersecurity training program requires identifying the specific skills and knowledge needed to confront cyber threats in a way that aligns with the organization&#39;s goals and objectives. There are several ways to do so.&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;Conduct a skills-gap analysis by comparing your workforce&#39;s skills to those needed to confront cyber threats. The National Institute of Standards and Technology&#39;s (NIST&#39;s) &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nist.gov/itl/applied-cybersecurity/nice/nice-framework-resource-center&quot;>;NICE Cybersecurity Workforce Framework&lt;/a>; is a helpful resource for identifying the skills and knowledge needed for an effective cybersecurity team. Reviewing your security policies, procedures, and protocols is another good starting point.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Review industry standards with organizations such as &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nist.gov/cyberframework&quot;>;NIST&lt;/a>; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cisa.gov/topics/cybersecurity-best-practices&quot;>;CISA&lt;/a>; to ensure that your organization is aligned with the best practices in your industry, and incorporate those practices into your cybersecurity training program. For example, there are special controls for organizations handling certain kinds of data, such as health care data and personal identifiable information, so certain industries need to adhere to regulations such as &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.dol.gov/general/ppii&quot;>;Personal Identifiable Information (PII)&lt;/a>; or the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.hhs.gov/hipaa/for-professionals/index.html&quot;>;Health Insurance Portability and Accountability Act (HIPPA)&lt;/a>;.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Engage with departments and leaders within your organization to understand their specific cybersecurity concerns and challenges. For example, a global sales force must consider its use of data in light of legislation such as the EU&#39;s &lt;a href=&quot;https://gdpr.eu/what-is-gdpr/&quot;>;General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)&lt;/a>; and the &lt;a href=&quot;https://oag.ca.gov/privacy/ccpa&quot;>;California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA).&lt;/a>; Speaking to each department leader will provide insight into the specific training needs at all organizational levels.&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Develop a Performance Improvement Plan to Meet Your Strategy&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Once you have identified the skills and knowledge needed to combat cyber threats, the next step is to develop a comprehensive training and exercise program to improve them. Here are steps that can be taken to develop an effective program:&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;Design simulations to cover a range of scenarios, including phishing, ransomware, and social-engineering attacks.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Like blocking and tackling practice in football, begin with simple scenarios that focus on core concepts, and gradually increase the complexity of the scenarios. Focus on building skills and confidence before tackling more-difficult threats.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Focus simulations on real-world scenarios that teammates are likely to encounter in their daily work. This helps to build confidence about responding to specific threats and ensures that individuals are prepared to act accordingly.&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;After each exercise, provide feedback and discuss what worked well and what could be improved. Helping teammates learn from their mistakes and improve their responses is one of the most valuable takeaways from any training event.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Execute an Ongoing Campaign of Effective Training and Exercises&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Great athletes train regularly. Businesses must likewise prioritize ongoing skills development to remain competitive as &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/05/the-digital-world-is-changing-rapidly-your-cybersecurity-needs-to-keep-up&quot;>;technologies and cyber threats change rapidly&lt;/a>;. Here are some key considerations.&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;Training and exercise budgets should not be sacrificed in cost-cutting measures. Investing in employee development delivers enormous value, and no company can afford to underestimate &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/05/the-devastating-business-impacts-of-a-cyber-breach&quot;>;the long-term financial costs of a cyber breach&lt;/a>;.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Planning and scheduling training and exercises is crucial; it allows teams to assess their performance. By regularly identifying areas for improvement, teams can plan and execute more effectively in the future. Additionally, taking the time to review and evaluate past performance can lead to more-informed decisions about which scenarios to exercise and which tools to use in future training sessions.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Team exercises should be done regularly and with the same tools, techniques, and procedures used in daily operations to build useful muscle memory in real-world situations.&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;In his speech, Pacino says, “You find out life&#39;s this game of inches; so is football.” So is cybersecurity. Every inch of progress counts. Today&#39;s threats are more sophisticated and widespread than previous ones, and it&#39;s not a question of &lt;em>;if&lt;/em>; an organization will face a cyber-attack but &lt;em>;when&lt;/em>;. That&#39;s why it&#39;s crucial for business leaders to prioritize cybersecurity training and exercise as a key component of their overall security stance. By identifying the specific skills and knowledge needed to effectively combat threats, planning and scheduling training and exercises, and engaging with key stakeholders to understand the specific training needs of their organization, businesses can build a stronger, more confident team. Investing in employee development through formal training programs and ongoing exercises can deliver enormous value and help businesses stay ahead of adversaries in the ever-changing cybersecurity landscape.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 25 May 2023 22:25:03 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>