<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>哈佛商业评论</title><description>哈佛商业评论全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link/> https://hbr.org/ <item><title><![CDATA[3 Strategies to Boost Sales and Marketing Productivity]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/3-strategies-to-boost-sales-and-marketing-productivity]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄形象>; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_05_2974330.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Yaroslav Danylchenko/Stocksy&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span >;总结。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;一项针对 B2B 公司的研究发现，只有十分之一的公司能够持续以高于销售和营销费用的速度增长销售额。随着公司寻求在不确定的经济中削减成本，提高商业生产力是一项明智的战略。研究表明，公司可以通过三种方式做到这一点：改进进入市场的模式，将每个代表转变为 A 参与者，并提高销售和营销支持的效率。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt; div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/3-strategies-to-boost-sales-and-marketing-productivity?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/3-strategies-to-boost-sales-and-marketing-productivity?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;差不多了不言而喻的是，收入的增长需要以同样的速度增加销售和营销成本。大多数销售和营销负责人骨子里都相信，他们的团队不可能在很长一段时间内提高生产力。团队可以找到削减成本和提高效率的方法，是的，但不是全面的、持续的生产力提高。这是一种破坏性的、自我强化的信念——我们的研究表明它不一定是真的。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我们关注的指标是所谓的“商业生产力”，它衡量收入（或毛利润）每美元商业成本返回，然后评估收入增长相对于销售和营销费用增长的速度。我们想更好地了解管理者是否相信随着时间的推移很难推动商业生产力的持续提高，因此我们进行了一项研究。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我们分析了 10 个国家的 1,254 家上市企业对企业公司2017 年至 2021 年全球行业。我们发现，在所有行业中，平均每家公司在任何一年的商业生产力都持平，收入增长与销售和营销费用的增长速度相同。大约 19% 的公司在任何给定年份将商业生产力提高了 10% 以上，但大多数最终都将其收回。只有 5% 的公司能够在四年中的三年内实现商业生产力的提高。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这些精英公司（持续的生产力领导者）获得了另一个巨大的收益。他们实现了比同行高得多的年度股东总回报 (TSR)，平均相差 12%。 TSR 优势从物流和运输领域的 21% 到纸张和包装领域的 4% 不等。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我们的研究确定了试图提高商业生产力的常见方法，这些方法注定要失败，或者充其量只能表现平庸.一种方法包括仅关注成本，这会阻碍长期增长。在其他情况下，公司严重依赖最新的销售或营销软件或未经证实的人工智能工具，然后看到成本增长而收入增长却没有相应增长。其他人可能会将不合理的生产力提升纳入他们的计划，而没有切实可行的途径来实现这些目标，这可能导致销售代表无法实现目标并退出。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;生产力领导者的不同做法&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;我们的研究表明发现商业生产力领导者多年来系统地追求三个领域的杠杆。他们改进了进入市场的模型。他们提高了一线的生产率，试图让每个代表都成为 A 级员工。他们还确定了销售和营销支持的效率。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;改进进入市场模型。&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;这需要评估如何针对可能带来的机会部署销售和营销能力产生最高的回报。太多的公司依靠回顾性销售数据和过时的覆盖模型来确定他们需要多少代表以及将他们分配到哪里。这些覆盖模型往往会生锈，从而降低销售和营销组织的投资回报。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;根据客户的预期未来支出重新平衡帐户分配，为客户创建最合适的区域，要有效得多每个卖家。领先的公司调整他们的客户细分并将客户重新分配到更有利可图的市场途径，使用成本更低的覆盖范围，例如内部销售、离岸角色和适当的电子商务。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;将每个代表变成 A &lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;为了提高一线代表的工作效率，公司可以采用多种策略。一个是创建以数据为依据的销售策略——一组与目标客户协调的销售和营销活动，包括量身定制的销售抵押品和跟踪，以确保代表专注于最高价值的机会。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;持续的培训和指导也帮助缩短新秀的上手时间并提高老将的表现。贝恩研究发现，与表现不佳的代表相比，表现最好的代表与其经理的互动更频繁、质量更高，例如每周一对一的会议和定期的管道审查。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;进行销售和营销&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;运行精益支持团队可以节省大量资金或释放运营费用，用于面向客户的销售活动。优化支持支出需要找到合适的数字和自动化工具来简化复杂的流程。此外，其他策略包括提高个人代表配额的准确性（由支持团队设置）、减少组织中的跨度和层级，以及审查非销售和非配额角色。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;生产力领导者系统地执行这些类别中的每一个策略。想一想一家计算机应用程序安全提供商在年收入增长从大约 40% 放缓至不到 20% 后如何改进其覆盖范围。公司扩大了客户群的数量，并为每个细分市场创建了更多量身定制的销售活动。它根据总目标市场、每个客户的购买倾向和客户特征重建了销售区域。这些举措和其他举措使这家安全提供商在连续四年中的三年内实现了超过 10% 的商业生产力提升。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;其他公司也开始了类似的旅程，以释放商业生产力。一家跨国食品包装公司已开始通过多种策略改变其进入市场的模式。它们包括根据机会和服务需求重新细分客户，更多地使用内部销售和电子商务等低成本的市场途径，以及在全球范围内汇集专家资源。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;设计和重复&lt;/h2 >; &lt;p>;除了不断重新审视一套经过验证的杠杆之外，真正让生产力领导者与众不同的是他们采用深思熟虑且可重复的方法来执行变革。他们的方法有几个组织层面。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;首先，他们指定了一个明确的商业生产力负责人，通常是一个专门的角色。这位高管通常直接向首席收入、财务或运营官报告，并拥有专门的计划资源。员工帮助建立积压的策略来执行，推动每个策略的进展，并协助改变销售和营销各个级别的流程和行为。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;经验丰富的生产力领导者还将商业生产力目标与年度和多年规划，使工作范围扩大到销售团队之外。为此，CRO、CFO 和 COO 必须定期就明确的生产力问题进行沟通。 CFO 的收入和销售/营销成本目标应反映销售和营销组织的预期生产力收益，并有一套明确的策略来实现这些收益。多年的商业生产力路线图必须与 IT 路线图相吻合，这样公司才能规划所需的技术投资。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;最后，成熟的商业运营团队对于建模销售和营销能力、与财务沟通至关重要组，并创建不断修订的上市蓝图。运营团队确保策略在不同的地区和业务线中始终如一地发挥作用。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;在经济低迷时期提出正确的问题&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;CRO、CFO 和 COO 致力于保持他们的生产力收益将想要解决一系列高收益问题：&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;我们的组织是否知道推动商业生产力的因素以及我们是否达到、高于或低于我们的目标？&lt;/li>; &lt;li >;到明年、三年、五年后，我们需要在哪些方面提高生产率以及提高到什么水平？&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;将结合哪些策略来制定实现目标的现实路径？&lt;/li >; &lt;li>;我们是否拥有正确的结构、运营模式和高层领导的参与来实现这些收益？&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;谁负责实现这些收益？他或她是否与财务、人力资源和其他职能部门的领导者建立了正确的报告和沟通机制？&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;保持商业生产力的提高会给任何行业和任何阶段的公司带来好处经济周期。但这在当前的宏观经济条件下尤为重要，因为经济低迷会重新安排董事会。贝恩分析发现，在 2008-09 年的经济衰退期间，全球近 3,900 家公司的业绩差异很大。在随后的扩张中，赢家远离输家，并扩大了利润和市值差距。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;今天同样适用。商业生产力框架迫使公司在收入和成本节约行动之间做出健康的权衡，这些权衡将帮助他们在未来几年加速超越竞争对手。&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt; /div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Mon, 05 Jun 2023 21:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[How Brands Can Sell to Environmentally Conscious Nonconsumers]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/how-brands-can-sell-to-environmentally-conscious-nonconsumers]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄形象>; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_05_2417355.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Yevgeniia Vradii/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;更多&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt; span>;总结。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;关于消费者对气候变化的态度如何影响他们的行为和购买习惯的新研究发现，最大的部分是“有意识的非消费者” 8221； &amp;#8212;也就是说，人们改变了他们的行为以保护环境，但并未购买环保产品。对于销售这些产品的公司来说，接触这部分消费者可以成为利润和影响力的来源。该研究发现了阻碍这一群体进行可持续采购的具体障碍——以及帮助克服这些障碍的相应策略。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/how-brands-can- sell-to-environmentally-conscious-nonconsumers?language=es&quot;>;阅读西班牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/how-brands-can-sell-to-environmentally-conscious-nonconsumers ?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;在气候变化日益明显的世界中，我们都会遇到正在改变行为以帮助保护环境的人：骑自行车上班的人为了避免消耗燃料，携带自己的餐具以避免使用一次性塑料叉子，或者挂在他们的可回收垃圾上，绕过垃圾桶，直到他们找到合适的地方来回收它。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这些人有两件事共同点：一方面，他们对环境的关注足以改变他们的日常习惯。另一方面，从表面上看，这种行为改变并不包括购买贴有环保标签的产品。因为他们目前的可持续生活之路侧重于减少消耗（燃料、塑料、家庭能源等），所以他们没有将可持续性与他们需要购买的产品联系起来。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我们称这个群体为&amp;nbsp; “有意识的非消费者”，根据贝恩最近的研究，他们现在约占美国所有消费者的 32%。对于寻求新的增长来源的大品牌来说，它们已成为某种圣杯。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;毫无疑问，消费者越来越关注环境问题，即使只是因为他们在家里打人。最近的 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.pewresearch.org/short-reads/2022/08/12/most-americans-who-have-faced-extreme-weather-see-a-link-to-climate -change-republicans-included/&quot;>;皮尤研究中心民意调查&lt;/a>;发现，71% 的美国人在过去一年中在他们的社区经历过极端天气事件。贝恩消费者实验室在 2022 年对近 4,000 名美国消费者进行的研究显示，直面气候变化已导致 52% 的美国人表示他们“极度或非常关注”气候变化的影响2023 年对 1,000 名消费者进行的后续调查。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;人们对环境问题的日益关注为“有意识的非消费者”的潜在 3650 亿美元市场铺平了道路（在“有意识的消费者”的 2780 亿美元市场之上”），根据贝恩研究，如果公司消除阻碍购买的障碍。这是一个涵盖从减少包装的产品到需要更少水的洗发水的一切事物的市场。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;然而，充分抓住这个机会对消费品公司来说将是一个挑战，因为消费者日益增长的担忧并没有统一反映在他们的产品中。购买行为。不可否认，消费者所说的他们想要的和他们实际放入篮子里的东西之间存在着不可否认的“说做”差距。然而，缩小这一差距的回报是巨大的。当消费者尝试并喜欢可持续产品时，他们更有可能成为直言不讳的拥护者。例如，根据我们的研究，推荐环境、社会和治理 (ESG) 产品的人中有 44% 是超级推荐者，这意味着他们会向 10 人以上推荐产品，而出于任何其他原因推荐的人中这一比例仅为 22% .&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;为了了解消费品公司和零售商的前景和最大机遇，贝恩最近对美国消费者进行的调查考察了诸如他们对气候变化的担忧以及出于可持续性原因改变生活方式的数量等因素。我们的研究使我们能够确定五个定义明确的细分市场，所有这些细分市场都跨越年龄和收入水平：&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;气候变化否认者：&lt;/strong>;这些消费者不相信气候在变化。因此，他们不参与 ESG，也不打算参与。他们约占美国消费者的 4%。&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;习惯消费者：&lt;/strong>;这些消费者倾向于通过购买他们熟悉和喜爱的产品来简化他们的生活。他们并不积极关注气候变化，因此他们在购物时不会考虑可持续性。他们约占美国消费者的 30%。&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;好奇的消费者：&lt;/strong>;这些消费者购买环保产品是出于对这些产品的好奇心，这些产品通常标榜为优质产品。他们并不积极关注环境，但他们喜欢尝试新的优质产品。他们约占美国消费者的 11%。&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;有意识的非消费者：&lt;/strong>;这些人积极关注气候变化并有一些环保的生活习惯，但不购买环保品牌产品。他们约占美国消费者的 32%，是最大的群体。&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;有意识的消费者：&lt;/strong>;这些消费者积极关注地球并在购物时考虑产品的环保证书，因为他们将此视为通往更可持续生活的途径。他们约占美国消费者的 24%。&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;Conscious Nonconsumers——一个被许多消费品公司和零售商忽视的庞大群体——提供了大量、未开发的机会。我们的大部分后续研究都集中在这个细分市场上，试图发现是什么阻碍了他们的购买，以及消费品公司和零售商可以做些什么来占领这个市场。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;没有单一的人口统计资料有意识的非消费者。他们跨越年龄以及收入和教育水平。他们住在城市地区的可能性与住在小镇的可能性一样大。大多数人的共同点是希望与他们当前的生活方式改变相匹配——例如，调低恒温器、骑自行车上班和过度循环利用。我们还看到，虽然许多有意识的非消费者选择不尝试可持续购物，但他们确实有积极的意图。令人印象深刻的 71% 的 Conscious Nonconsumers 表示他们愿意为可持续产品支付更多费用，理论上，如果有直接好处，如果它不影响其他因素，并且如果他们认为这真的对地球、员工或或供应商。在我们的调查受访者中，44% 的 Conscious 非消费者希望在未来三年内增加对此类品牌的支出。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;购买障碍&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;但自 Conscious 以来非消费者目前不购买可持续产品，作为我们研究的一部分，我们提出了额外的问题以了解障碍。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;第一个障碍——可能也是最难克服的障碍——是这些消费者不他们在购物时积极考虑可持续性。 34% 的有意识的非消费者报告了这一障碍，凸显了该细分市场对可持续性的看法。他们专注于减少燃料、家庭能源等的消耗，而不太关心他们购买的产品。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;第二个障碍是有意识的非消费者面临的障碍，他们&lt;em>;是&lt;/em>;购物时考虑可持续性：37% 的受访者表示，他们难以权衡取舍，无法做出明智的购买决定。例如，他们很难理解和比较竞争产品的碳足迹，而且通常一开始就对什么使产品具有可持续性或不具有可持续性只有模糊的理解。当我们要求各细分市场的消费者确定两种产品中哪一种具有较低的碳足迹时，我们看到了这种知识差距。平均而言，所有消费者类别中有 75% 的受访者不知道或回答不正确。例如，只有 11% 的人正确回答一次性塑料袋的碳足迹低于一次性棉袋。只有 22% 的人正确回答无机蔬菜的碳足迹低于有机肉类。这种知识差距是在可持续采购中做出正确选择的障碍。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;采购的最终障碍是有形的。 34% 的有意识的非消费者认为价格是购买的障碍；这些更高的价格意味着消费者需要更加努力地工作才能证明购买的合理性。另一个问题：通常更难找到可持续的产品。例如，消费者可能需要前往专卖店或普通超市内的不同部门才能找到范围更广的可持续商品。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;如何接触有意识的非消费者&lt;/strong>;&lt;/ h2>; &lt;p>;品牌和零售商可以承认自己在“说做”差距中的责任，并立即采取行动消除消费者和购物者面临的障碍。在我们 2022 年的调查中，一半的美国消费者认为品牌和零售商有责任帮助消费者以可持续的方式购物——相比之下，例如，只有 19% 的人认为这是政府的责任。品牌和零售商可以采取三项基本行动：&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;简化消费者的决策。&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;品牌可以通过强调具体的、可衡量的 ESG 特征来帮助提高意识并缩小知识差距引导消费者选择的同时。美容公司 Natura 清楚地阐述了其与巴西亚马逊雨林社区的公平贸易实践的具体积极影响。在其网站上，&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.naturabrasil.fr/en-us/our-values/sustainable-development&quot;>;报告&lt;/a>;：“通过购买 Natura EKOS 产品，您正在帮助改善这些巴西农业社区中 2,000 个家庭的收入——总计近 8,500 人。也正是由于 Natura EKOS 产品和这些社区的努力，180 万公顷的森林得到了保护，以实现可持续的资源利用，并为子孙后代创造更美好的未来。” Natura EKOS 产品包装使用明确的术语（例如素食主义者、亚马逊雨林成分、公平贸易和雨林保护），并量化产品的好处，例如购买可再灌装产品使 EKOS 产品的塑料减少 25% .它有意识地避免消费者因多个 ESG 符号而感到困惑。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;对于零售商而言，简化消费者决策意味着让可持续产品成为消费者购买旅程的一部分。这可能涉及帮助消费者轻松识别可持续产品。例如，沃尔玛提供由零售商归类为“可持续发展领导者”的公司提供的在线产品系列，并使用“&lt;a href=&quot;https://corporate.walmart.com/global-responsibility/hunger-nutrition/great-for -you&quot;>;Great for You&lt;/a>;”图标帮助消费者识别货架上更健康的食品选择。零售商还可以通过在消费者做出购买决定时将可持续产品与其他所有产品放在同一个货架上，让他们更容易获得，从而从中受益。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;将 ESG 纳入现有的选择理由。&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;消费者已经在质量、价格、健康和便利性这些相互竞争的优先事项之间取得平衡。添加新的 ESG 维度会带来额外的复杂性，这可能会迫使消费者不选择可持续的选项。最有效的公司将 ESG 纳入了现有的考虑因素。例如，反叛者已经证明，ESG 可以使产品更易于购买（通​​过 &lt;a href=&quot;https://smolproducts.com/&quot;>;Smol&lt;/a>; 等无塑料自动订阅）、更实惠（通过耐用、可重复使用的产品，例如 &lt;a href=&quot;https://us.upcirclebeauty.com/products/hemp-and-cotton-makeup-pads&quot;>;UpCircle 的&lt;/a>;卸妆棉垫），而且更简单（通过 multibenefit 和多功能产品，例如 &lt;a href=&quot;https://carenb-com.translate.goog/?_x_tr_sl=pt&amp;amp;_x_tr_tl=en&amp;amp;_x_tr_hl=en&amp;amp;_x_tr_pto=sc&quot;>;Care Natural Beauty&lt;/a>;）。现有品牌必须效仿他们。零售商可以通过激励措施加强成本效益等式的积极方面，从而加快可持续性的采用。例如，冰岛提供&lt;a href=&quot;https://about.iceland.co.uk/wp-content/uploads/2019/08/reverse_vending_machines.pdf&quot;>;“反向”自动售货机&lt;/a>;，其中 PET 瓶以换取商店信用。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;发展现有品牌。&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;我们的研究发现，有意识的非消费者可能会看重相同但更好的版本&lt;strong>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/ strong>;他们喜欢的产品，只要价格不高得多。品牌采取两种基本方法：创新包装设计和调整产品形式或成分。作为前者的一个例子，考虑联合利华的 TRESemmé 品牌，其洗发水瓶由 100% 回收和可回收塑料制成。就其本身而言，零售商 Sainsbury&#39;s 销售采用无托盘包装的肉类和鸡肉，并在其自有品牌中淘汰了一次性塑料 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.packaging-gateway.com/news/sainsburys-plastic-dip- pots/&quot;>;浸锅&lt;/a>;。作为调整成分的一个例子，Mustela 推出了植物基婴儿毛巾，作为其原始婴儿毛巾的无塑料版本。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3 style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;。 . .&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;转化有意识的非消费者是提供可行且易于找到的选项的问题，并使价值主张清晰。由于物有所值是这一细分市场的一个关键考虑因素，因此取得最大进展的品牌和零售商将是那些也可以让他们的可持续产品价格合理的品牌和零售商。对于大多数公司而言，这需要平衡可持续产品的交付与成本节约。这是一个棘手的平衡，但可以通过让消费者相信，除了回收利用、骑自行车上班和降温之外，他们还可以改变他们的购买习惯，从而帮助公司实现盈利增长。&lt;/p>; &lt;div>; &lt; em>;作者想感谢 Luciana Batista 的贡献。&lt;/em>; &lt;/div>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;br>;&lt;hr>;&lt;div>;获得更多RSS：&lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.net&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.net&lt;/a>; &lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot; https://feedx.best&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.best&lt;/a>;&lt;br>;&lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Mon, 05 Jun 2023 20:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Today&rsquo;s Cyber Threats Require Modern Cloud Network Security - SPONSOR CONTENT FROM MICROSOFT X AMD]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/sponsored/2023/06/todays-cyber-threats-require-modern-cloud-network-security]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;html>; &lt;head>;&lt;/head>; &lt;body>; &lt;figure>; &lt;img 咏叹调-describedby=&quot;caption-attachment-356576&quot; src=&quot;/resources/images/article_assets/2023/05/Azure_AMD-Hero_Image-for-HBR-Network-Security-Article.jpg&quot; >; &lt;/figure>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong >;作者：Narayan Annamalai&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;当网络安全措施失败时，结果可能是毁灭性的且代价高昂。在过去的一年里，网络安全故障导致网站瘫痪、航班延误、视频游戏无法运行等等。此类事件会削弱客户、投资者和董事会成员的信任，并导致出现您不希望出现的头条新闻类型。技术挑战以及网络攻击日益频繁和复杂的问题引发了跨行业的对话——以及可以理解的担忧。 CISO 和其他 C-Suite 成员以及安全专家都认识到云采用率的提高和向混合工作的转变如何扩大了攻击面。一些领导人还提到了动态和复杂的监管环境所带来的挑战。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;考虑这些安全统计数据：&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;网络犯罪的年度成本预计为 &lt;span style=&quot; text-decoration: underline;&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;color: #3366ff; text-decoration: underline;&quot;>;&lt;a style=&quot;color: #3366ff; text-decoration: underline;&quot; href=&quot;https://cybersecurityventures.com/stats/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;到 2026 年超过 20 万亿美元&lt;/a>;&lt;/span>;&lt;/span>;。&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;一个网络安全 &lt;span style=&quot;text-decoration: underline;&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;color: #3366ff; text-decoration: underline;&quot;>;&lt;a style=&quot;color: #3366ff; text-decoration: underline;&quot; href=&quot;https://eng.umd.edu/news/story/study-hackers-attack-every-39-seconds&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;攻击每 39 秒发生一次&lt;/a>;&lt; /span>;&lt;/span>;.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;span style=&quot;color: #3366ff;&quot;>;&lt;a style=&quot;color: #3366ff; text-decoration: underline;&quot; href=&quot;https://securityintelligence.com/articles/most-common-cyberattack-patterns-2022/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;2022 年四种最常见的攻击类型&lt;/a>;&lt;/span >; 是勒索软件、电子邮件泄露、供应链攻击和对物联网 (IoT) 设备的攻击。&lt;​​/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;您的网络是您组织的核心，也是对不良行为者的诱人奖品。网络安全将控制措施落实到位，以帮助防止网络犯罪分子破坏它。让我们探讨一下如何做。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;保护您的数据和资产&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;云网络安全可以以传统安全工具无法实现的方式应对现代网络安全威胁.它可以保护对于支持云环境中的混合劳动力至关重要的数据和应用程序。它使您能够保护组织资产免受新出现的攻击并保护应用程序和基础设施。&lt;/p>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div id=&quot;DFP_IC_pos3&quot;>; &lt;script type=&quot;text/javascript&quot;>;if (isAdobeSync( )) googletag.cmd.push(function() { googletag.display(&quot;DFP_IC_pos3&quot;); });&lt;/script>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;云中的网络安全很重要因为所有资产都通过网络访问。以下是云中有效网络安全的主要组成部分：&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;零信任方法：&lt;/strong>; 零信任意味着使用最低权限访问来限制用户访问，始终验证身份，并通过假设安全漏洞最小化爆炸半径和段访问。它可以帮助您管理人员、设备、数据和资产，这样您就可以启用混合劳动力、保护敏感信息并自信地管理多云资产。&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;网络防火墙：&lt;/strong>;网络防火墙通过监视和检查您的网络流量并阻止恶意流量来帮助防止网络犯罪分子访问您的网络资源。&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;DDoS 保护：&lt;/strong>;分布式拒绝服务 (DDoS) 攻击涉及网络犯罪分子针对通过向网站或服务充斥流量来破坏网络服务。 DDoS 保护通常提供监控、攻击缓解和其他防御功能。&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Web 应用程序保护&lt;/strong>;：Web 应用程序和应用程序编程接口 (API) 是网络犯罪分子的热门目标，因为它们可通过公共互联网访问，并可能提供对敏感数据的访问。 Web 应用程序保护有助于保护网站、应用程序和 API 免受攻击。&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;行动中的网络安全&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;制造商创建了大量的敏感信息数据，包括知识产权和研发数据。他们使用的物联网设备在 DDoS 攻击中具有很强的针对性。他们的供应链也经常成为目标。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;制造商可能比其他行业的制造商更愿意向犯罪分子支付赎金，因为他们的数据很敏感，而且他们依赖供应链来接收产品组件和运送他们的产品。针对供应链的攻击可能会使运营陷入停顿。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;让我们来看看一个常见的制造用例——安全互联洞察，可用于防盗、丢失监控、仓库优化、以及整个城市或零售环境中的交通流量洞察力，以自动补货。制造商可以通过互连的工厂设置实时监控其仓库车间、装配线、生产和配送的活动。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;连同用于关键任务分析的机器学习和计算技术，制造商和其他行业需要云网络安全来确保数据安全并将中断降至最低。它保护您的应用程序和网络基础设施免受威胁。 The benefits of using network security include reducing security threats, improving operational efficiency, and increasing business agility.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Cloud network security services, like those of &lt;a href=&quot;https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/solutions/network-security/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;color: #3366ff;&quot;>;Azure Network Security&lt;/span>;&lt;/a>;, paired with Microsoft Azure Virtual Machines powered by AMD, ensure you can deliver secure connected insights efficiently. Features include:&lt;/p>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div id=&quot;DFP_IC_pos4&quot;>; &lt;script type=&quot;text/javascript&quot;>;if (isAdobeSync()) googletag.cmd.push(function() { googletag.display(&quot;DFP_IC_pos4&quot;); });&lt;/script>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;Operations scalability to maximize warehouse efficiency&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Faster issue resolution tracking products across the value chain&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Better safety and quality control&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;On-time delivery of goods and services&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Protect against modern threats &lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Cyber threats continually challenge traditional security methods. Modern network security can answer the call with a Zero Trust approach, network firewall, DDoS protection, and web application protection.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Microsoft and AMD share the objective of prioritizing network security services—fully secure modern network protection for Azure workloads. Network security can help you protect your people, data, and operations in any sector.&lt;/p>; &lt;hr>; &lt;p>;&lt;em>;&lt;b>;Narayan Annamalai&lt;/b>;&lt;/em>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;em>;&lt;strong>;leads the SDN product management group in Microsoft Azure that focuses on virtual networks, load balancing and network security.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/em>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;&lt;em>;&lt;span>;Learn how &lt;a title=&quot;https://www.amd.com/en/case-studies?keyword=Azure&quot; href=&quot;https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/partners/directory/amd-corporation/?cdn=disable#overview&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;AMD helps accelerate Azure workloads&lt;/a>; and &lt;/span>;how &lt;a title=&quot;https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/solutions/network-security/&quot; href=&quot;https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/solutions/network-security/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;Azure Network Security&lt;/a>; can help your organization protect your data and assets.&lt;/em>;&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;/body>; &lt;/html>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Fri, 02 Jun 2023 22:25:02 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[You&rsquo;re Not Powerless in the Face of Imposter Syndrome]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/youre-not-powerless-in-the-face-of-imposter-syndrome]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/05/Jun23_01_1432577634_4727481.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;HBR Staff; Simone Wave/Stocksy; Vladimir18/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Research shows that high achievers from underrepresented backgrounds often find themselves confronting imposter syndrome or feeling they don&amp;#8217;t fit in, are not welcome, or don&amp;#8217;t belong. But understanding imposter syndrome does little to end it. The author, who studied underrepresented board members for his PhD and who interacts with hundreds of aspiring and existing board directors in his role at an executive search firm, has found that attributes of moxie &amp;#8212; strength of will, self-discipline, and the ability to persist despite challenges &amp;#8212; were vital to underrepresented directors&amp;#8217; success. He recommends four tactics to help make moxie your own super power.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/youre-not-powerless-in-the-face-of-imposter-syndrome?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/youre-not-powerless-in-the-face-of-imposter-syndrome?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;“I was intimidated for many years in the early part of my board career because I didn&#39;t have a business degree and felt underprepared,” a female board director once told me. Another director, explaining that she “grew up in the shadows of a plantation” reflected, “It&#39;s still very much a white male show, so the fact that I was the first African American female on the board was astounding to me.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;As US practice leader of CEO and board services at Boyden, an executive search firm, I interact with hundreds of aspiring and existing directors. Questions about their qualifications for board service remain a concern for many of the people I talk to, particularly those from underrepresented backgrounds.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;My experience aligns with &lt;a href=&quot;https://psycnet.apa.org/doiLanding?doi=10.1037%2F0033-3204.30.3.495&quot;>;research&lt;/a>; that shows that high achievers from underrepresented backgrounds often find themselves confronting imposter syndrome, or doubting their skills and achievements or fearing being exposed as a fraud. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ucalgary.ca/news/impostor-syndrome-diversity-equity-inclusion-issue&quot;>;Women and people of color&lt;/a>; may be more likely to feel they don&#39;t fit in, they&#39;re not welcome, and they don&#39;t belong.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Imposter syndrome can be crippling mentally and emotionally, drain your energy and attention, and cause you to fall short of the performance you are capable of, thus, feeding the cycle of self-doubt. If you experience imposter syndrome, you may explain away your successes by thinking anyone could have done what you did, or thinking you just got lucky, or fearing that others are mistaken in believing that you&#39;re talented. As if that isn&#39;t bad enough, when you stumble or face challenges, your self-perceived incompetence looms larger than life — increasing your chance of failure and perpetuating the syndrome.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;While awareness of this cycle is helpful, understanding imposter syndrome does little to end it. Instead, you need action. And to take action, you need moxie.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Moxie: A Working Definition&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Moxie reflects &lt;a href=&quot;https://link.springer.com/article/10.1007/s12144-022-03304-7&quot;>;an intensity of motivation&lt;/a>; and is related to (but distinct from) traits such as grit, self-control, and the ability to overcome procrastination. The term was &lt;a href=&quot;https://muse-jhu-edu.ezp-prod1.hul.harvard.edu/article/456883/pdf&quot;>;popularized&lt;/a>; by a 1920s soft drink advertised to give its drinkers vigor, nerve, and pep. After Boston Red Sox player Ted Williams endorsed the drink, moxie entered the cultural consciousness as shorthand for strength, aggressiveness, skill, and know-how.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.proquest.com/docview/2670010304&quot;>;my own research&lt;/a>;, I&#39;ve seen that the attributes of moxie — strength of will, self-discipline, and the ability to persist despite challenges — was vital to underrepresented directors&#39; success. One Latina executive I spoke with described moxie in this way: “I noticed my Black colleagues overcoming the objections coming at them in their careers. Whenever they set goals, they achieved them. They had a &#39;refuse to lose&#39; mentality. And once I emulated what I saw in them, I rapidly ascended the corporate ladder myself.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The directors I interviewed explained that they neither internalized the obstacles they encountered as personal failures, nor did they externalize them as irreconcilable systemic barriers. In fact, when I asked them to identify the barriers they faced, it took them a while to recall and identify them because they had transformed their obstacles into sources of motivation. It became apparent that moxie was a response to their childhood experiences of racism, sexism, microaggression, and other difficulties.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;If you are a woman or person of color and you want to push forward and advance in your career, you will encounter obstacles and you will experience failure. At these times, you have a choice to make: Will you allow the obstacles and failures to feed imposter syndrome, or will you pick yourself up and use moxie to persist toward your goal?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;If you choose moxie, you may not be disappointed. In &lt;a href=&quot;https://link.springer.com/article/10.1007/s12144-022-03304-7&quot;>;a study&lt;/a>; by psychology professor Jessica Curtis and colleagues, moxie was found to predict intrinsic and extrinsic motivation more than other motivational constructs like grit or self-control. Moxie also predicted goal achievement — largely because people with moxie invest more resources into their aims. For example, one director I interviewed realized that her career choice of spending years as a consultant and then becoming CEO of a small company created substantial obstacles to her landing a corporate board seat. “Boards still tend to recruit against a checklist of wanting a sitting CEO of a multinational corporation,” she explained. “So when I&#39;d approach recruiters, they would push back with, &#39;Ooo…ah…I&#39;ll &lt;em>;really&lt;/em>; have to convince the board that it is worth it for them to speak with you.&#39;” At this point, she could have agreed with others&#39; opinions that she wasn&#39;t boardroom material. Instead, she recognized the need to translate her experiences and skills into language a board would understand and find attractive. Now, only a few years into board service, she sits on three publicly traded company boards and three nonprofit boards.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Making Moxie Your Superpower&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Based on the experiences of the underrepresented directors I interviewed in my study and the aspiring and existing directors I continue to interact with, I suggest four tactics to help you make moxie your very own superpower:&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;1. Utilize the strengths you&#39;ve forged through culture-based hardships.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;People of color have endured centuries of hardship and oppression and, through these, we have forged attitudes and approaches that give us unique advantages, as research regarding &lt;a href=&quot;https://doi.org/10.1177/0095798419889752&quot;>;racism-related coping&lt;/a>; and posttraumatic growth following racial trauma has shown. Tabitha Grier-Reed and colleagues at the University of Minnesota &lt;a href=&quot;https://psycnet.apa.org/doiLanding?doi=10.1037/tra0001220&quot;>;have found&lt;/a>; that deepening your connections with others, harnessing your inner strengths, developing fresh perspectives and appreciation for life, and connecting with your spirituality, in particular, help us grow and flourish in our careers and life.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;One Black women board member I interviewed explained that her grandparents had raised her to understand the inequity of opportunities presented to people of color. As a result, she persisted through barriers because, as she put it: “I had no choice. Like other women of my generation, we were told by our parents and grandparents to just get out there and do it. Make it happen. If you&#39;re given an opportunity, demonstrate to them that you deserve the opportunity.” Similarly, the other directors I interviewed explained that they learned to ignore, go under, go over, go around, or go through any obstacles put in front of them — in other words, they used moxie.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;To turn your own hardships into moxie, identify a challenging situation from your past that you ultimately overcame. Reflect on how you got through it and how you resolved the situation. Finally, formulate these as the principles you learned and strengths you gained. Together, these are some ingredients of your unique brand of moxie.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;For example, women and students of color &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sciencenews.org/article/science-technology-math-race-ethnicity-gender-diversity-gap&quot;>;commonly report&lt;/a>; facing negative stereotypes when enrolling in STEM courses. One such woman recalled, “I had to take organic chemistry, but without the years of preparatory courses all my classmates had. So I had lots of questions that seemed very elementary to others. As a result, everyone — students, lecturers, and my mentor — thought I didn&#39;t belong there and refused to help me.” To overcome this formidable challenge, she explained, “I spent many sleepless nights reading extra material, going over class notes and homework multiple times, and slowly caught up. I ultimately graduated from my degree program with one of the highest grades.” From this experience, this young woman recognized that she relished challenge and realized she could rely on her strengths of a strong work ethic, self-discipline, focus, and ability to learn unfamiliar, scientific material with limited support. This moxie continued to help her flourish in her career.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;2. Give yourself permission to play. &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Herminia Ibarra, professor at London Business School, has &lt;a href=&quot;https://doi.org/10.2307/2667055&quot;>;conducted extensive research&lt;/a>; on what she calls “identity play,” which involves experimenting with new ideas and behaviors as you take on new professional challenges and roles. She uses the term “play” to normalize the idea that you won&#39;t perform as well in the new role as you do in more familiar roles.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Importantly, play is not a “fake it till you make it” situation. Instead, it&#39;s about authentically growing into new roles by trying new behaviors, gaining confidence, and allowing yourself time and space for development. This was a critical tactic for one director I interviewed, who explained, “Debt financing, bond markets, and the investor base were foreign concepts to me. So when these came up, I reminded myself that I had to have just enough knowledge to stay on the stage, and I kept trying and focused on being a learner.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;To foster your own identity play, think of a work situation where you are still on a learning curve. Break the situation or role into a series of small learning experiences with deliberate action planning, experimentation, and gathering data on your performance. Then repeat the cycle.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;3. Tune out the naysayers.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;If you are working hard to achieve much in your career and life, you are bound to encounter naysayers who are more than eager to point out the ways you don&#39;t measure up. The late Kaleel Jamison, a pioneering career woman in 1970s corporate America, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Nibble-Theory-Kernel-Power-Self-Empowerment/dp/0809141876/ref=asc_df_0809141876/?tag=hyprod-20&amp;amp;linkCode=df0&amp;amp;hvadid=312281483245&amp;amp;hvpos=&amp;amp;hvnetw=g&amp;amp;hvrand=1946812945678087117&amp;amp;hvpone=&amp;amp;hvptwo=&amp;amp;hvqmt=&amp;amp;hvdev=c&amp;amp;hvdvcmdl=&amp;amp;hvlocint=&amp;amp;hvlocphy=9002000&amp;amp;hvtargid=pla-760812857192&amp;amp;psc=1&quot;>;called these messages “nibbles”&lt;/a>; intended to make you smaller.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;When you agree with the nibble (or, worse, initiate the nibble yourself), you feed the imposter syndrome. I recently witnessed this in a young and talented mentee of mine who has been spearheading transformative change in her company despite having taken her role only months ago. While her proposed initiative had been blessed by her boss and her CEO, another leader above her blocked her with, “Well, your plan is completely unworkable.” She slid into a pit of paralyzing self-doubt. Having seen the plan myself, I knew the criticism was unfounded but suspected there was more to the story. Once we debriefed on the situation, I realized that she had circulated her plan in a way that inadvertently criticized the leader&#39;s work, resulting in a predictable backlash. We then discussed more effective ways to solicit support from the various stakeholders involved—including the leader in question. She then created and implemented a more successful approach, in turn, learning from this experience and strengthening her competencies.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;When you experience criticism, begin by reframing it as a hypothesis (eg, “The plan will not work”). Next, identify ways to test the hypothesis, such as by getting feedback from trusted mentors or conducting a low-risk proof of concept. Third, gather data and test the hypothesis. Regardless of the results, you will gain concrete and actionable feedback that will help you progress.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;4. Recognize when to walk away.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Imposter syndrome often is used to mask systemic bias and racism in the workplace, as Ruchika Tulshyan and Jodi-Ann Burey aptly &lt;a href=&quot;/2021/02/stop-telling-women-they-have-imposter-syndrome&quot;>;noted&lt;/a>;. This means that moxie won&#39;t work in every situation.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;One director I interviewed had a longstanding dream to become the CEO at her employer. “I eventually realized that even though I was performing well, I couldn&#39;t control how the leadership decided who actually got C-suite opportunities and who didn&#39;t. So, I made the hard decision that I still wanted to be a CEO, but it didn&#39;t have to be there. And I left.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;When you encounter an obstacle, take time to assess the competencies, energy, and passion you would need to overcome it, and then soberly evaluate whether you want to invest your resources in this way. For example, if you discover that success requires knowledge or skills you don&#39;t have and cannot realistically develop in the needed time frame, or when you cannot get the mentoring or advocacy you need to succeed, it may be wiser to walk away. When you deliberately evaluate the obstacles facing you, you will either take on the challenges fully informed, or reallocate your abilities in more suitable environments.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;I will be the first to admit that the steps I describe above are not easy. Turning away from the imposter syndrome and embracing your moxie requires you to re-examine your assumptions, values, and beliefs; risk new behaviors; and commit more to yourself and your growth than you may ever have before. In other words, embracing moxie sets you on a path of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Transformative-Learning-Practice-Community-Workplace/dp/0470257903&quot;>;transformative learning&lt;/a>;, which is rooted in the truism that growth comes from discomfort. As the old man in George Bernard Shaw&#39;s &lt;em>;Back to Methusaleh &lt;/em>;noted&lt;em>;,&lt;/em>; “Life is not meant to be easy, my child, but take courage, for it can be delightful.”&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;br>;&lt;hr>;&lt;div>;获取更多RSS：&lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.net&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.net&lt;/a>; &lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.best&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.best&lt;/a>;&lt;br>;&lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Fri, 02 Jun 2023 22:25:02 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[4 Areas of Cyber Risk That Boards Need to Address]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/4-areas-of-cyber-risk-that-boards-need-to-address]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_02_947442668.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;PM Images/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;In our technology-dependent society, the effectiveness of cyber risk governance of companies affects its stock prices, as well as short-term and long-term shareholder value. New SEC cybersecurity rules provide a solid basis for transparency. Unfortunately, monitoring the long-term effectiveness of a cyber risk management strategy is not easy to grasp. This article provides four critical areas investors should be informed about for evaluating its long-term effectiveness.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/4-areas-of-cyber-risk-that-boards-need-to-address?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/4-areas-of-cyber-risk-that-boards-need-to-address?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;As technological innovations such as cloud computing, the Internet of Things, robotic process automation, and predictive analytics are integrated into organizations, it makes them increasingly susceptible to cyber threats. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cyentia.com/wp-content/uploads/IRIS2020_cyentia.pdf&quot;>;Fortune 1000 companies&lt;/a>;, for example, have a 25% probability of being breached, and 10% of them will face multi-million loss. In &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.house.gov/meetings/SM/SM00/20150422/103276/HHRG-114-SM00-20150422-SD003-U4.pdf&quot;>;smaller companies&lt;/a>;, 60% will be out of business within six months of a severe cyberattack. This means that governing and assessing cyber risks becomes a prerequisite for successful business performance — and that investors need to know how vulnerable companies really are.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This need for transparency has been recognized by the regulators and facilitated by the new cyber security rules. Currently, the US Security and Exchange Commission (SEC) &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reuters.com/legal/legalindustry/sec-is-inching-closer-clarity-cybersecurity-requirements-2023-04-19/&quot;>;has increased its enforcement&lt;/a>; to ensure companies maintain adequate cybersecurity controls and appropriately disclose cyber-related risks and incidents.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Unfortunately, our research shows that cyber risk is not easy to understand. Organizations seem often to &lt;a href=&quot;https://riskcenter.wharton.upenn.edu/wp-content/uploads/2017/11/WP2017-18_Perceptions-of-Corp-Cyber-RiskInsuracnce-Decisions.pdf&quot;>;underestimate the financial loss&lt;/a>; related to cyber threats. These can include:&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;Immediate effects, such as business interruptions, decreases in production, and delays in product launches, as well as additional costs to recover from an attack.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Long-term consequences, such as damage to the company&#39;s competitiveness and reputational loss, as well as loss of revenues from intellectual property theft, data theft, or unauthorized use of proprietary information.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;There&#39;s also legal risks resulting from neglecting, for instance, &lt;a href=&quot;https://digital-strategy.ec.europa.eu/en/library/cyber-resilience-act&quot;>;cyber resilience obligations in products and services&lt;/a>;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tanium.com/blog/cyber-whistleblowing-is-putting-security-chiefs-in-the-hot-seat/&quot;>;breach reporting&lt;/a>;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://cms.law/en/media/international/files/publications/publications/gdpr-enforcement-tracker-report-may-2022?v=1&quot;>;safeguarding of sensitive data&lt;/a>;, or &lt;a href=&quot;https://op.europa.eu/en/publication-detail/-/publication/2f8456d4-5c60-11eb-b487-01aa75ed71a1/language-en&quot;>;critical infrastructure protection&lt;/a>;.&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;There isn&#39;t a simple way forward, though. &lt;a href=&quot;https://weis2019.econinfosec.org/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2019/05/WEIS_2019_paper_22.pdf&quot;>;Overinvesting in cyber risk management&lt;/a>; or risk-management strategies that don&#39;t align with business needs can have &lt;a href=&quot;https://scholarspace.manoa.hawaii.edu/server/api/core/bitstreams/22d83d19-e7e4-4dcd-a69b-df297e2455fa/content&quot;>;equivalently negative impacts&lt;/a>;. This article explains the importance of the SEC&#39;s new cybersecurity rules and addresses the four essential topics investors should discuss with the board for evaluating the long-term effectiveness of their companies&#39; cyber risk management strategy.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Transparency in Cyber-Risk Governance&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Being transparent about cybersecurity isn&#39;t just best practice, it&#39;s now a requirement for US companies. The SEC&#39;s &lt;a href=&quot;/2022/11/is-your-board-prepared-for-new-cybersecurity-regulations&quot;>;new cybersecurity rules&lt;/a>; “require publicly enlisted companies to disclose their cybersecurity governance capabilities, including the board&#39;s oversight of cyber risk, a description of management&#39;s role in assessing and managing cyber risks, the relevant expertise of such management, and management&#39;s role in implementing the company&#39;s cybersecurity policies, procedures, and strategies.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This kind of disclosure allows investors to evaluate the attention of executives and business leaders to cyber risks. Management boards need to understand how these threats can cause material harm. For instance, the ransomware attack on &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.pcmag.com/news/ransomware-attack-costs-hanesbrands-100-million-in-lost-sales&quot;>;Hanesbrands&lt;/a>; disrupted order fulfillment for three weeks, causing a $100 million loss in revenue. Another example is the IT outage caused by a cyber attack at &lt;a href=&quot;https://healthitsecurity.com/news/tenet-healthcare-cyberattack-leads-to-100m-in-lost-q2-revenue&quot;>;Tenet Healthcare&lt;/a>;, which also resulted in $100 million of lost revenues. And the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-07-10/kaseya-failed-to-address-security-before-hack-ex-employees-say&quot;>;Kaseya VSA breach&lt;/a>; was the result of insecure operational software that ultimately let to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.channele2e.com/investors/private-equity/kaseya-private-equity-investor-tpg-pursues-initial-public-offering-ipo/&quot;>;the postponement of an initial public offering&lt;/a>; that sought to raise $875 million.&lt;/p>; &lt;article-promo>; &lt;hbr-component type=&quot;promo&quot; is-insight=&quot;insight-center&quot; title=&quot;Managing Cyber Risk&quot; dek=&quot;Exploring the challenges and the solutions.&quot; cta-text=&quot;&quot; href=&quot;/insight-center/managing-cyber-risk&quot;>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/insight-center/managing-cyber-risk&quot; style=&quot;color:black;text-decoration:none&quot;>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; Insight Center Collection &lt;/div>; &lt;h3>;Managing Cyber Risk&lt;/h3>; &lt;div>; Exploring the challenges and the solutions. &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hbr-component>; &lt;/article-promo>; &lt;p>;Under the new SEC guidelines companies are also required to report within four days of incidents that are deemed “material.” The “materiality” determination is influenced by the incident&#39;s impact on the company&#39;s business, operations, and financial conditions. This mandatory incident reporting allows investors to evaluate the effectiveness of the firm&#39;s cyber risk policies and may provide learnings for future improvements in cyber risk management. And there is a significant opportunity for improvement &amp;nbsp;since the cost of cyber crime — including the cost for recovery and remediation — are expected to grow to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.weforum.org/agenda/2023/01/global-rules-crack-down-cybercrime/&quot;>;$10.5 trillion per year by 2025&lt;/a>;.&lt;del>;&lt;/del>;&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;4 Critical Areas Investors Should Expect Boards to Address&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;These new cybersecurity rules should be considered a starting point for the dialogue about cyber-risk governance. To shore up their cybersecurity and stay ahead of the curve, companies need to consciously anticipate to changing internal and external environment and prioritize their cyber risk efforts accordingly.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Cyber risk can be hard to understand. Board members already deal with a lot of different strategic challenges, and when faced with issues around cyber risk — such as&lt;strong>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-07-10/kaseya-failed-to-address-security-before-hack-ex-employees-say?leadSource=uverify%20wall&quot;>;prioritizing product market growth versus its security&lt;/a>;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.dutchnews.nl/2023/04/court-tells-software-firm-nebu-to-come-clean-about-massive-data-leak/&quot;>;critical supplier dependency for secure service delivery,&lt;/a>; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wired.com/story/ransomware-tactics-cancer-photos-student-records/&quot;>;dealing with “heinous” aspects of ransomware attacks&lt;/a>;, or &lt;a href=&quot;https://cyberpeaceinstitute.org/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ukraine-Report-Q1_FINAL.pdf&quot;>;falling victim to geopolitical cyber tensions&lt;/a>; — they can be overwhelmed by the complexity and dynamic nature of the problems. Ultimately, this may cause cybersecurity-related blind spots, impacting the effectiveness of intended decisions and even yielding unintended consequences, which can lead to what is the “capability trap,” an ongoing deterioration of essential organizational processes. An essential characteristic of this trap is that its effects remain hidden from management for a very long time, until it is too late. The capability trap happens more often than many decision-makers imagine.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;To avoid this trap, companies need to focus on long-term effectiveness of their strategic decisions in four areas:&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;1. Align cyber risk management with business needs.&lt;del>;&lt;/del>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Boards have many corporate challenges to face and limited amounts of funding available to meet them, so being able to make the business case for this investment is essential. Clear insights into business, operational, and financial exposures: 1) generate language to discuss cyber risks, 2) connect to board members who do not have a technical background, and 3) &lt;a href=&quot;/2022/11/is-your-board-prepared-for-new-cybersecurity-regulations&quot;>;put cyber risk on the agenda&lt;/a>;, as well as allow for comparing this risk with other corporate challenges. It also helps the board explain the cyber risk exposure of the firm to investors. The &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nacdonline.org/services/content.cfm?ItemNumber=73711&quot;>;National Association of Corporate Directors (NACD)&lt;/a>; recognizes this need and deployed a commercially available solution to its members.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;2. Continuously monitor the cyber risk capability performance.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;The people, processes, and technology that make up firms is changing — and there are more and more areas that need protection, imposing an ever-increasing and dynamically shifting burden on the security capabilities of the organization, making lapses more likely. Solving these problems may require significant security capability improvements, which may take several months or even years.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Continuous monitoring is essential to establish if the cyber-risk management strategy performs as intended. Often management reporting dashboards, combined with insights from cyber event exercises are used for this purpose. Currently, in their most advanced form, these activities can capture the near real-time situation. Yet, for bridging the timing gap for utilizing improvements decision-makers have a need to see what the future outcome of their strategic decisions. This evokes the need for simulation aided approaches to strengthen &lt;a href=&quot;https://scholarspace.manoa.hawaii.edu/server/api/core/bitstreams/e9fbf734-b80c-45a4-ad7e-3ceb9768c07d/content&quot;>;managerial foresight capabilities&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;3. Proactively anticipate to the changing threat landscape.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Digital transformation also allows for faster, stronger, and more sophisticated attacks. This adversarial behavior strengthens the ongoing, changing, and emerging struggle between the offensive and the defensive. Both parties try to observe, learn, and anticipate each other. Consequently, adversaries introduce new, innovative techniques to remain successful.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Proactive cyber risk management enables defending organizations to learn from information sharing and exercises prior to cyberattacks. It contributes to security capability improvement prior to attacks and therefore reduces the number of significant security incidents. Reactive learning is significantly costlier because organizational improvement takes place based on the lessons learned from cybersecurity incidents that they have suffered. Currently, 56% of knowledgeable decision-makers make costly, &lt;a href=&quot;https://doi.org/10.3390/systems10020049&quot;>;suboptimal decisions&lt;/a>; when it comes to cyber risk management. The overspending on cyber risk management affects the profitability of the firm.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;4. Position security as a strategic business enabler.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Cyber-risk-management strategy implementation can be a challenge. As previously mentioned, the ongoing increase in surfaces that require protection and increasing adversarial behavior require more efforts from cybersecurity teams to improve the defensive posture. However, these teams are struggling with a lack of qualified security resources. Currently, the United States alone has more than 750,000 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cyberseek.org/heatmap.html&quot;>;cybersecurity job openings&lt;/a>;. This makes focusing on today&#39;s workload already difficult, let alone preparing for the defense posture of the future by running a cyber risk management program.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Effective ongoing workload reduction becomes essential. Therefore, secure by design, collaboration with other parties, automation, and the realization of economies of scale are critical to achieving a future state of security. Organizations that cannot properly make these adjustments become increasingly exposed to unintended control lapses and reactive learning mechanism.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The SEC&#39;s new cybersecurity rules provide a solid basis for transparency about companies cyber-risk governance. These rules are a great basis for starting a dialogue about long-term effectiveness of cyber-risk governance with the board. This article provides four critical areas relevant to this dialogue.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;em>;Acknowledgements: &lt;/em>;&lt;em>;This work is co-funded by ”Fondo Europeo di Sviluppo Regionale Puglia POR Puglia 2014 – 2020 – Asse I – Obiettivo specifico 1a – Azione 1.1 (RS) – Titolo Progetto: Suite prodotti Cybersecurity e SOC” and BV TECH SpA &lt;/em>;&lt;em>;This work is co-funded by &lt;a href=&quot;https://cams.mit.edu&quot;>;Cybersecurity at MIT Sloan&lt;/a>; (CAMS).&lt;/em>;&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Fri, 02 Jun 2023 21:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[The AI Hype Cycle Is Distracting Companies]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/the-ai-hype-cycle-is-distracting-companies]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_02_Skizzomat.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Illustration by Skizzomat&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Machine learning has an &amp;#8220;AI&amp;#8221; problem. With new breathtaking capabilities from generative AI released every several months &amp;#8212; and AI hype escalating at an even higher rate &amp;#8212; it&amp;#8217;s high time we differentiate most of today&amp;#8217;s practical ML projects from those research advances. This begins by correctly naming such projects: Call them &amp;#8220;ML,&amp;#8221; not &amp;#8220;AI.&amp;#8221; Including all ML initiatives under the &amp;#8220;AI&amp;#8221; umbrella oversells and misleads, contributing to a high failure rate for ML business deployments. For most ML projects, the term &amp;#8220;AI&amp;#8221; goes entirely too far &amp;#8212; it alludes to human-level capabilities. In fact, when you unpack the meaning of &amp;#8220;AI,&amp;#8221; you discover just how overblown a buzzword it is: If it doesn&amp;#8217;t mean artificial general intelligence, a grandiose goal for technology, then it just doesn&amp;#8217;t mean anything at all.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/the-ai-hype-cycle-is-distracting-companies?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/the-ai-hype-cycle-is-distracting-companies?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;You might think that news of “major AI breakthroughs” would do nothing but help machine learning&#39;s (ML) adoption. If only. Even before the latest splashes — most notably OpenAI&#39;s ChatGPT and other generative AI tools — the rich narrative about an emerging, all-powerful AI was already a growing problem for applied ML. That&#39;s because for most ML projects, the buzzword “AI” goes too far. It overly inflates expectations and distracts from the precise way ML will improve business operations.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Most practical use cases of ML — designed to improve the efficiencies of existing business operations — innovate in fairly straightforward ways. Don&#39;t let the glare emanating from this glitzy technology obscure the simplicity of its fundamental duty: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.predictiveanalyticsworld.com/book/pdf/Predictive_Analytics_by_Eric_Siegel_Excerpts.pdf&quot;>;the purpose of ML is to issue actionable predictions&lt;/a>;, which is why it&#39;s sometimes also called &lt;em>;predictive analytics&lt;/em>;. This means real value, so long as you eschew &lt;a href=&quot;https://blogs.scientificamerican.com/observations/the-medias-coverage-of-ai-is-bogus/&quot;>;false hype that &lt;/a>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://blogs.scientificamerican.com/observations/the-medias-coverage-of-ai-is-bogus/&quot;>;it is&lt;/a>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://blogs.scientificamerican.com/observations/the-medias-coverage-of-ai-is-bogus/&quot;>; “highly accurate,”&lt;/a>; like a digital crystal ball.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This capability translates into tangible value in an uncomplicated manner. The predictions drive millions of operational decisions. For example, by predicting which customers are most likely to cancel, a company can provide those customers incentives to stick around. And by predicting which credit card transactions are fraudulent, a card processor can disallow them. It&#39;s practical ML use cases like those that deliver the greatest impact on existing business operations, and the advanced data science methods that such projects apply boil down to ML and only ML.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Here&#39;s the problem: Most people conceive of ML as “AI.” This is a reasonable misunderstanding. But “AI” suffers from an unrelenting, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.aimyths.org/the-term-ai-has-a-clear-meaning&quot;>;incurable case of vagueness&lt;/a>; — it is a catch-all term of art that does not consistently refer to any particular method or value proposition. Calling ML tools “AI” oversells what most ML business deployments actually do. In fact, you couldn&#39;t overpromise more than you do when you call something “AI.” The moniker invokes the notion of artificial general intelligence (AGI), software capable of any intellectual task humans can do.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This exacerbates a significant problem with ML projects: They often lack a keen focus on their value — exactly how ML will render business processes more effective. As a result, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.kdnuggets.com/2022/01/models-rarely-deployed-industrywide-failure-machine-learning-leadership.html&quot;>;most ML projects fail to deliver value&lt;/a>;. In contrast, ML projects that keep their concrete operational objective front and center stand a good chance of achieving that objective.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;What Does AI Actually Mean?&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;&lt;em>;“&#39;AI-powered&#39; is tech&#39;s meaningless equivalent of &#39;all natural.&#39;”&lt;/em>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;–Devin Coldewey, &lt;a href=&quot;https://techcrunch.com/2017/01/10/ai-powered-is-techs-meaningless-equivalent-of-all-natural/&quot;>;&lt;em>;TechCrunch&lt;/em>;&lt;/a>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;AI cannot get away from AGI for two reasons. First, the term “AI” is generally thrown around without clarifying whether we&#39;re talking about AGI or &lt;em>;narrow AI&lt;/em>;, a term that essentially means practical, focused ML deployments. Despite the tremendous differences, the boundary between them blurs in common rhetoric and software sales materials.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Second, there&#39;s no satisfactory way to define AI besides AGI. Defining “AI” as something other than AGI has become a research &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.machine-ethics.net/podcast/what-is-ai-2/&quot;>;challenge unto itself&lt;/a>;, albeit a quixotic one. If it doesn&#39;t mean AGI, it doesn&#39;t mean anything — other suggested definitions either fail to qualify as “intelligent” in the ambitious spirit implied by “AI” or fail to establish an objective goal. We face this conundrum whether trying to pinpoint 1) a definition for “AI,” 2) the criteria by which a computer would qualify as “intelligent,” or 3) a performance benchmark that would certify true AI. These three are one and the same.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The problem is with the word “intelligence” itself. When used to describe a machine, it&#39;s relentlessly nebulous. That&#39;s bad news if AI is meant to be a legitimate field. Engineering can&#39;t pursue an imprecise goal. If you can&#39;t define it, you can&#39;t build it. To develop an apparatus, you must be able to measure how good it is — how well it performs and how close you are to the goal — so that you know you&#39;re making progress and so that you ultimately know when you&#39;ve succeeded in developing it.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In a vain attempt to fend off this dilemma, the industry continually performs an awkward dance of AI definitions that I call &lt;em>;the AI shuffle&lt;/em>;. AI means computers that do something smart (a circular definition). No, it&#39;s intelligence demonstrated by machines (even more circular, if that&#39;s possible). Rather, it&#39;s a system that employs certain advanced methodologies, such as ML, natural language processing, rule-based systems, speech recognition, computer vision, or other techniques that operate probabilistically (clearly, employing one or more of these methods doesn&#39;t automatically qualify a system as intelligent).&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;But surely a machine would qualify as intelligent if it seemed sufficiently humanlike, if you couldn&#39;t distinguish it from a human, say, by interrogating it in a chatroom — the famous &lt;em>;Turing Test.&lt;/em>; But the ability to fool people is an arbitrary, moving target, since human subjects become wiser to the trickery over time. Any given system will only pass the test at most once — fool us twice, shame on humanity. Another reason that passing the Turing Test misses the mark is because there&#39;s limited value or utility in doing so. If AI could exist, certainly it&#39;s supposed to be useful.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;What if we define AI by what it&#39;s capable of? For example, if we define AI as software that can perform a task so difficult that it traditionally requires a human, such as driving a car, mastering chess, or recognizing human faces. It turns out that this definition doesn&#39;t work either because, once a computer can do something, we tend to trivialized it. After all, computers can manage only mechanical tasks that are well-understood and well-specified. Once surmounted, the accomplishment suddenly loses its charm and the computer that can do it doesn&#39;t seem “intelligent” after all, at least not to the whole-hearted extent intended by the term “AI.” Once computers mastered chess, there was little sentiment that we&#39;d “solved” AI.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This paradox, known as &lt;em>;The AI Effect&lt;/em>;, tells us that, if it&#39;s possible, it&#39;s not intelligent. Suffering from an ever-elusive objective, AI inadvertently equates to “getting computers to do things too difficult for computers to do” — artificial impossibility. No destination will satisfy once you arrive; AI categorically defies definition. With due irony, the computer science pioneer Larry Tesler famously suggested that we might as well define AI as “whatever machines haven&#39;t done yet.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Ironically, it was ML&#39;s measurable success that hyped up AI in the first place. After all, improving measurable performance is &lt;em>;supervised machine learning&lt;/em>; in a nutshell. The feedback from evaluating the system against a benchmark — such as a sample of labeled data — guides its next improvement. By doing so, ML delivers unprecedented value in countless ways. It has earned its title as “the most important general-purpose technology of our era,” as &lt;a href=&quot;/2017/07/the-business-of-artificial-intelligence&quot;>;Harvard Business Review&lt;/a>; put it. More than anything else, ML&#39;s proven leaps and bounds have fueled AI hype.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;All in with Artificial General Intelligence&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;&lt;em>;“I predict we will see the third AI Winter within the next five years… When I graduated with my Ph.D. in AI and ML in &#39;91, AI was literally a bad word. No company would consider hiring somebody who was in AI.”&lt;/em>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;–Usama Fayyad, June 23, 2022, speaking at Machine Learning Week&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;There is one way to overcome this definition dilemma: Go all in and define AI as AGI, software capable of any intellectual task humans can do. If this science fiction-sounding goal were achieved, I submit that there would be a strong argument that it qualified as “intelligent.” And it&#39;s a measurable goal, at least in principle if not in practicality. For example, its developers could benchmark the system against a set of 1,000,000 tasks, including tens of thousands of complicated email requests you might send to a virtual assistant, various instructions for a warehouse employee you&#39;d just as well issue to a robot, and even brief, one-paragraph overviews for how the machine should, in the role of CEO, run a Fortune 500 company to profitability.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;AGI may set a clear-cut objective, but it&#39;s out of this world — as unwieldy an ambition as there can be. Nobody knows if and when it could be achieved.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Therein lies the problem for typical ML projects. By calling them “AI,” we convey that they sit on the same spectrum as AGI, that they&#39;re built on technology that is actively inching along in that direction. “AI” haunts ML. It invokes a grandiose narrative and pumps up expectations, selling real technology in unrealistic terms. This confuses decision-makers and dead-ends projects left and right.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;It&#39;s understandable that so many would want to claim a piece of the AI pie, if it&#39;s made of the same ingredients as AGI. The wish fulfillment AGI promises — a kind of ultimate power — is so seductive that it&#39;s nearly irresistible.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;But there&#39;s a better way forward, one that&#39;s realistic and that I would argue is already exciting enough: running major operations — the main things we do as organizations — more effectively! Most commercial ML projects aim to do just that. For them to succeed at a higher rate, we&#39;ve got to come down to earth. If your aim is to deliver operational value, don&#39;t buy “AI” and don&#39;t sell “AI.” Say what you mean and mean what you say. If a technology consists of ML, let&#39;s call it that.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Reports of the human mind&#39;s looming obsolescence have been greatly exaggerated, which means another era of AI disillusionment is nigh. And, in the long run, we will continue to experience AI winters so long as we continue to hyperbolically apply the term “AI.” But if we tone down the “AI” rhetoric — or otherwise differentiate ML from AI — we will properly insulate ML as an industry from the next AI Winter. This includes resisting the temptation to ride hype waves and refrain from passively affirming starry-eyed decision makers who appear to be bowing at the altar of an all-capable AI. Otherwise, the danger is clear and present: When the hype fades, the overselling is debunked, and winter arrives, much of ML&#39;s true value proposition will be unnecessarily disposed of along with the myths, like the baby with the bathwater.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;em>;This article is a product of the author&#39;s work as the Bodily Bicentennial Professor in Analytics at UVA Darden School of Business.&lt;/em>;&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Fri, 02 Jun 2023 20:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Why Every Modern Enterprise Organization Needs Insight-Driven Marketing - SPONSOR CONTENT FROM MELTWATER]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/sponsored/2023/06/why-every-modern-enterprise-organization-needs-insight-driven-marketing]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;html>; &lt;head>;&lt;/head>; &lt;body>; &lt;figure>; &lt;img aria-describedby=&quot;caption-attachment-356512&quot; src=&quot;/resources/images/article_assets/2023/04/HBR-Article-1200x675-1.jpg&quot; >; &lt;/figure>; &lt;p>;If there&#39;s one truth at the center of modern marketing, it&#39;s this one: Brands don&#39;t own the narrative anymore. Consumers do.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Once formulated around the boardroom table, brand perception is now in consumers&#39; hands as they turn to digital spaces to share their opinions, recommendations, and needs. In turn, the narratives that define brands are created through consumers&#39; conversations with one another, evolving by the second.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;At a time when consumers trust their peers most for advice and recommendations, one of the best investments executives can make is in understanding consumers better. This is where insight-driven marketing enters the strategic picture, bringing consumers&#39; needs to the forefront.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;The Need for Insight-Driven Marketing&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Consumer insights were once rare, based on static data harvested from time-intensive processes like surveys and polls. As billions of new posts are uploaded across the internet each day, organizations have countless opportunities to get to know their customers better. But almost overnight, brands have become overwhelmed with digital sources for much more dynamic insights. Between 60% and 73% of all data within an enterprise goes unused for analytics, according to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forrester.com/blogs/hadoop-is-datas-darling-for-a-reason/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;Forrester Consulting&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;To stay competitive and relevant, enterprises need advanced means of staying in step with consumer conversations across all channels and markets. This is why insight-driven marketing is so essential.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Using Artificial Intelligence, advanced data structuring, and other technology-forward capabilities, insight-driven marketing reveals direction in that chaos. It can give executives a deeper understanding of what truly matters to their audiences, which can then inform their business decisions.&lt;/p>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div id=&quot;DFP_IC_pos3&quot;>; &lt;script type=&quot;text/javascript&quot;>;if (isAdobeSync()) googletag.cmd.push(function() { googletag.display(&quot;DFP_IC_pos3&quot;); });&lt;/script>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;The Critical Role of AI in Insight-Driven Marketing&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Today, next-generation AI and large language models streamline the journey from data noise to actionable insights.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Natural language processing and visual analytics give marketers advanced tools for understanding brand narratives and perceptions in real time. AI-powered tools such as pattern detection algorithms and digital “assistants” are also enriching marketers&#39; contextual intelligence so they can better predict what will happen next.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;As AI continues to rapidly advance, there&#39;s never been a better time for organizations to embrace tech-forward solutions. With them, brands are equipped to future-proof their operations with capabilities like trendspotting, viral content forecasting, and predicting campaign returns on investment.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Solutions for Enterprise-Level Challenges&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The benefits of insight-driven marketing run parallel to business growth. Brands that do data-driven marketing at scale can increase net sales value by up to 5% and marketing efficiency by up to 20%, according to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mckinsey.com/capabilities/growth-marketing-and-sales/our-insights/the-new-marketing-model-for-growth-how-cpgs-can-crack-the-code&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;McKinsey &amp;amp; Company&lt;/a>;. Still, with added benefits come added responsibilities and increased chances for critical information to fall through the cracks.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Insight-driven marketing solutions give executives a holistic view of their consumer data sets across key elements of the business, including marketing, public relations, strategy, and research and development. However, all that information loses its potential utility without a system and a team for analyzing and delivering them to key stakeholders and decision makers.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;With so many potential knowledge dropout points to consider, large businesses require tailored solutions for successful insight-driven marketing. But only those solutions that combine tech-forward tools with premium services are geared to meet enterprise-level needs.&lt;/p>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div id=&quot;DFP_IC_pos4&quot;>; &lt;script type=&quot;text/javascript&quot;>;if (isAdobeSync()) googletag.cmd.push(function() { googletag.display(&quot;DFP_IC_pos4&quot;); });&lt;/script>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Real-World Results&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Numerous industry-leading brands are already winning in their markets by applying insight-driven marketing at scale, with transformative results.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Since 2016, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.meltwater.com/en/customer-stories/shiseido?utm_source=paid-3rd-party&amp;amp;utm_medium=hbr&amp;amp;utm_campaign=paid-3rd-party-hbr&amp;amp;utm_content=customer-story-demo-request&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;Shiseido&lt;/a>; has used a suite of enterprise-grade solutions to consolidate and optimize its international multi-brand social media operations. Bringing more than 200 users to one suite with unified data sets and a custom analytics dashboard gave Shiseido a single source of truth about its customers&#39; needs and perceptions. “We were able to create a globally consistent KPI framework that then made the shift from return on marketing objectives all the way to linking it to return on investment,” says Amit Naik, SVP, global head of analytics at Shiseido.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.meltwater.com/en/customer-stories/haleon&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;Haleon&lt;/a>; uses enterprise-grade social intelligence solutions to manage its portfolio of more than 25 owned brands, available in 170 markets. “Today, our brands are more competitive, as we provide them with insights no one else in the business can,” says Danny Gardner, social intelligence lead at Haleon. “And we do it fast.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;With globally aligned social intelligence, the benefits of insight-driven marketing reach across brands and teams. So even as Haleon&#39;s dental department sales team saw an 80% increase in consumer research efficiency, one of its ointment brands&#39; social media teams used insights to drive 272% year-over-year engagement growth at the same time.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Looking Ahead&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;As the most powerful force in brand management today, consumer conversations can inform business decisions at every organizational level. Only insight-driven marketing lets organizations center their customers&#39; voices at scale. And as the technology at its core advances, brands will gain ever-improving opportunities to understand their consumers.&lt;/p>; &lt;hr>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;&lt;em>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.meltwater.com/en/insights-driven-marketing?utm_source=paid-3rd-party&amp;amp;utm_medium=HBR&amp;amp;utm_campaign=paid-3rd-party-HBR&amp;amp;utm_content=demo-request&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;Learn how&lt;/a>; the Meltwater Enterprise Intelligence Suite helps organizations put customer voices at the center of their marketing.&lt;/em>;&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;hr>; &lt;p>;&lt;em>;Copyright Meltwater © 2023&amp;nbsp; &lt;/em>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;em>;The views reflected in this sponsored article are the views of the authors and do not necessarily reflect the views of the global Meltwater organization.&lt;/em>;&lt;/p>; &lt;/body>; &lt;/html>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 01 Jun 2023 22:25:02 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[CEOs Are Predicting a Mild Recession in the U.S.]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/ceos-are-predicting-a-mild-recession-in-the-u-s]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_01_5277457.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Jakub and Jedrzej Krzyszkowski/Stocksy&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;A recent survey of CEOs suggests that most expect a recession in the US but that it will be &amp;#8220;short and shallow.&amp;#8221; For that reason, many aren&amp;#8217;t anticipating layoffs and some are even still hiring. It points toward a continuation of the current tight labor market, even as the economy cools in response to the Federal Reserve&amp;#8217;s interest rate hikes and the ongoing banking turmoil.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/ceos-are-predicting-a-mild-recession-in-the-us?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/ceos-are-predicting-a-mild-recession-in-the-us?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;CEOs continue to send the same message about the US economy: A recession is looming but persistent strength in the labor market will endure. Typically, corporate executives would be focused on cutting costs and jobs amid such uncertain times, but they instead anticipate the job market will stay competitive. The seeming cognitive dissonance underlies the complexity of an economy that has suffered serial shocks in recent years — from the pandemic to inflation to rapid interest rate hikes to a mini banking crisis — but which nonetheless continues to exude signs of resilience.&lt;/span>;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335559739&amp;quot;:160,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:259}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.conference-board.org/topics/CEO-Confidence&quot;>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;The CEO confidence measure published by the Conference Boar&lt;/span>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;none&quot;>;d&lt;/span>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;, where I am chief economist, &lt;/span>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;reveals that for the fourth consecutive quarter the world&#39;s top executives overwhelmingly anticipate a US recession over the next 12 to 18 months. But they expect it will be short and shallow, with limited global spillover. An outsized 87% of CEOs envision this scenario, according to the survey&#39;s second quarter iteration, while only 6% anticipate a deep recession with global spillover, and just 7% expect no recession at all. CEOs&#39; general pessimism continues to weigh on the overall gauge of confidence, which at 43 is little better than the lows achieved during the worst of the pandemic. (The Conference Board Measure of CEO Confidence is a quarterly survey conducted of nearly 150 CEOs in partnership with The Business Council. Respondents are members of The Business Council and a reading below 50 reflects more negative than positive responses to the survey.)&lt;/span>;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335559739&amp;quot;:160,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:259}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;In past quarterly surveys, CEOs indicated that they expected that the Fed&#39;s anti-inflationary efforts would drive this brief and mild US economic downturn. CEOs continue to say they support the central bank&#39;s aggressive rate hikes this quarter, even amid clear expectations of recession and an ongoing banking crisis. Indeed, 82% of CEOs think inflation should be the driving force behind the Fed&#39;s monetary policy decisions. CEOs ranked other influences on Fed policy as being far less important, including the tight labor market (49%), banking stress and the potential for a credit crunch (43%), GDP growth (28%), and debt limit uncertainty (1%). Given that common gauges of consumer inflation hover well above the Fed&#39;s 2% target and the risk of elevated inflation expectations becoming embedded, this view makes sense. &lt;/span>;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335559739&amp;quot;:160,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:259}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;CEOs appear to be taking the lingering banking crisis in stride, and largely do not view it as likely to trigger a major recession, or even help cause one at all. Asked in the survey about different responses to the crisis, only 28% of CEOs say that they are increasing their own company&#39;s liquidity, and just 17% are altering banking relationships. Most CEOs are “examining relationships” as opposed to taking drastic measures to shield themselves from residual crisis fallout: 62% of CEOs are examining relationships with their banks, 28% are examining their own risk management, 33% are examining their customers&#39; liquidity adequacy, and 30% are examining their suppliers&#39; liquidity adequacy. &lt;/span>;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335559739&amp;quot;:160,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:259}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;The US economy&#39;s dour outlook notwithstanding, CEOs continue to believe that the labor market will defy expectations and remain largely afloat. Three sets of survey responses support this conclusion: First, only 20% of CEOs intend to reduce their workforce over the next 12 months. A surprising 33% expect to continue hiring and a sizable 46% anticipate no changes in staffing. Second, 75% of CEOs intend to raise wages by 3 percentage points or more over the next year and another 20% plan to raise wages by 1–3 percentage points over the same period. Meanwhile, a total of only 5% either anticipate no changes in wages (4%) or aim to cut wages (1%). Third, and finally, only 9% of CEOs expect no difficulty in hiring qualified workers, meaning 91% expect some or great difficulty.&lt;/span>;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335559739&amp;quot;:160,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:259}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335559739&amp;quot;:160,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:259}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;Labor shortages are the key difference between the outlook today versus prior downturns. Additionally, labor shortages are why CEOs anticipate the recession to be “short and shallow.” Missing workers, strict immigration policy, and, most critically, an aging workforce, are creating an acute shortage in the supply of workers even as demand is likely to ebb in some industries over the course of this year. While workers aged 25 through 64 have largely returned to the labor market post-pandemic, those 65 and older are quickly exiting, creating a dearth of employees with skills and experience.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335559739&amp;quot;:160,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:259}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;This backdrop makes CEOs&#39; responses somewhat easier to interpret, with CEOs falling into one of three camps. In the first camp, a significant share of CEOs are still hiring workers to fill roles vacated by retiring Baby Boomers. Those positions are most prevalent in industries requiring in-person work, including in health care, child- and elder-care, hotels, restaurants, and travel. &lt;/span>;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335559739&amp;quot;:160,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:259}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;In the second are the one-fifth of firms signaling layoffs. These are likely among the pandemic darlings that outperformed during the health crisis as demand surged for goods, technology, finance, and housing. They are being forced to right-size amid higher interest rates and as consumers are shifting their demand to services. These less fortunate areas include broad swaths of the tech sector, finance, real estate, construction, and transportation and warehousing.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335559739&amp;quot;:160,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:259}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;Most CEOs fall into the third camp and expect to make no changes to their workforces, as they anticipate a short and shallow recession, and prefer to hoard labor rather than release workers and rehire them at what will likely be a higher cost.&lt;/span>;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335559739&amp;quot;:160,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:259}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;This CEO behavior underscores the difficulty firms face in maintaining a skilled workforce even while staring into the maw of another recession. While they face less difficulty than a year ago, most firms still anticipate at least some difficulty hiring talented workers. Moreover, to both attract and retain talent, chief executives continue to view throwing money at the problem (in the form of higher wages and benefits) as the primary solution to this long-term issue. As raising wages and benefits indefinitely is unsustainable, many firms are turning to automation and digital transformation to fill the gap created by the constrained worker supply.&lt;/span>;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335559739&amp;quot;:160,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:259}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;So, do CEOs&#39; sentiments regarding recession and the labor force make sense?&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335559739&amp;quot;:160,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:259}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;Yes. Consumers also fear recession within the next six months but continue to give the labor market relatively high marks according to &lt;/span>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.conference-board.org/topics/consumer-confidence&quot;>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;none&quot;>;The Conference Board Consumer Confidence Survey&lt;/span>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;. Additionally, &lt;/span>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.conference-board.org/topics/us-leading-indicators&quot;>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;The Conference Board US Leading Economic Index&lt;/span>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>; has signaled recession in the US starting right about now for more than a year, yet the Current Economic Index remains buoyant due to strong labor market components. Even financial market pricing for Fed rate cuts to commence this year, despite stubborn inflation, suggests that investors expect recession. Nonetheless, that projected easing is comparatively minor, pointing to a short and shallow recession facilitated by continued labor shortage-related tightness in the labor market.&lt;/span>;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335559739&amp;quot;:160,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:259}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 01 Jun 2023 21:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[How to Keep Cyberattacks from Tanking Your Balance Sheet]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/how-to-keep-cyberattacks-from-tanking-your-balance-sheet]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_01_1387537769.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Javier Zayas Photography/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;The threat of cyberattacks &amp;#8212; and potential impact on corporate balance sheets &amp;#8212; is only expected to grow. Technological advances in areas such as generative AI and automation have strengthened threat actors, leading to&amp;#160;new and evolving threats. Against this backdrop, it becomes increasingly crucial for corporate boards to align their organizations&amp;#8217; cyber-risk management with their business needs. Cyberattacks are, first and foremost, a risk to a business&amp;#8217; integrity. They can damage the most fundamental components of a business, from the integrity of customer data to IT infrastructure, all while impacting the company&amp;#8217;s intellectual property, reputation, valuation, and even the morale of staff. How should board directors and senior leaders be managing this type of business risk? Knowledge brings power, and the more corporate leadership knows about the impact of cyber risk on the business, the better it can provide effective leadership.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/how-to-keep-cyberattacks-from-tanking-your-balance-sheet?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/how-to-keep-cyberattacks-from-tanking-your-balance-sheet?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;As a leader of a cybersecurity company, I have first-hand experience of the degree to which enterprises have been targeted by cyberattacks. We&#39;ve all seen recurrent headlines about ransomware; but enterprises are also facing distributed denial of service (DDoS) attacks, supply chain breaches, and phishing attacks, among others.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;According to a recent &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forrester.com/report/lessons-learned-from-the-worlds-biggest-data-breaches-and-privacy-abuses-2022/RES178936&quot;>;Forrester report&lt;/a>;, last year saw 1 billion records exposed in the top 35 breaches; $2.6 billion stolen in the top nine cryptocurrency breaches; and $2.7 billion in fines levied to the top 35 violators. Here are just a few examples:&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;Lapsus$ claimed to have stolen 1 terabyte of crucial data from semiconductor chip company &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cpomagazine.com/cyber-security/nvidia-data-leak-exposed-proprietary-information-but-wasnt-a-russian-ransomware-attack-company-says/&quot;>;Nvidia&lt;/a>;. They demanded a $1 million &lt;strong>;ransom&lt;/strong>; and made additional demands.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://cloud.google.com/blog/products/identity-security/how-google-cloud-blocked-largest-layer-7-ddos-attack-at-46-million-rps&quot;>;Google&lt;/a>; stifled a &lt;strong>;DDoS&lt;/strong>; attack on a Google Cloud Armor customer, comparing it to “receiving all the daily requests to Wikipedia (one of the top-trafficked websites) in just 10 seconds.”&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Company shares plunged when authentication company &lt;a href=&quot;https://techcrunch.com/2022/03/23/okta-breach-sykes-sitel/&quot;>;Okta&lt;/a>; announced that records of around 2.5% of its customer base were exposed in a &lt;strong>;supply chain attack.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;A new high was recorded for &lt;strong>;phishing&lt;/strong>;, with more than 1,270,00 attacks recorded in the third quarter of 2022 alone, according to the &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.apwg.org/reports/apwg_trends_report_q3_2022.pdf&quot;>;Anti-Phishing Working Group&lt;/a>;.&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;The Cost of a Data Breach&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;The average cost of a data breach reached $4.35 million in 2022, according to IBM&#39;s &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ibm.com/downloads/cas/3R8N1DZJ&quot;>;Cost of a Data Breach Report 2022&lt;/a>;, which represents a 2.6% increase from 2021, and a 12.7% increase from 2020.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;For ransomware, costs are different: The average payment in 2021 was approximately $1.85 million — more than double the $760,000 figure from 2020, per a &lt;a href=&quot;https://f.hubspotusercontent20.net/hubfs/3791228/2021-Ransomware-Defense-Report_SpyCloud.pdf&quot;>;SpyCloud report&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;And these are just direct costs; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/05/the-devastating-business-impacts-of-a-cyber-breach&quot;>;indirect costs are greater&lt;/a>;. They include:&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;Lost business, due to business disruption and revenue losses&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Lost customers, and the cost of acquiring new ones&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Reputation losses, and diminished goodwill&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Regulatory fines and legal proceedings, when attacks lead to class-action lawsuits&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Cyber Threats Are Growing&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Rising geopolitical tensions, particularly around the Russia-Ukraine conflict and US-China relations, created a knock-on effect in which state-sponsored cyber warfare is impacting the private sector. Bottom line: Enterprises often become collateral damage.&lt;/p>; &lt;article-promo>; &lt;hbr-component type=&quot;promo&quot; is-insight=&quot;insight-center&quot; title=&quot;Managing Cyber Risk&quot; dek=&quot;Exploring the challenges and the solutions.&quot; cta-text=&quot;&quot; href=&quot;/insight-center/managing-cyber-risk&quot;>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/insight-center/managing-cyber-risk&quot; style=&quot;color:black;text-decoration:none&quot;>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; Insight Center Collection &lt;/div>; &lt;h3>;Managing Cyber Risk&lt;/h3>; &lt;div>; Exploring the challenges and the solutions. &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hbr-component>; &lt;/article-promo>; &lt;p>;The threat of cyberattacks — and potential impact on corporate balance sheets — is only expected to grow. Technological advances in areas such as generative AI and automation have strengthened threat actors, leading to &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/04/cyber-risk-is-growing-heres-how-companies-can-keep-up&quot;>;new and evolving threats&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Against this backdrop, it becomes increasingly crucial for corporate boards to align their organizations&#39; cyber-risk management with their business needs.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Cybersecurity as a Key Business Risk&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Cyberattacks are, first and foremost, a risk to a business&#39; integrity. They can damage the most fundamental components of a business, from the integrity of customer data to IT infrastructure, all while impacting the company&#39;s intellectual property, reputation, valuation, and even the morale of staff.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;How should board directors and senior leaders be managing this type of business risk? Knowledge brings power, and the more corporate leadership knows about the impact of cyber risk on the business, the better it can provide effective leadership.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Cyber-Risk Balance Sheets Can Provide Insight&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;According to the World Economic Forum&#39;s report, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www3.weforum.org/docs/WEF_Cyber_Risk_Corporate_Governance_2021.pdf&quot;>;Principles for Board Governance of Cyber Risk&lt;/a>;, 37% of organizations strongly agree that quantifying risk leads to better management of cyber risks. But what&#39;s the best way to quantify risks?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;A cyber-risk balance sheet is one way of mapping the potential financial impact of cyber events. Creating a balance sheet involves:&lt;/p>; &lt;ol>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Standardization:&lt;/strong>; Selecting a cyber risk quantification framework, for example, by leveraging &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fairinstitute.org/&quot;>;Factor Analysis of Information Risk&lt;/a>; (FAIR), an international standard quantitative model framework providing operational risk and information security&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Prioritization: &lt;/strong>;Defining an organization&#39;s top cyber threats and quantifying the likelihood of these threats&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Mapping:&lt;/strong>; Connecting the probability of cyber threats to cyber risks in financial terms and associating them with future cyber investments&lt;/li>; &lt;/ol>; &lt;p>;This creates a ledger that can be used by chief information security officers (CISOs) to describe the business case for cybersecurity efforts that show a positive return on investment.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;How Corporate Boards Should Manage Cyber Risk&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www3.weforum.org/docs/WEF_Cyber_Risk_Corporate_Governance_2021.pdf&quot;>;Principles for Board Governance of Cyber Risk&lt;/a>; introduces six principles for boards to begin with:&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Understand that cybersecurity is a strategic business enabler&lt;/strong>;: Enterprises should analyze cybersecurity in the context of strategic implications, as part of enterprise risk.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Understand the economic drivers and impacts of cyber risk&lt;/strong>;: Enterprises should define cyber-risk appetite in financial terms to help inform decision-making.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Align cyber-risk management with business needs&lt;/strong>;: Management should integrate cyber-risk analysis into business decisions.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Ensure organizational design supports cybersecurity&lt;/strong>;: Management should ensure the cybersecurity function is represented adequately.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Incorporate cybersecurity expertise into board governance&lt;/strong>;: Regular sessions between management and the board should provide updates on incidents, trends, and vulnerabilities.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Encourage systemic resilience&lt;/strong>;: Board should ensure that management has plans to improve resilience through collaboration with the public sector.&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Finding the Right Balance – From a Business Perspective&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Boards need an in-depth understanding of top risks facing the enterprise and should be able to quantify their potential impact. Decisions about cost investments can then be weighed against the potential cost of &lt;em>;not&lt;/em>; taking action.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;By aligning cyber-risk management with business needs, organizations can build a security profile that aligns with the defined risk appetite. This process requires encouraging collaboration between the CISO, the chief technology officer, and chief information officer functions, all of whom should be involved in analyzing each cyber scenario.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Through this approach, the board can ask to see real risk reduction. In parallel, security leaders can create allies within business units by helping them reduce the risk of business impact.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Mapping Out the “Crown Jewels”&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;The first step in cyber-risk management involves prioritizing where to home in. Organizations can leverage an industry framework like the &lt;a href=&quot;https://attack.mitre.org/&quot;>;MITRE ATT&amp;amp;CK&lt;/a>; to provide insight into blind spots through consolidated threat visibility. MITRE provides a foundation for security operations teams to develop and map out a framework for detection rules, which are specific to the unique threats and vulnerabilities of an organization.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Frameworks like MITRE make it possible to &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.cyberproof.com/blog/creating-a-smarter-soc-with-the-mitre-attck-framework&quot;>;improve threat coverage and response&lt;/a>; by looking at parameters like industry, geolocation, and leadership. With MITRE, organizations can identify which threats, as well as which aspects of the technology landscape, are most likely to lead to damage. By using MITRE to map out key business assets, a customized plan for reducing business risk can be developed.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Lowering Costs &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Given the impact of the macroeconomic downturn, the biggest question many senior executives are facing is how to maintain effective cybersecurity with more limited resources. That&#39;s where automation and artificial intelligence (AI) come in, as they have the potential to lower the expense of mitigating risk.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;According to IBM&#39;s &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ibm.com/reports/data-breach&quot;>;2022 Cost of a Data Breach&lt;/a>;, organizations deploying AI and automation incurred $3 million less, on average, in breach costs. AI was their biggest cost saver; those deploying AI and automation detected breaches faster, minimizing the impact on operations. Another strategy for cutting costs involves advanced cloud solutions that save dramatically on data ingestion and storage costs.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Start by Getting the Right Talent &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;To pull all of this off, organizations need to have the right talent in place. But that&#39;s easier said than done. To put it simply: There are more cybersecurity jobs than the number of available professionals. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.isc2.org/-/media/ISC2/Research/2022-WorkForce-Study/ISC2-Cybersecurity-Workforce-Study.ashx&quot;>;According to the (ISC)&lt;sup>;2&lt;/sup>;&lt;/a>;, the cybersecurity workforce grew to 4.7 million people in 2022, the highest number of workers ever recorded. Yet more than 3.4 million positions still remained open. This is a stark situation.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Managed Detection and Response (MDR) can address the lack of available talent. MDR providers are outsourced services that can provide organizations with advanced security operations capabilities and work collaboratively with those organizations to remediate threats once they are discovered. They offer access to top professionals who provide input regarding roadmap-related decisions, and who can handle existing, new, and evolving threats. Enterprises find that an advanced MDR service provider makes it possible to do more with less — maintaining scalability while keeping head count down.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In the current climate, MDR providers are increasingly relevant. It&#39;s not just about resources and how to use them, but also about how to build a roadmap moving forward. Shifting focus to evaluate cybersecurity as a business risk — while investing efforts specifically on the threats that pose the greatest danger — can help ensure that an enterprise is poised to detect and respond quickly enough to protect the organization&#39;s key assets. And that&#39;s the real goal.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;With the ever-growing threat of cyber attack, business leaders should be thinking about cybersecurity as a strategic business enabler. By illustrating the business case for cybersecurity — aligning cyber-risk management with an organization&#39;s business objectives — it becomes possible to make current and future decisions about the organization&#39;s cyber health in terms that the board can understand.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 01 Jun 2023 20:55:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[When Blind Hiring Advances DEI &mdash; and When It Doesn&rsquo;t]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/when-blind-hiring-advances-dei-and-when-it-doesnt]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_01_539661201.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;jenniholma/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;As a decision-making strategy, &amp;#8220;blind hiring&amp;#8221; involves blocking evaluators from receiving potentially biasing information about a job candidate until after an evaluation of their application materials are complete. Most famously, the tactic was used to boost the hiring of women in orchestras by having people audition from behind a screen that concealed their gender. But there&amp;#8217;sa body of research that&amp;#8217;s been conducted since that 2000 study showing that, while the strategy is generally effective, there are situations in which it might not help you diversify your candidate pool. The author outlines this research, and suggests three questions you should ask in order to get the most out of a blind hiring approach.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/when-blind-hiring-advances-dei-and-when-it-doesnt?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/when-blind-hiring-advances-dei-and-when-it-doesnt?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Inspired by the results of the famous &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.aeaweb.org/articles?id=10.1257%2Faer.90.4.715&amp;amp;source=post_page-----deda93da109b----------------------&quot;>;orchestra study&lt;/a>; — where symphony orchestras began hiring more women by having people audition from behind a screen that concealed their gender — some major &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.hrmagazine.co.uk/content/news/bbc-embraces-blind-recruitment/&quot;>;organizations&lt;/a>; are now using a “blind hiring” strategy to help achieve goals related to diversity. The typical blind hiring process involves stripping information from job application materials before review that could signal applicants&#39; memberships in specific groups and cue discrimination. Though not yet widespread, this de-biasing strategy is gaining traction: A recent &lt;a href=&quot;https://papers.ssrn.com/sol3/papers.cfm?abstract_id=3768039&quot;>;survey&lt;/a>; of over 800 US-based HR practitioners indicated that about 20% worked for organizations that used blind hiring and about 60% were familiar with it.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;What many practitioners may be unaware of, however, is the large span of new research on blind hiring that has been published since that orchestra study in 2000. Over the past two decades, the efficacy of blind hiring as a strategy to boost hiring outcomes for members of historically disadvantaged groups has been tested in the “field” — that is, in real hiring decisions in real organizations — in various settings across Europe, Canada, and the US By understanding the results of these recent studies, decision-makers in organizations can now determine, at a very granular level, whether a blind hiring strategy is likely to help or hinder their organizations&#39; efforts to diversify pools of new hires.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;What Is “Blind Hiring”?&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;As a decision-making strategy more broadly, “blinding” involves blocking evaluators from receiving potentially biasing information about a target of evaluation until after an evaluation is complete. Blind hiring policies typically implement this strategy at the initial screening stage of the hiring pipeline, when hiring managers or other decision-makers decide which applicants to interview and which to screen out of the pool.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Organizations using blind hiring policies single out information conveyed in job application materials like resumes and application forms that is irrelevant to the job but could cue unconscious biases in managers. They then strip that information from materials before they are reviewed. Names, for instance, communicate nothing about people&#39;s skills but often communicate their gender and/or race; receiving this information can lead decision-makers to unconsciously favor applicants of certain groups, like &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.aeaweb.org/articles?id=10.1257/0002828042002561&quot;>;white people&lt;/a>;. Thus, an organization concerned about this type of discrimination might use a blind hiring approach, removing applicants&#39; names from their materials before letting managers see them. Other types of information, like college graduation years (which communicate age) or hobbies (which can signal social class), are similarly candidates for blinding.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The logic underlying a blind hiring approach is simple: Discrimination against members of certain groups cannot occur at a given hiring stage if evaluators at that stage cannot discern applicants&#39; group memberships. Accordingly, decision-makers tasked with increasing the diversity of new sets of hires in their organizations may wonder whether a blind hiring approach could help them achieve that goal.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;The State of the Science&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Over roughly the past two decades, careful academic studies exploring the efficacy of a blind hiring approach have been undertaken across Europe, Canada, and the US In these studies, researchers have compared the proportions of job applicants from disadvantaged groups who are selected for interviews — at organizations in both the public and private sectors — when application materials are blinded or evaluated in the normal fashion. Generally (but not entirely), these studies have found that more applicants from disadvantaged groups advance to the interview stage when a blind hiring approach is used.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In &lt;a href=&quot;https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/pdf/10.1177/001979391206500105?casa_token=35AgNww0QpQAAAAA:KFt0QpS6nXTiWIIlbs86EhzSAjQV4DzCI_1imLlSF8bEZIWVfEuMGWvi2L-tKUewcqiDqXeDC0g&quot;>;one study&lt;/a>; in the public sector in Sweden, researchers found that more women and ethnic minorities were selected for interviews when their applications were anonymized versus when names were maintained. Another &lt;a href=&quot;https://econpapers.repec.org/paper/hhsifauwp/2006_5F004.htm&quot;>;study&lt;/a>; in the Swedish public sector found that women who uploaded their credential information to a database used by potential employers were more likely to receive interview invites when their gender information was blinded. And in the Netherlands, researchers &lt;a href=&quot;https://mpra.ub.uni-muenchen.de/33332/&quot;>;found&lt;/a>; that people of non-Western origin, who represent a traditionally disadvantaged, Dutch job-seeker group, were more likely to be advanced to interviews for public sector jobs when application materials were evaluated in a blind fashion.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Across the Atlantic, a comprehensive &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.canada.ca/en/public-service-commission/services/publications/Name-blind-recruitment-pilot-project.html&quot;>;study&lt;/a>; by the Canadian government explored whether blinding information, including applicants&#39; names and also their citizenships, addresses, educational institutions, and religions, would impact interview selection rates for minority applicants to the public service. Results indicated that, while non-minority applicants were selected for interviews at a slightly higher rate than minority applicants under the traditional process, minority applicants were selected at a higher rate under the blind process. And in the US, a &lt;a href=&quot;https://jhr.uwpress.org/content/early/2021/08/31/jhr.0420-10831R1.abstract?casa_token=uu28ASzExNgAAAAA:Jqi4OO6HVJrJEuaKKJjv697-9xYg4EhfkaLPbXyGiWMQD0FUa1cgC2qa02zN2__16fSXRfk&quot;>;study&lt;/a>; in a restaurant chain indicated that older workers were more likely to be advanced to the interview stage when they submitted applications online, which blinded applicants&#39; ages.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Some studies, however, have been less positive on the effects of blind hiring. For instance, employers in France were &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.aeaweb.org/articles?id=10.1257/app.20140185&quot;>;less likely&lt;/a>; to select applicants from minority social groups for interviews when applicants&#39; names were blinded versus when they were provided on materials. Consistent with this finding, a &lt;a href=&quot;https://izajoels.springeropen.com/articles/10.1186/2193-9012-1-5&quot;>;large study&lt;/a>; in Germany found that blind hiring only boosted interview rates for job applicants from minority groups when employers tended to discriminate &lt;em>;against&lt;/em>; applicants from those groups under a traditional process. For employers who were &lt;em>;more &lt;/em>;likely to interview applicants from minority groups under a traditional process, however, the use of a blind hiring policy negated that tendency, leading to worse interview selection rates for applicants from minority groups.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Viewed together, these recent studies suggest that a blind hiring process often helps, but may sometimes hinder, organizations&#39; goals related to diversity. Informed by these findings, decision-makers should ask themselves three questions to understand whether a blind hiring policy is right for them.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Question 1: Does my organization systematically under-select applicants from traditionally disadvantaged groups for interviews?&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Research suggests that blind hiring only boosts interview rates for members of traditionally disadvantaged groups when used by companies that typically under-select applicants from these groups for interviews. This makes sense intuitively — blind hiring will only help if there is bias to eliminate. Thus, if decision-makers are operating in organizations that are failing to diversify pools of new hires overall but are &lt;em>;succeeding &lt;/em>;at diversifying pools of interviewees, adoption of a blind hiring policy to govern the initial screening stage will not help diversity hiring efforts. Instead, they should focus on solutions that address biases during interviews and selection decisions afterward.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Conversely, in organizations that have a history of selecting mostly members of advantaged social groups (eg, men, white people) for interviews, using blind hiring at the initial screening stage could help.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Question 2: Is the job in question one where being from an advantaged group predicts having the preferred credentials?&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Blind hiring blocks unconscious biases by ensuring that decisions about whom to interview are based on credentials alone. However, due to systematic inequities in access to resources and opportunities between groups in society, members of traditionally advantaged groups are &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nytimes.com/2023/04/05/business/tech-internship-application-grind.html&quot;>;disproportionately likely&lt;/a>; to attend prestigious undergraduate universities, secure sought-after internships, and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.equityinhighered.org/indicators/enrollment-in-graduate-education/&quot;>;achieve a post-graduate&lt;/a>; &lt;a href=&quot;https://news.nau.edu/stem-graduate-programs/&quot;>;(eg, master&#39;s) degree&lt;/a>;. Thus, if the job being hired for is one where people with fancy credentials are especially likely to be selected for interviews — for example, a management position — members of advantaged groups may still have a leg-up under a blind hiring process, even though discrimination is seemingly blocked.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In these cases, adopting a blind hiring policy to support diversity hiring goals may backfire. Instead, decision-makers might consider either broadening the span of “preferred” credentials for a position, or incorporating applicants&#39; social identities into interview decisions, so that complicated credentials can be evaluated through the lens of the hurdles — or privileges — applicants may have experienced along the way to achieving them.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Conversely, if interview decisions are based less on having fancy credentials and more on straightforward evaluations of relevant skills and experience — for instance, if the job being hired for is an entry-level position — the discrimination-blocking benefits of blind hiring will likely lead to greater interview rates for members of disadvantaged groups.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Question 3: Are complementary de-biasing strategies being used at other stops along the hiring pipeline?&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Say you have a job where, in the past, members of disadvantaged groups have been under-selected for interviews, and group membership doesn&#39;t predict applicants&#39; likelihood of having the “right” credentials. This job would clear the hurdles in questions one and two and could seem like a good match for a blind hiring approach. Even in this situation, however, a blind hiring approach on its own might not lead to more diversity in the ultimate pool of hires. Blind hiring can only be fully leveraged at the initial screening stage if paired with other de-biasing strategies operating before and after initial screens.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;One complementary strategy that should be paired with a blind hiring approach is targeted recruitment of members of disadvantaged groups, such as through &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nytimes.com/2023/04/05/technology/bowie-hbcu-tech-intern-pipeline.html?smid=nytcore-ios-share&amp;amp;referringSource=articleShare&quot;>;pipeline programs&lt;/a>; at HBCUs. This strategy pairing addresses the fact that discrimination reduction in interview-selection decisions may not boost the diversity of interviewee pools if few members of disadvantaged groups apply in the first place. Blind hiring policies should also be paired with de-biasing strategies at the interview stage, since interviews are generally conducted in an unblind fashion. Indeed, in some of the studies described above, blind hiring boosted interview selection rates for members of disadvantaged groups but did not ultimately increase their likelihood of getting job offers after interviews. One especially promising strategy to reduce discrimination at the interview stage involves the use of &lt;a href=&quot;https://outsmartingimplicitbias.org/module/how-to-conduct-a-structured-interview/&quot;>;structured&lt;/a>; &lt;a href=&quot;https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/full/10.1111/j.1744-6570.2010.01172.x?casa_token=S_r9YqxRcY4AAAAA%3AWx8fD3stmGZi6u7rR5qPoF_fOm7GcbnD1LA01LgbujFdU9fYQsmlfaF56jTSLcZ1kI9J8TFZPhKs&quot;>;interviewing&lt;/a>;, which keeps interviewers focused on job-related questions only and reduces the impact of homophily — our natural preference for people who are like us — on interview assessments.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;By asking themselves these three questions, decision-makers can determine whether a blind hiring approach to the initial screening process will help or hinder their efforts related to diversity in hiring overall. And even for those organizations that do not clear these hurdles, a blind hiring approach can still be leveraged if modified carefully. For instance, an organization might still wish to use a blind hiring strategy even though the job being hired for is one where being from an advantaged group predicts having the “target” credentials, like a graduate degree or an Ivy League pedigree (question two). In this case, organizations can consider using a “blind-then-see” approach — hiring managers can form initial evaluations of applicants based on credentials alone, then learn information that was blinded, like demographics, and re-weight their initial appraisals, re-considering applicants&#39; credentials through the lens of the hurdles they may have had to overcome to achieve them. Research &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S074959782200019X?casa_token=sAnj-BiCRNEAAAAA:DbKnwX-iAfWyJnBptZ19wJz2XUY-jimlLc7aQMUufGF9QeS34RY_zCQJlqLWxiatBc7AVkul&quot;>;suggests&lt;/a>; that a blind-then-see approach like this can reduce bias in favor of members of advantaged groups while still preserving the benefits of a blind, initial look at qualifications.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3 style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;. . .&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;The key takeaway is that blind hiring is not a one-size-fits-all solution. In some cases, it may even be detrimental when it comes to goals related to hiring more applicants from disadvantaged groups. However, the state of the science surrounding blind hiring suggests that, for the right jobs in the right organizations, this strategy can open the door to the achievement of diversity-related hiring goals.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;br>;&lt;hr>;&lt;div>;获取更多RSS：&lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.net&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.net&lt;/a>; &lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.best&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.best&lt;/a>;&lt;br>;&lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 01 Jun 2023 20:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[4 Actions CEOs Should Be Taking to Drive Growth With Their Ecosystem Strategy - SPONSOR CONTENT FROM EY-PARTHENON]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/sponsored/2023/05/4-actions-ceos-should-be-taking-to-drive-growth-with-their-ecosystem-strategy]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;html>; &lt;head>;&lt;/head>; &lt;body>; &lt;figure>; &lt;img aria-describedby=&quot;caption-attachment-353332&quot; src=&quot;/resources/images/article_assets/2023/03/EY_230625_HERO.png&quot; >; &lt;/figure>; &lt;p>;&lt;em>;By Jeff Wray and Greg Sarafin&lt;/em>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;To retain market leadership, CEOs seeking to accelerate innovation in their organizations often find themselves at a crossroads: They must decide whether to build, buy, or partner. In response, a growing number of CEOs are embracing ecosystem business models—and with good reason.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Ecosystems make up an average of 13.7% of the annual revenue of organizations using at least one ecosystem business model, according to a recent EY study, as well as driving 12.9% in cost reduction and generating 13.3% in incremental earnings. Beyond the numbers, ecosystems offer organizations clear benefits, such as greater access to technical capabilities talent and assets.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Despite these benefits, however, ecosystem business models can be contractually, logistically, and commercially complex, with structures that are often unclear to new participants. These challenges multiply for CEOs who are uncomfortable being in a partnership arrangement where they can&#39;t be in the driver&#39;s seat.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The real questions CEOs should ask themselves are:&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;Are we ready for a mindset change?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Can we cede control, trusting our partners within a defined ecosystem business model?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Are we prepared to share the limelight to gain the greater benefits of a united value proposition?&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Many types of ecosystems&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div id=&quot;DFP_IC_pos3&quot;>; &lt;script type=&quot;text/javascript&quot;>;if (isAdobeSync()) googletag.cmd.push(function() { googletag.display(&quot;DFP_IC_pos3&quot;); });&lt;/script>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Organizations looking to access new growth opportunities with an ecosystem approach, as opposed to building it themselves or buying a company, need to identify the “right” ecosystem with the right arrangements and the right participants for the business goals they are trying to achieve.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Three of the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ey.com/en_gl/alliances/seven-business-models-for-creating-ecosystem-value&quot;>;seven business models for creating ecosystem value&lt;/a>; are orchestrated marketplaces of large tech companies; setups that allow competitors with differing footprints to join forces, such as airline-loyalty alliances; and value-chain integration, such as Insurwave, a blockchain-based shipping insurance ecosystem built in conjunction with the EY organization and other collaborators.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;The benefits of ecosystems&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Building, buying, and partnering are not necessarily mutually exclusive. Ecosystems are powerful for organizations testing new waters, as they offer a comparatively safe environment for experimentation with limited financial commitments. Organizations can also use ecosystems as a pipeline-development strategy in tandem with mergers and acquisitions.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Ecosystems are about more than just growing revenues by accessing new growth opportunities. They allow firms to grow their multiples due to the capital- and cost-efficient way they access these opportunities using the expertise of their ecosystem partners. Ecosystems generated incremental earnings of ~12.9% and enabled cost reduction of ~12.9%, according to the EY Ecosystem study.&lt;/p>; &lt;figure>; &lt;img aria-describedby=&quot;caption-attachment-353333&quot; src=&quot;/resources/images/article_assets/2023/03/Chart-1-copy.png&quot; >; &lt;/figure>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Barriers to an ecosystem mindset&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Despite their intent, some organizations struggle to understand how to use ecosystems to drive growth. The struggle stems from a narrow understanding of what an ecosystem “should” look like, based on preexisting industry norms, when the organization has already tested the obvious options and found and implemented the most promising variants.&lt;/p>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div id=&quot;DFP_IC_pos4&quot;>; &lt;script type=&quot;text/javascript&quot;>;if (isAdobeSync()) googletag.cmd.push(function() { googletag.display(&quot;DFP_IC_pos4&quot;); });&lt;/script>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;However, to stay ahead of the innovation curve, firms need to look at options they have not explored. Companies need to think bigger and bolder by looking at all seven ecosystem models, not just at those they are most familiar with. Each organization needs to investigate which one is best suited, based on the desired business outcome.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In addition, organizations need to shift their focus to concentrate on the logic and governance of the ecosystem they are orchestrating or participating in, instead of just thinking about finding the right partner.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In sports, a winning team is not necessarily a set of the best players, but of those who work well together on a defined game plan to reach a common goal. Most teams require a captain—an orchestrator. The rest of the team play vital roles, but they adhere to the common standards defined by the orchestrator.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This approach—where an orchestrator sets the common standards, but the niche roles are enacted by the rest of the team—can make sense when firms with niche capabilities are accessing new areas of growth, or where they and their competitors are both aiming to orchestrate ecosystems but clients are keen on avoiding overreliance on a single supplier.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In this scenario, CEOs need to ask themselves, “If I can&#39;t drive it, am I willing to take a back seat to access the growth I see in this new opportunity?”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Implications and next steps&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;To make the most of ecosystem opportunities, CEOs and C-suite leaders should consider the following steps:&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;Take a conscious look at the alliances and partnerships you and your competitors are a part of. Identify any patterns and ask if your organization is sticking to the mold that&#39;s most prevalent in your industry—or if you have explored the art of the possible in the ecosystem strategy.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Ask yourself, “Am I just taking smaller comfortable steps that are close to my core business, or am I ready to take the leap of faith for broader growth opportunities?” When thinking about growth strategy, expand your horizons. Rethink how you have been considering your strategy and whether to pivot.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Revisit growth priorities you may have discarded. Were they set aside because they couldn&#39;t be unlocked with your current value chain structure? Can a suitable ecosystem change that?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Learn to let go! Embrace the opportunity to enter attractive new growth vectors where your organization might not be best placed to lead the charge on its own but can make a valuable contribution to a broader value proposition.&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;hr>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;&lt;em>;Learn more about how EY teams can help your organization master its ecosystem strategy.&lt;/em>;&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;hr>; &lt;p>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ey.com/en_gl/people/jeff-wray&quot;>;&lt;strong>;&lt;em>;Jeff Wray&lt;/em>;&lt;/strong>;&lt;/a>;&lt;strong>;&lt;em>; is Global EY-Parthenon Leader. &lt;/em>;&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ey.com/en_gl/people/greg-sarafin&quot;>;&lt;strong>;&lt;em>;Greg Sarafin&lt;/em>;&lt;/strong>;&lt;/a>;&lt;strong>;&lt;em>; is EY Global Alliance and Ecosystem Leader.&lt;/em>;&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;hr>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;&lt;em>;Additional contributors: &lt;/em>;&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;&lt;em>;Andrew Hearn, EY Global Development Leader, Strategy and Transactions; Prachi Gupta&lt;/em>;&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;/body>; &lt;/html>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 01 Jun 2023 00:25:03 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>