<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>路透社</title><description>路透社全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link/> http://reuters.com <item><title><![CDATA[Analysis: Fever over BlackRock“s bitcoin fund faces chill of rate hikes and regulations]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://reuters.com/article/fintech-crypto-bitcoin/analysis-fever-over-blackrocks-bitcoin-fund-faces-chill-of-rate-hikes-and-regulations-idUSKBN2YC0U6]]><description> &lt;div>;&lt;i>;2023-06-26T12:39:25Z&lt;/i>;&lt;/div>;&lt;p>;贝莱德的比特币基金计划帮助推动全球最大的加密货币达到一年来的最高水平，但利率不断上升分析师和业内人士表示，监管打击可能会扼杀涨势。&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;比特币上涨超过 15% &lt;a href=&quot;/technology/bitcoin-hits-1-year-high-amid-blackrock -etf-excitement-2023-06-23/&quot;>;上周&lt;/a>;，自 4 月份以来首次突破 30,000 美元，是 3 月份以来表现最好的一周，这在很大程度上是由贝莱德推动的&lt;a href=&quot;https:/ /www.reuters.com/companies/BLK.N/&quot;target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;(BLK.N)&lt;/a>; &lt;a href=&quot;/business/finance/blackrock-close-filing-bitcoin-etf-coindesk -2023-06-15/&quot;>;向美国证券交易委员会提交申请&lt;/a>;，推出由比特币支持的交易所交易基金 (ETF)。&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;如果获得批准，将推出比特币 ETF来自全球最大资产管理公司的投资可能会吸引不愿直接购买这种高风险加密货币的投资者。&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;在发生一系列重大金融危机后，今年该行业受到了投资者信心丧失和监管审查加强的打击。 2022 年的加密货币公司让投资者蒙受了损失。&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;在市场&lt;a href=&quot;/technology/whats-behind-bitcoins-latest-surge-2023-03-22/&quot;>;受情绪驱动&lt; /a>;，&lt;a href=&quot;/markets/us/bitcoin-could-hit-100000-by-end-2024-standard-chartered-says-2023-04-24/&quot;>;天价估值预测&lt;/ a>; 加密行业将贝莱德的申请视为华尔街转向比特币的标志，这并不罕见，而由 Citadel 证券、富达投资和嘉信理财支持的加密货币交易所的推出也强化了这一观点。&lt;/p>;&lt;p但分析师表示，经济压力可能会阻碍持续反弹的希望。临近周末，比特币涨势放缓，周一交易价格为 30,405 美元。&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;“粘性通胀和经济衰退担忧仍然是我们必须谨慎对待的长期风险，”Youwei 表示比特币矿商 BTCM 首席经济学家杨。&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;“从我们的角度来看，根据与卖方部门的对话，这次反弹是由机构买家主导的，”比特币矿商 BTCM 交易和运营主管韦斯·汉森 (Wes Hansen) 表示。加密货币对冲基金 Arca。&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;在加密货币经纪商 Genesis Trading，销售和交易董事总经理戈登·格兰特 (Gordon Grant) 表示，在贝莱德提交文件后，“数十名”顶级客户增加了对比特币的投资。&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;格兰特补充道，在今年早些时候美国加密货币贷款机构 Signature、Silvergate 和硅谷银行倒闭后，现货比特币 ETF 可以重建投资者对将美元转入和转出加密货币的能力的信心。 .&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;“市场现在正在定价将大量法定货币（如果有意愿的话）投入比特币的能力，这是一个重大的发展。”&lt;/p>;&lt; p>;加密衍生品交易所 Deribit 首席商务官 Luuk Strijers 表示，他看到看涨期权购买量显着增加，指出“看涨势头”。&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;当然，美国证券交易委员会尚未批准贝莱德的申请，但迄今为止，贝莱德已经拒绝了富达和芝加哥期权交易所全球市场等公司提出的追踪比特币的 ETF。美国证券交易委员会 (SEC) 提到了对&lt;a href=&quot;/business/us-sec-disapproves-propose-rule-list-trade-shares-vaneck-bitcoin-trust-2021-11-12/&quot;>;市场操纵&lt;/a>;的担忧在此类产品中。数字资产管理公司 &lt;a href=&quot;/markets/us/us-sec-rejects-grayscales-spot-bitcoin-etf-application-2022-06-30/&quot;>;Grayscale&lt;/a>; 提出了现货比特币 ETF 的提案研究分析师 Riyad Carey 表示：“在之前的现货 ETF 拒绝中，美国证券交易委员会提到了对市场操纵的担忧，而贝莱德的申请似乎采取了不同的方法来解决这一症结。” &lt;/p>;&lt;p>;在澳大利亚和加拿大意外加息之后，以及美联储的预测&lt;a href=&quot;/markets/us/fed-poished-punt-rate-hike-into-summer-wind -2023-06-14/&quot;>;再加息两次&lt;/a>;，投资者现在押注利率将保持不变&lt;a href=&quot;/markets/global-markets-wrapup-1-2023-06-23/&quot;>;长期走高&lt;/a>;。&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;比特币受益于超低利率，这激励投资者为了寻求回报而进行风险更高的押注。&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;Genesis Trading 的 Gordon Grant 表示走高利率意味着投资者可以获得其他资产的回报。&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;“名义上，大量流动性已从系统中撤出......总体资本减少了，不仅如此，现金现在不再是垃圾。”&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;尽管比特币已从去年的低点 15,479 美元反弹，但其交易价格仍不到 2021 年底达到的历史高点 69,000 美元的一半。&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;分析师表示监管不确定性也压低了价格，因为 SEC 越来越严厉地打击其认为的&lt;a href=&quot;/technology/sec-enforcement-chief-rejects-criticism-crypto-crackdown-2023-06-16 /&quot;>;整个行业的打破规则文化&lt;/a>;。本月早些时候，SEC 起诉了主要交易所 Coinbase 和 Binance。&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;“SEC 活动的不确定性导致价格走势疲软，贝莱德出面“支持”，感觉有点不同，”Usman 表示Ahmad，渣打银行风险投资部门的加密货币交易所 Zodia Markets 首席执行官 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reuters.com/companies/STAN.L/&quot;target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;(STAN.L) &lt;/a>; 和香港加密货币公司 BC Technology。&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;“尽管如此，随着利率持续上升，可能会面临进一步的挑战，”他说。&lt;/p>;&lt;h2>;相关画廊： &lt;/h2>;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cloudfront-us-east-2.images.arcpublishing.com/reuters/FCVB3Q4PVZMW7LBO3BK27DU7MU.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;>;&lt;div>;&lt;small style=&quot;color: #999 ;&quot;>;2013 年 9 月 17 日，这张照片插图中是比特币爱好者 Mike Caldwell 在他位于犹他州桑迪的办公室中的一些硬币。REUTERS/Jim Urquhart/File Photo&lt;/small>;&lt;/div>;&lt;img src=&quot;https:/ /cloudfront-us-east-2.images.arcpublishing.com/reuters/INPKL4FL7VNQFD24ZBHD3Q254A.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;>;&lt;div>;&lt;small style=&quot;color: #999;&quot;>;在其办公室外可以看到 BlackRock 徽标2016 年 10 月 17 日，美国纽约。REUTERS/Brendan McDermid/档案照片&lt;/small>;&lt;/div>;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cloudfront-us-east-2.images.arcpublishing.com/ reuters/LMDVOJXAGROCREDZ4PXHYHS3ZM.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;>;&lt;div>;&lt;small style=&quot;color: #999;&quot;>;2015 年 7 月 28 日，纽约金融区的纽约比特币中心展示了比特币标志。 REUTERS/布伦丹·麦克德米德/档案照片&lt;/小>;&lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Mon, 26 Jun 2023 20:55:07 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Special Report: US, Swedish prosecutors study graft complaint naming son of Turkey“s Erdogan]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://reuters.com/article/turkey-investigation-erdogan/special-report-us-swedish-prosecutors-study-graft-complaint-naming-son-of-turkeys-erdogan-idUSKBN2YC0U2]]><description> &lt;div>;&lt;i>;2023-06-26T12:46:30.036Z&lt;/i>;&lt;/div>;&lt;p>;美国和瑞典的反腐败机构正在审查一项指控，指控一家美国公司的瑞典子公司承诺如果土耳其总统雷杰普·塔伊普·埃尔多安的儿子帮助其在该国获得主导市场地位，将支付数千万美元的回扣。&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;路透社看到的通讯和商业文件中详细介绍了拟议的计划。 ，以及一位熟悉此事的人士。路透社首次报道了这一计划以及由此产生的初步调查。&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;根据个人向当局提交并经路透社审查的投诉，最终没有支付任何回扣。事实上，据路透社看到的两名知情人士和公司通讯称，瑞典公司 Dignita Systems AB 在去年年底突然放弃了该项目。&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;Dignita 的美国所有者向路透社证实，该项目被撤销，称其已获悉土耳其“可能存在令人担忧的行为”，并解雇了几名相关人员。&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;根据投诉，该公司的计划是让埃尔多安总统的政府通过法规，以促进Dignita 产品的销售：仪表板呼气分析仪，可在驾驶员醉酒时锁定车辆点火装置。&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;作为对其产品 10 年商业独家销售权的回报，Dignita 承诺将支付数千万美元的游说费诉状称，通过一家空壳公司，向比拉尔·埃尔多安 (Bilal Erdogan) 担任董事会成员的两家机构提供了资金。&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;尽管这一努力在 9 月份就被泡汤了，但它提供了罕见的洞察力，让我们了解投资者如何将比拉尔·埃尔多安 (Bilal Erdogan) 视为接触埃尔多安总统的关键人物，他&lt;a href=&quot;/world/middle-east/turkeys-erdogan-triumphs-election-test-extending-his-20-year-rule-2023-05-29/&quot;>; 5 月 28 日赢得了新的五年授权。&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;Dignita 首席执行官安德斯·埃里克森 (Anders Eriksson) 告诉路透社，他无法讨论这一涉嫌计划，因为他即将离开公司，并受到以下约束：保密协议。&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;比拉尔·埃尔多安通过律师表示，有关他与 Dignita 勾结的指控“完全不正确”。律师补充说，这是一张“谎言网”。土耳其总统通讯局的一名高级官员拒绝对本文发表评论。&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;路透社无法独立确认总统埃尔多安和他的儿子比拉尔是否知道或参与了 Dignita 所谓的回扣计划。&lt; /p>;&lt;p>;四月份收到投诉后，美国司法部和瑞典检察官分别指派一名特工和一名侦探督察进行初步调查，以确定美国和瑞典反贿赂法的任何条款是否可能违反美国和瑞典的反贿赂法。根据路透社看到的官方回应，已被侵犯。初步调查可能不会导致正式调查或指控。&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;美国和瑞典反腐败专家表示，在这两个国家，承诺支付佣金在某些情况下可能构成刑事犯罪。华盛顿反腐败监督机构美国透明国际组织的律师斯科特·格雷塔克表示，在美国，即使没有资金易手，也可以认定违反《反海外腐败法》(FCPA)。 “但你必须证明双方达成了协议，并且存在某种公开行为，例如开设银行账户，为这笔钱提供一个去处。”&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;司法部发言人瑞典检察官表示不予置评。&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;美国可能有权根据 FCPA 调查 Dignita 在土耳其的行为，因为这家瑞典公司由 1A Smart Start LLC 所有，该公司是一家位于德克萨斯州的公司，属于向世界上最大的资产管理公司之一阿波罗全球管理公司询问。&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;Apollo 将有关其所谓角色的问题转给了 Smart Start，该公司表示，它从未在土耳其销售过产品或产生任何收入。&lt;/p>;该公司在给路透社的一份声明中表示，“在得知土耳其未来商业机会的潜在令人担忧的行为后，我们立即调查并采取了纠正措施，包括解雇唯一员工和相关第三方顾问。” “因此，我们没有继续在土耳其开展业务。”&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;根据土耳其公司记录，Smart Start 保留了一家在土耳其注册的附属公司。&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;瑞典初步消息对 Dignita 土耳其活动的调查正值安卡拉和斯德哥尔摩双边关系的敏感时刻。 &lt;a href=&quot;/world/turkey-wont-back-swedish-nato-bid-unless-it-stops-anti-turkish-protests-erdogan-2023-06-14/&quot;>;土耳其已封锁瑞典&lt;/a>;瑞典公司拒绝加入北大西洋公约组织（北约），指责北欧国家为恐怖分子提供庇护，但瑞典当局拒绝了这一指控。&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;这家瑞典公司的计划取决于说服土耳其当局使用根据路透社看到的 2022 年夏季为埃尔多安总统准备的八张幻灯片演示文稿，该公司对某些类别的驾驶员和车辆强制要求其呼吸分析仪和点火锁，然后获得 10 年的独家供应权。&lt;/p>;&lt; p>;根据商业文件，经过四年的令人沮丧的努力，Dignita 终于能够向土耳其领导人写了一封信，概述了其计划，其中包括 2022 年 6 月消息的副本。&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;这个机会出现了据一位知情人士透露，大约四个月前，Dignita 的一名代表据称于去年 2 月在伊斯坦布尔与比拉尔·埃尔多安会面，审查了双管齐下的战略。&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;根据第一部分路透社看到的一份长达 11 页的“营销探索协议”详细阐述了这一战略。Smart Start 的土耳其子公司承诺向一家总部位于伊斯坦布尔的空壳公司定期支付咨询费，该空壳公司由瑞典和美国精心挑选的人士控制&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;向空壳公司支付的咨询费从每台设备每月 50 美分到 3 美元不等，具体取决于配备 Dignita 套件的车辆数量。在此基础上，在设想的 10 年独家经营期内，向空壳公司支付的 50 万辆汽车的总费用将达到 5,400 万美元，而 200 万辆汽车的总费用将滚雪球般达到 3.84 亿美元，日期为 2022 年 3 月的协议以及 Dignita 的信件据知情人士透露，该战略的第二部分仅进行了口头讨论，呼吁空壳公司向比拉尔·埃尔多安 (Bilal Erdogan) 担任董事会成员的两家机构伊本 (Ibn) 提供大量捐款。哈尔顿大学和图格瓦青年基金会。&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;伊本·哈尔顿大学由图尔格夫创立，图尔格夫是埃尔多安总统在 20 世纪 90 年代担任伊斯坦布尔市长时帮助创建的慈善组织。与此同时，Tugva 已注册为非营利组织，有权为社会福利项目募集捐款。它在土耳其的两打城市经营学生宿舍。&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;这两个基金会已扩展到大型社会福利业务，支撑着反对派领导人所说的埃尔多安总统用来照顾选民的全国性赞助体系。 .&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;土耳其总统通讯局的高级官员拒绝就政治对手提出的庇护指控发表评论。图尔格夫的一位发言人表示，该基金会与 Dignita 没有任何关系，并补充说，有关该慈善机构不正常活动的指控毫无根据。该发言人表示：“为了确保我们活动的透明度，我们的行政和财务流程会定期由独立审计师进行评估。”伊本哈尔顿大学和图格瓦的董事没有回复寻求置评的消息。&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;比拉尔·埃尔多安很少出现在公开场合。这位 42 岁的商人与埃尔多安家族的其他成员一样，拥有海运和建筑公司 BMZ 集团的少数股权。&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;他的名字过去曾与涉嫌腐败联系在一起。 2016年，意大利检察官对比拉尔·埃尔多安进行了洗钱调查，怀疑他在未申报的情况下将现金带入该国。他否认了这一指控，意大利检察官最终以缺乏证据为由放弃了调查。去年，俄罗斯政府声称有证据表明埃尔多安总统的儿子从与叙利亚伊斯兰国的跨境石油贸易中获利。俄罗斯拒绝分享其证据。比拉尔·埃尔多安否认了这些指控，称激进叛乱分子是土耳其的敌人。&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;Dignita 于 2017 年踏入土耳其，雄心勃勃地出售其交通安全设备。土耳其公司记录显示，那一年，Dignita 首席执行官埃里克森 (Eriksson) 掌舵了 Smart Start 成立的土耳其公司。&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;多年来，Dignita 和 Smart Start 几乎没有取得任何进展，因为他们无法知情人士称，即使是间接接触埃尔多安总统。&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;2021 年初取得了突破，埃里克森的一名助手向一位土耳其神学教授介绍了这家瑞典公司的计划。据知情人士透露，政治家伊尔凡·冈杜兹(Irfan Gunduz)。该人士表示，Dignita 选择与这位政治家接触是因为众所周知，他与比拉尔·埃尔多安关系密切，而埃尔多安反过来又可以提供与土耳其总统的接触。冈杜兹 (Gunduz) 担任伊本·哈尔顿大学 (Ibn Haldun University) 董事会主席；比拉尔·埃尔多安 (Bilal Erdogan) 是副主席。&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;冈杜兹于 5 月 30 日到达美国，他说自己正在出差，他告诉路透社，这“都是八卦”，并补充说“我和比拉尔都不是”听说过这家公司；曾经见过这家公司。”&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;突然间，在所谓的与 Gunduz 会面之后，大门开始敞开，Dignita 能够与埃尔多安总统政府的一名高级成员讨论他们将如何修改据公司信件和知情人士透露，交通安全法规涵盖了呼吸分析仪和点火锁的使用。&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;一些国家要求公共交通运营商以及被定罪的醉酒司机在其车辆上配备点火锁系统。在启动发动机之前，驾驶员必须向吹嘴吹气：如果呼出的酒精浓度高于法律允许的限值，该装置会阻止发动机启动。&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;2021 年春季，Dignita 了解到：据知情人士透露，Gunduz 正在寻求预付游说费，可能高达 1 亿美元。 “让我们讨论一下，”Dignita 首席执行官埃里克森在 6 月 8 日发给他的土耳其助手的消息中说道。&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;在路透社看到的通信中，埃里克森和他的助手最初提到了冈杜兹和比拉尔·埃尔多安的名字– 或者在比拉勒的情况下被称为“儿子” – 特别是在讨论会议安排时，但据知情人士透露，后来采取了预防措施，将土耳其方面指定为“游说团”。&lt;/p>;&lt;埃里克森在一条消息中表示：“如果游说集团为此获得 1 亿美元，他们会非常高兴。” “我无法想象他们有这么多钱，或者他们将有机会如此轻松地再次赚到 1 亿美元。”&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;路透社无法独立确认 Gunduz 是否要求支付一笔款项。游说费。&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;在随后向助手发出的信息中，埃里克森试图澄清这笔费用将购买哪些服务。 “我们希望游说集团能够长期支持我们，并‘保护’我们免受竞争，”他在同一天的另一条消息中写道。他说，如果允许竞争，费用将减半。&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;埃里克森还明确表示，Dignita 在开始在土耳其赚钱之前不会支付任何游说费。这位首席执行官在 6 月 14 日的一条消息中表示：“如果他们不同意，我们最好停下来，因为我们的所有者永远不会允许我们在收到报酬之前向他们付款。”&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;到 2022 年初，据知情人士透露，瑞典和土耳其双方已经放弃了预付款的想法，转而采用所谓的双管齐下的策略，即通过空壳公司支付持续的游说费。知情人士称，去年 2 月 25 日，在伊斯坦布尔亚洲一侧的一所儿童音乐学校内，据称与比拉尔·埃尔多安 (Bilal Erdogan) 会面后，Dignita 明白应该向埃尔多安总统发送一封正式信函公司信件显示，概述了其业务宣传。&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;公司信件显示，2022 年夏天，Eriksson 收到了 Smart Start 首席执行官 Matthew Strausz 的信件草稿和一些指示。 “安德斯，”这位美国首席执行官在 6 月 23 日的一条消息中告诉他的瑞典同事。 “见附件。除了我们如何向总统讲话之外，这是我们将使用的草案。它已经得到律师的批准。你能翻译并发回以供最终签署吗？阿波罗有一个（...）律师将进行最终审查，然后我们将提供给您亲自发送的信息。”&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;Strausz 将问题转给了 Smart Start 的发言人，但该发言人没有提及首席执行官在公司回答问题时所扮演的角色。路透社。&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;路透社看到的这封信的最终版本日期为 6 月 29 日，并由 Dignita 首席执行官用蓝色墨水签署。在这封三页的信中，埃里克森首先赞扬了埃尔多安总统在改善土耳其道路安全方面取得的成就，并表示他的公司愿意帮助他走得更远。这位首席执行官表示，如果醉酒驾驶罪犯和校车等公共交通车辆强制使用点火锁，并且如果 Dignita 获得合同，该公司随时准备讨论“必要的基本保证和条件”。据知情人士透露，这封信已发送给政客冈杜兹，并于 7 月中旬转交给总统。&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;尽管 Dignita该人士表示，无法确定埃尔多安总统是否看到了这封信，但它产生了立竿见影的积极影响。同月，这家瑞典公司从 Gunduz 获悉，根据公司通讯，将很快与埃尔多安总统政府的一名高级成员（可能还有总统本人）举行会议，讨论下一步行动。&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;根据土耳其商业记录，7 月晚些时候，计划中的空壳公司在伊斯坦布尔成立。法律文件显示，其目的之一是充当国内外公司之间的调解人。 8 月，Dignita 为埃尔多安总统准备了八张幻灯片的文件。&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;然而，据另一位知情人士透露，Dignita 在美国的所有者 Smart Start 和 Apollo 已经发展壮大担心土耳其项目的不良方面，包括它可能违反美国反贿赂法。该人士表示，经过内部审查后，决定停止该项目。&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;9 月，Dignita 通知土耳其方面的一位谈判参与者，这家瑞典公司已放弃该项目，但没有路透社看到的一条消息显示，给出了一个原因。&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;参与者回答说：“让我们期待最好的结果。”&lt;/p>;&lt;h2>;相关图库：&lt;/h2>;&lt;img src=&quot;https ://cloudfront-us-east-2.images.arcpublishing.com/reuters/L5MRAZQJBRP4XAXKPIUHKLJZYU.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;>;&lt;div>;&lt;small style=&quot;color: #999;&quot;>;土耳其总理塔伊普·埃尔多安 (L ）在儿子比拉尔的陪同下，于 2014 年 3 月 30 日在安卡拉的 AK 党总部向他的支持者致意。 REUTERS/Stringer/File Photo&lt;/small>;&lt;/div>;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cloudfront-us- east-2.images.arcpublishing.com/reuters/R7KU52B3XROGZNI3TYG44OODSM.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;>;&lt;div>;&lt;small style=&quot;color: #999;&quot;>;土耳其总统塔伊普·埃尔多安在安卡拉举行的新闻发布会上宣布新内阁，土耳其，2023 年 6 月 3 日。REUTERS/Umit Bektas/档案照片&lt;/small>;&lt;/div>;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cloudfront-us-east-2.images.arcpublishing.com/reuters/H245TUDO55MANDOYUSWKY6I7CQ.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;>;&lt;div>;&lt;small style=&quot;color: #999;&quot;>;5 月 28 日总统决选投票之前，汽车驶过土耳其总统塔伊普·埃尔多安 (Tayyip Erdogan) 的竞选广告牌，土耳其安卡拉，5 月 26 日， 2023.路透社/伊夫·赫尔曼/档案照片&lt;/小>;&lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Mon, 26 Jun 2023 20:55:07 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Russian officials emphasise unity after aborted mutiny]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://reuters.com/article/ukraine-crisis-russia/russian-officials-emphasise-unity-after-aborted-mutiny-idUSKBN2YC086]]><description> &lt;div>;&lt;i>;2023-06-26T12:52:52Z&lt;/i>;&lt;/div>;&lt;p>;周一，俄罗斯高级官员聚集在弗拉基米尔·普京总统周围，对似乎构成雇佣军兵变的问题仍未得到解答这是对他 23 年统治权力的最大威胁。&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;在强大的瓦格纳集团的战士占领军事总部并向莫斯科进军后的第一个工作日，官员们仍然没有透露有关这起事件的细节。协议突然结束了叛乱。&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;以总理身份领导普京内阁的米哈伊尔·米舒斯京承认，俄罗斯面临“稳定的挑战”，并呼吁公众忠诚。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;他在电视转播的政府会议上表示：“我们需要作为一个团队共同行动，保持所有力量的团结，团结在总统周围。”&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;没有关于叛乱的任何消息。普京本人周六曾表示，这次叛乱使俄罗斯的生存受到威胁，并誓言要惩罚叛乱背后的人。克里姆林宫发布了他向工业论坛参与者表示祝贺的视频，但没有说明该视频的拍摄时间。&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;在另一项显然是为了传达常态的举动中，当局发布了国防部长谢尔盖·绍伊古的视频。叛变者要求解雇他，导致人们猜测，他的免职可能是结束叛乱安排的一部分。&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;瓦格纳的老板和叛变领袖叶夫根尼·普里戈任(Yevgeny Prigozhin)仍然没有公开露面。最后一次出现是在周六，他在一辆 SUV 的后座上微笑着离开南部城市顿河畔罗斯托夫，在他命令他们下台之前被他的手下抓获。&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;俄罗斯国家反恐委员会表示该国局势&lt;a href=&quot;/world/europe/moscow-mayor-cancels-wagner-mutiny-anti-terror-regime-city-statement-2023-06-26/&quot;>;稳定&lt;/a>; 。莫斯科市长谢尔盖·索比亚宁（Sergei Sobyanin）周六告诉居民待在室内，因为叛乱武装分子已逼近首都数百公里范围，他表示他将取消反恐安全制度。&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;普里戈任和他的领导者战斗人员被给予免于起诉的条件，以换取他们的撤离。但国家控制的新闻机构周一报道称，针对普里戈任的刑事案件仍然悬而未决，仍在追查中。&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;周六的非同寻常事件让对俄罗斯友好和敌对的政府都在摸索背后发生的事情的答案。场景以及接下来可能发生的事情。&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;俄罗斯的盟友中国表示支持莫斯科维护国家稳定。俄罗斯高级外交官周日访问了中国。乌克兰及其一些西方盟友表示，骚乱暴露了俄罗斯的裂痕。&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;欧盟外交政策负责人何塞普·博雷尔(Josep Borrell) &lt;a href=&quot; /world/europe/eu-says-aborted-Russia-mutiny-shows-moscows-military-power-is-cracking-2023-06-26/&quot;>;在卢森堡抵达与会面时告诉记者&lt;/a>;来自27个成员国的部长们。&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;德国外长安娜莱娜·贝尔博克表示，入侵乌克兰正在摧毁俄罗斯，普京称之为应对威胁的“特别军事行动”，西方将继续返回基辅。&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;周六，在乌克兰作战的瓦格纳雇佣军越境进入俄罗斯，占领了罗斯托夫的战争指挥部，并在 1,100 公里（700 英里）的路程中大部分抵达莫斯科，在路上没有遇到任何抵抗。地面，然后突然停止前进。&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;他们的指挥官，&lt;a href=&quot;/world/europe/who-is- Russian-mercenary-chief-yevgeny-prigozhin-2023-06-24/&quot;>;Prigozhin &lt;/a>;，要求将国防部长绍伊古和陆军最高将领移交给他。国防部周一发布的视频显示，绍伊古与一名同事乘坐飞机，并在指挥所听取报告。没有证据表明它是在何时何地拍摄的，也没有声音。&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;总参谋长瓦列里·格拉西莫夫(Valery Gerasimov)自事件发生以来也没有在公开场合露面。克里姆林宫表示，人事变动问题是总统的唯一特权，不可能成为任何协议的一部分。&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;随着周六事态的发展，普京在电视讲话中将俄罗斯的混乱与1917 年导致了布尔什维克革命。&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;北约表示，这些事件表明克里姆林宫在对乌克兰发动战争时犯下了严重的战略错误，西方防务联盟不会因为受到威胁而结束对乌克兰的支持。&lt; /p>;&lt;p>;莫斯科已宣布周一为非工作日，以便有时间解决问题，而且几乎没有证据表明首都的安全有所加强。&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;美国国务卿安东尼·布林肯周六与七国集团和欧盟同行进行了交谈，&lt;a href=&quot;/world/europe/us-secretary-state-blinken-says-Russia-turmoil-could-take-months-play-out-2023-06-25 /&quot;>;暗示&lt;/a>;这场动荡可能需要几个月的时间才能结束，并称俄罗斯的外表已经出现了更多裂痕。&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;乌克兰总统弗拉基米尔·泽连斯基在与美国总统乔·拜登的单独电话中讨论了这些事件泽连斯基在推特上表示：“世界必须向俄罗斯施加压力，直到国际秩序恢复”。&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;国家电视台表示，普京将本周参加俄罗斯安理会会议，但没有详细说明，白俄罗斯贝尔塔通讯社称，普京和卢卡申科在周六至少两次通话后，周日再次通话。&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;法国总统埃马纽埃尔·马克龙告诉《普罗旺斯报》报纸称，叛乱暴露了俄罗斯阵营内部的分裂以及俄罗斯军队和瓦格纳的脆弱性。&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;普京前盟友、前罪犯，他的部队在俄罗斯进行了 16 个月战争中最血腥的战斗。乌克兰现年 62 岁的普里戈任本月无视将其部队置于国防部指挥之下的命令。&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;他于周五发动叛乱，此前他声称军方在俄罗斯国防部的一次空袭中杀死了他的一些人。乌克兰国防部否认。&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;乌克兰表示，自本月早些时候开始反攻以来，乌克兰军队已收复南部前线约 130 平方公里（50 平方英里）的土地。&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;国防部副部长汉娜·马利亚尔周一告诉国家电视台，过去一周几乎没有什么重大变化。俄罗斯否认乌克兰有关战场城市巴克穆特周围小规模进展的报道。&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;乌克兰联合部队指挥官谢尔盖·纳耶夫 (Serhiy Nayev) 回应了有关瓦格纳战斗机的推测性报道 - 据报道周末将返回俄罗斯控制的地区乌克兰地区 - 可以转移到白俄罗斯，从北部攻击乌克兰。&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;“如果发生这种情况，敌人试图越过国家边界，对他们来说无异于自杀，”纳耶夫在Telegram。&lt;/p>;&lt;h2>;相关图库：&lt;/h2>;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cloudfront-us-east-2.images.arcpublishing.com/reuters/NT532SXIU5PK3MZLO75HA7JZ5Q.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;>; &lt;div>;&lt;small style=&quot;color: #999;&quot;>;2023 年 6 月 25 日，人们站在俄罗斯莫斯科封闭的红场附近。REUTERS/Evgenia Novozhenina&lt;/small>;&lt;/div>;&lt;img src=&quot;https: //cloudfront-us-east-2.images.arcpublishing.com/reuters/M7HJA6JL2JMTHOHHIDIHADZJJY.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;>;&lt;div>;&lt;small style=&quot;color: #999;&quot;>;人们在克里姆林宫附近的亚历山德罗夫斯基花园散步2023 年 6 月 25 日在俄罗斯莫斯科。REUTERS/Evgenia Novozhenina&lt;/small>;&lt;/div>;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cloudfront-us-east-2.images.arcpublishing.com/reuters/CD7CKMHRTNNYLDPSU2R5TX6IPQ.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;>;&lt;div>;&lt;small style=&quot;color: #999;&quot;>;2023 年 6 月 25 日，俄罗斯顿河畔罗斯托夫，一名妇女骑着摩托车沿着顿河堤岸行驶。REUTERS/Alexander Ermochenko&lt; /small>;&lt;/div>;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cloudfront-us-east-2.images.arcpublishing.com/reuters/U4DQJ7E3EVJWTDOPAXZ2H6M43A.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;>;&lt;div>;&lt;small style=&quot;color : #999;&quot;>;Fighters of Wagner private mercenary group pull out of the headquarters of the Southern Military District to return to base, in the city of Rostov-on-Don, Russia, June 24, 2023. REUTERS/Stringer&lt;/small >;&lt;/div>;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cloudfront-us-east-2.images.arcpublishing.com/reuters/JJC274LUYRM6XFRDA6WMQ5UP6A.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;>;&lt;div>;&lt;small style=&quot;color: # 999;&quot;>;Fighters of Wagner private mercenary group pull out of the headquarters of the Southern Military District to return to base, in the city of Rostov-on-Don, Russia, June 24, 2023. REUTERS/Stringer&lt;/small>;&lt; /div>;&lt;br>;&lt;hr>;&lt;div>;获取更多RSS：&lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.net&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https:// feedx.net&lt;/a>; &lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.best&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.best&lt;/a>;&lt;br>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Mon, 26 Jun 2023 20:55:07 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Oil up, stocks dip after short-lived Russian mutiny]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://reuters.com/article/global-markets/stocks-down-gold-up-as-investors-embrace-safe-havens-after-russia-mutiny-idUSKBN2YB0FN]]><description> &lt;div>;&lt;i>;2023-06-25T23:28:42Z&lt;/i>;&lt;/div>;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cloudfront-us-east-2.images.arcpublishing.com/reuters/7K7TV7EYJ5OSBL5DKARPMPUXNY.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;>;&lt;div>;&lt;small style=&quot;color: #999;&quot;>;An investor sits in front of a board showing stock information at a brokerage office in Beijing, China, December 7, 2018. REUTERS/Thomas Peter/File Photo&lt;/small>;&lt;/div>;&lt;p>;Oil nudged higher in early trade on Monday as an abortive weekend mutiny by Russian mercenaries raised questions about crude supply, though other financial markets started steadily with investors unsure of any further immediate implications.&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;Brent crude futures rose 1.3% to $74.78 a barrel and US crude was up by the same margin to $70, recouping a little of losses made last week. S&amp;amp;P 500 futures were 0.2% higher and currency markets were broadly steady.&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;Russian mercenaries made a &lt;a href=&quot;/world/europe/rebel-russian-mercenaries-halt-advance-moscow-kremlin-says-fighters-face-no-2023-06-24/&quot;>;short-lived rebellion&lt;/a>; on Saturday, seizing the southern city of Rostov and advancing on Moscow demanding the removal of Russian military commanders in charge of the war in Ukraine.&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;The private Wagner army &lt;a href=&quot;/world/europe/wagner-head-suggests-his-mercenaries-headed-moscow-take-army-leadership-2023-06-24/&quot;>;then withdrew&lt;/a>; after striking a &lt;a href=&quot;/world/europe/russian-mercenary-boss-prigozhin-move-belarus-under-wagner-deal-kremlin-says-2023-06-24/&quot;>;deal&lt;/a>; guaranteeing their safety and the exile of their leader, &lt;a href=&quot;/world/europe/who-is-russian-mercenary-chief-yevgeny-prigozhin-2023-06-24/&quot;>;Yevgeny Prigozhin&lt;/a>;, to Belarus. The consequences for the Ukraine war were not clear, though the challenge to Russian President Vladimir Putin&#39;s authority was the starkest in decades of his leadership.&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;&quot;Geopolitical risk amid internal instability in Russia has increased,&quot; said Rystad Energy analysts Jorge Leon. &quot;As such, we are likely to see a marginal uptick in oil prices in the coming days, if the situation does not deteriorate.&quot;&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;US Secretary of State Antony &lt;a href=&quot;/world/europe/us-secretary-state-blinken-says-russia-turmoil-could-take-months-play-out-2023-06-25/&quot;>;Blinken&lt;/a>; said the turmoil in Russia could take months to play out, while Italy&#39;s foreign minister said it had shattered the &quot;myth&quot; of Russian unity.&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;Elsewhere markets were already on edge about a darkening growth outlook, as China&#39;s post-pandemic recovery stalls and global interest rates remain high, and traders were unwilling to take any new positions on the basis of Russian events.&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;The risk-sensitive Australian dollar was steady at $0.6682. The euro nursed last week&#39;s modest drop at $1.0906 and sterling held at $1.2722.&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;&quot;I don&#39;t think the market can get its head around working out if there are implications,&quot; said Ray Attrill, head of foreign exchange strategy at National Australia Bank in Sydney.&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;&quot;People may think that ultimately Putin&#39;s grip on power is weakened here. Maybe the Ukrainians may be emboldened to be upping their counteroffensives,&quot; he said, but without obvious progress traders in Asia would be focused on China.&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;China returns from holidays with the yuan having dropped sharply in offshore trade, leaving investors looking to the morning&#39;s fix of the onshore trading band for signs of the central bank&#39;s level of comfort with the slide.&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;The offshore yuan last traded at 7.21 per dollar.&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;The Japanese yen , which has been on a slide as global interest rate expectations rise and Japan&#39;s central bank stays steadyfastly dovish, steadied at 143.57.&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;Japan&#39;s top currency diplomat Masato &lt;a href=&quot;/markets/currencies/japans-top-fx-diplomat-escalates-warning-against-weak-yen-2023-06-25/&quot;>;Kanda&lt;/a>; said on Monday authorities will respond to any excessive moves and did not rule out intervening as happened last year.&lt;/p>;</description><pubDate> Mon, 26 Jun 2023 20:25:08 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[At least one dead, dozens of homes damaged after storms hit US Midwest and South]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://reuters.com/article/usa-weather/at-least-one-dead-dozens-of-homes-damaged-after-storms-hit-us-midwest-and-south-idUSKBN2YC0QN]]><description> &lt;div>;&lt;i>;2023-06-26T11:45:06Z&lt;/i>;&lt;/div>;&lt;p>;Tornadoes and thunderstorms hit the US Midwest and South on Sunday, leaving dozens of homes damaged and at least one person dead in Indiana, authorities said on Monday.&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;The National Weather Service said multiple tornadoes were reported on Sunday afternoon in central Indiana.&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;Emergency officials from Martin County, Indiana confirmed the victim&#39;s death. Emergency Management Director Cameron Wolf said the victim&#39;s injured partner was airlifted to hospital.&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;They lived in a two-storey log cabin, which was destroyed by the storms. Further details were not immediately available.&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;&quot;Damage is random, its kind of widespread,&quot; Wolf said in an interview to PBS. The damage mostly happened out in the country he said, adding that towns were not hit that hard by the storms.&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;Images and footage from local media showed fallen trees had blocked roads and homes were damaged. A large hail storm was also reported in Indiana and adjacent states, officials said.&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;Fire Chief Eric Funkhouser from the town of Bargersville, south of Indianapolis, said that while no casualties were reported, about 75 homes sustained moderate to severe damage after the weather, according an NBC News affiliate.&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;Emergency shelters were set up in central Indiana for those whose homes were damaged and destroyed.&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;As of Monday morning, about half a million utility customers faced power outages due to the weather in the US Midwest and South, according to outage tracking website PowerOutage.us.&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;At least one person died and about two dozen people were injured after &lt;a href=&quot;https://reut.rs/3NuqWpk&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;a tornado hit central Mississippi&lt;/a>; a few days ago.&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;A dangerous heat wave &lt;a href=&quot;https://reut.rs/3XaX4mx&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;had also recently&lt;/a>; helped spawn deadly tornadoes in Texas and Florida, where at least four people were killed this month in twisters that touched down in the panhandles of the states. Flooding forced almost 150 people out of their homes.&lt;/p>;&lt;h2>;Related Galleries:&lt;/h2>;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cloudfront-us-east-2.images.arcpublishing.com/reuters/NUEX4WIWO5IIJFDT3GZ2QVHRC4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;>;&lt;div>;&lt;small style=&quot;color: #999;&quot;>;Debris is lifted into the air by a possible tornado during severe weather near Greenwood, Indiana, US, June 25, 2023 in this screen grab obtained from a social media video. Eric Ford via TMX/via REUTERS /File photo&lt;/small>;&lt;/div>;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cloudfront-us-east-2.images.arcpublishing.com/reuters/ICTCI7PZA5PQ5CUT6LPW6TOISQ.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;>;&lt;div>;&lt;small style=&quot;color: #999;&quot;>;Debris is lifted into the air by a possible tornado during severe weather near Greenwood, Indiana, US, June 25, 2023 in this screen grab obtained from a social media video. Eric Ford via TMX/via REUTERS&lt;/small>;&lt;/div>;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cloudfront-us-east-2.images.arcpublishing.com/reuters/QDG5BBJ75BNXHF72VKVA6PVZUA.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;>;&lt;div>;&lt;small style=&quot;color: #999;&quot;>;Debris is lifted into the air by a possible tornado during severe weather near Greenwood, Indiana, US, June 25, 2023 in this screen grab obtained from a social media video. Eric Ford via TMX/via REUTERS&lt;/small>;&lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Mon, 26 Jun 2023 20:25:08 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Mexico“s Ebrard pursues presidential prize as unifier in polarized times]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://reuters.com/article/mexico-ebrard/mexicos-ebrard-pursues-presidential-prize-as-unifier-in-polarized-times-idUSKBN2YC0RZ]]><description> &lt;div>;&lt;i>;2023-06-26T11:54:19Z&lt;/i>;&lt;/div>;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cloudfront-us-east-2.images.arcpublishing.com/reuters/O6BF3SUPERNDBEAKN3XPRCRSNY.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;>;&lt;div>;&lt;small style=&quot;color: #999;&quot;>;Marcelo Ebrard, Mexico&#39;s former Foreign Minister and one of the candidates pursuing the ruling MORENA party&#39;s candidacy for the 2024 presidential election, takes part in a campaign rally at a hotel in Mexico City, Mexico June 19, 2023. REUTERS/Henry Romero/File photo&lt;/small>;&lt;/div>;&lt;p>;Urbane, socially progressive and eager to put Mexico on the world stage, Marcelo Ebrard presents a sharp contrast to the popular, sharp-tongued defender of the country&#39;s impoverished hinterlands he hopes to succeed as president.&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;Having followed once in the footsteps of President Andres Manuel Lopez Obrador as mayor of Mexico City, Ebrard is banking he can do it again in the race to be the ruling National Regeneration Movement&#39;s (MORENA) 2024 presidential candidate.&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;This month, the 63-year-old Ebrard stood down as foreign minister to seek the MORENA nomination, unleashing a contest that could strain the leftist party&#39;s unity.&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;His more business-oriented and moderate instincts stand apart from Lopez Obrador&#39;s outspoken rhetoric, but also raise doubts about whether he can get enough support from a party whose base identifies strongly with the president, analysts say.&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;Reuters spoke to over two dozen officials, politicians, diplomats, executives and aides to Ebrard to assess his chances of clinching the MORENA ticket for the June 2024 election.&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;A winner is expected on Sept. 6 after national polling.&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;Luis Huacuja, a political consultant and professor at the National Autonomous University of Mexico, said Ebrard&#39;s experience and record appeared to make him an &quot;ideal&quot; contender.&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;But that did not mean party loyalists would, when polled, see the more centrist Ebrard as most suited to upholding Lopez Obrador&#39;s legacy, he argued.&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;&quot;He could go down well in some quarters, and badly in others,&quot; Huacuja said.&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;Ebrard has won some early battles, &lt;a href=&quot;/world/americas/mexico-president-puts-unity-first-broker-compromise-succession-race-2023-06-08/&quot;>;persuading the president&lt;/a>; that contenders for the nomination should leave office, and that polls to pick the winner be open to the public.&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;He told Reuters &quot;hard&quot; left critics had long painted him as moderate, but said they had not governed - and that it was he who delivered results for the capital as mayor from 2006-2012.&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;Private investment flourished during his administration, Ebrard said, pointing to how the left&#39;s appeal in Mexico City extended from poorer households to the middle class, helping his successor secure a landslide victory.&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;That support was crucial to control Congress, he argued.&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;&quot;You need a coalition with the middle class either way,&quot; said Ebrard, who has been a key troubleshooter for Lopez Obrador, helping contain threats from former US president Donald Trump over immigration, trade and security.&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;While Lopez Obrador has slammed critics, clashed with business and questioned checks on presidential power, Ebrard, supporters say, is a unifier who will lift growth and reassure investors.&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;&quot;(Ebrard) is committed to the division of powers and strengthening institutions,&quot; said MORENA senator Rafael Espino.&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;If nominated, Ebrard is likely to become president, polling shows. MORENA is hot favorite to win, propelled by Lopez Obrador&#39;s approval ratings of around 60%. Mexican law bars presidents from re-election.&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;Polling shows Ebrard in a tight race with ex-Mexico City Mayor Claudia Sheinbaum, who has followed Lopez Obrador lock-step on policy. Many polls indicate Ebrard is better-known, but Sheinbaum more popular among MORENA&#39;s base. A survey published May 26 by newspaper Reforma gave &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reforma.com/encuesta-reforma-se-perfila-en-morena-contienda-de-dos/ar2611473&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;Sheinbaum a slight edge&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;Both contenders promise to defend Lopez Obrador&#39;s vision.&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;Aides to the president have told Reuters they believe he would &lt;a href=&quot;/world/americas/mexico-succession-puts-scientist-path-be-first-woman-president-2022-11-03/&quot;>;most like Sheinbaum&lt;/a>; to succeed him. Lopez Obrador denies this, and says voters must decide.&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;Some officials close to Lopez Obrador privately back Ebrard.&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;&quot;We need to unite the country,&quot; said one.&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;Ebrard is careful not to criticize the president. But he has staked out his own turf.&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;On June 11, MORENA&#39;s leadership agreed guidelines for the nomination contest stating contenders should avoid talking to media deemed conservative or hostile to the administration.&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;The next morning Ebrard gave an interview to journalist Ciro Gomez Leyva - a regular target of Lopez Obrador&#39;s broadsides - and declared himself open to all media, drawing fire from some MORENA supporters.&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;Ebrard dismisses such criticism, and says his legalization of same-sex marriage and abortion when Mexico City mayor was more radical than anything his detractors can lay claim to.&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;His independent streak has fed speculation he could break with MORENA if he feels the contest is unfair. Ebrard denies this, but has repeatedly called for a level playing field.&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;Vowing to prioritize security, healthcare, education and growth, Ebrard underlines the economic opportunity presented by so-called nearshoring - increased investment spurred by Washington&#39;s trade tensions with China.&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;In February, when Lopez Obrador threatened to deny billionaire Elon Musk&#39;s Tesla permission to build a plant in northern Mexico over water supply, Ebrard stepped in to ensure the deal &lt;a href=&quot;/business/autos-transportation/mexican-president-says-tesla-will-build-major-plant-northern-city-2023-02-28/&quot;>;prospered&lt;/a>;, three officials said.&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;Lopez Obrador has given MORENA&#39;s contenders room to maneuver by calling the succession &quot;continuity with change&quot;. But some Ebrard supporters hint he may be too independent of MORENA.&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;&quot;Sheinbaum agrees with Lopez Obrador&#39;s political project,&quot; said one senior executive backing Ebrard. &quot;Ebrard would be a different project.&quot;&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;A native of Mexico&#39;s poorer south, the folksy Lopez Obrador frames his presidency as the victory of a downtrodden majority over a corrupt, &#39;conservative&#39; minority.&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;The president, who has described sectors of the middle class as classist and racist, forged his electoral success on years of campaigning in forgotten rural areas, rewarding support with higher welfare spending and major public works.&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;The tall, bespectacled Ebrard, a veteran Mexico City political operator, is less at home in remote villages. He has instead targeted younger, metropolitan Mexicans, making light of himself in TikTok videos peppered with pop cultural nods.&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;Lopez Obrador wants MORENA to win a two-thirds congressional majority in 2024 to reshape the judiciary, which has resisted his efforts to strengthen state control over the economy.&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;Ebrard is best placed to win that super-majority, argued MORENA senator Martha Lucia Micher.&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;&quot;If we don&#39;t get two-thirds,&quot; she said, &quot;everything we want to do will suffer.&quot;&lt;/p>;</description><pubDate> Mon, 26 Jun 2023 20:25:08 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>